<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="957" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>49</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-02-01</startdate>
<enddate>1998-01-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Brave King GaoGaiGar</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Yuusha/Brave Series 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">GaoGaiGar TV</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">勇者王</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GGG</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">勇者王ガオガイガー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">GaoGaiGar: King of Braves</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">용자왕 가오가이거</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1717" type="Sequel">Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar Final</anime>
<anime id="745" type="Same Setting">Betterman</anime>
<anime id="1548" type="Other">Yuusha Tokkyuu Might Gaine</anime>
<anime id="1707" type="Other">Yuusha Exkaiser</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="354131">A super brobot favorite known to many devoted fans of mecha. Yelling, long and constant tranformation sequences, super attacks, large roster of robots (with tech detail) and a good chunk of heroic positive type of Gar. What`s not to like?</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gaogaigar.net/index_tv.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="726" type="Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="665" type="Character Design">Kimura Takahiro</name>
<name id="1519" type="Story Composition">Yamaguchi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="1531" type="Direction">Yonetani Yoshitomo</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
<name id="1071" type="Work">Tokyu Agency</name>
<name id="1019" type="Work">Nagoya TV Housou</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="657" type="Series Composition">Gobu Fuyunori</name>
</creators>
<description>One snowy night, the Amami couple who has no child encounter a huge white lion-shaped robot, which holds a baby. When they fearfully take that baby, the "lion" suddenly flies away. Though puzzling, Amami couple are happy to accept that baby as their own child.
Eight years later, the time is 2005 A.D. Without notice, a Zonder appear at the Tokyo Bay, merging with debris and a passing ship which have kids on its deck, advancing to Shinjyuku - the center of Tokyo. The Japanese Self-Defense Forces` conventional weapon has no effect and some kids are taken hostage.
But there is the hero who stands against that Zonder Robot. His name is Guy the Cyborg, the commander of GGG`s Mechanized Unit. The GGG ("Gutsy Geoid Guard") are the newly-made Japanese secret defense forces against the extraterrestrial invasion.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="310">6.35</permanent>
<temporary count="318">7.25</temporary>
<review count="1">5.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>191227.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1170</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>890</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>86</identifier>
<identifier>bsujdw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/works/list/detail.php?cid=4</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gaogaigar.net/index_tv.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_King_of_Braves_GaoGaiGar</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>勇者王ガオガイガー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2055</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88903</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2776" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>parasite</name>
<description>Parasites are life forms that feed off other beings in some way. In anime, they are often aliens and usually intelligent. For shock value, and to avoid having to draw aliens all the time, their prey is preferably human; they may see humans as food, as puppets for mind control, or simply as temporary body hosts. In every case, the human is the victim of a "merging", which is not to be confused with the more "amicable" symbiosis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3295" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>world domination</name>
<description>"Gee, Brain, what do you want to do tonight?"
"The same thing we do every night, Pinky: try to take over the world!"
A main objective for one of the characters is absolute control of not just one country, but a whole planet!</description>
<picurl>38878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3459" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-20">
<name>space monsters</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="19994" type="main character in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="6">6.40</rating>
<name>Hatsuno Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatsuno Hana is a childhood friend of Mamoru Amami, and closet love interest. Her cousin Ayame it often dragging her into dangerous situations. Hana remains unaware of Mamoru`s involvement in the events surrounding the Zonder invasion until Intestine Primeval captures her and several of the other children onboard the ship that the Primeval had used as robo material. At this point she sees Mamoru in his Latio form on their return to StealthGao II - Mamoru is unaware of this, and it is not until near the last battle with the Z-Master that she reveals this information to him. She was under the impression that the real Mamoru was replaced by an alien, and is relieved to know that Mamoru is the same one she has known all along, and becomes a steadfast supporter of Mamoru in the events to come. The other children soon thereafter declare that Mamoru and Hana should get married. She later reveals Mamoru`s identity to the other children during the battle with the New Machine Species Zonuda. In the epilogue, Hana comes to say goodbye to Mamoru wearing a wedding dress - the two share a kiss before Mamoru leaves with Galeon.
In King of Braves GaoGaiGar FINAL, Hana is the one with whom the introduction begins, taking a litter of Yosef`s puppies on a walk when she finds the wounded Ikumi Kaidou (Arma) engaged in combat with Repli-Mamoru. After the battle concludes (leading to the destruction of a harbor but leaving Hana and her dogs unscathed), Hana takes the unconscious Kaidou back to her home and questions him as to Mamoru`s actions and whereabouts. As the actions in the Trinary Solar System continue, Hana is often looked in upon to show the degradation of the situation on Earth. Despite the destruction being wrought upon the Earth, Hana remains determined that she will see Mamoru again. In the finale, she gets her wish, and is seen standing side-by-side with Mamoru and Kaidou before the memorial erected in honor of the GGG members who went missing in the crisis. She is also one of the singers for the first verse of Someday in the Sea of Stars: Character Version, which plays during said finale.
For much of the television series, Hana has an unfortunate tendency to be knocked unconscious. She almost compulsively repeats the phrase "I`m not scared" in times of mental stress - this was first taught to her by Mamoru as a coping mechanism.</description>
<picture>176779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4960" picture="153532.jpg">Yoshida Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19995" type="main character in" update="2015-08-25">
<rating votes="3">6.72</rating>
<name>Utsugi Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guy`s girlfriend and a GGG computer operator. Mikoto is responsible for launching the Gao Machines, activating the Final Fusion program and sending out equipment like the Dividing Driver.
Mikoto is a crucial part of the activation process of the Goldion Hammer, doing the final "relieving" of its safety device.
Mikoto`s parents died when EI-01 hit Tokyo. After passing out in the aftermath, the Zonderian Pasder implanted into her the spore of a new Zonder type, which slowly developed in her unbeknownst to her and everyone throughout the series. Following the defeat of the Primevals, the spore awoke, turning her into the "new machine species", or Zonuda. She drained all of the power out of the 3G Space Base, before landing in Tokyo in a fragment of one of the base ships. As a core part of Zonuda, Mikoto was alert but unable to do anything. After being reduced to a core in a final battle with GaoGaiGar, Zonuda turned back into its human-sized robot form, with Mikoto still contained within. Guy managed to use Mamoru to purify her, however, transforming the two into Evoluders.
Mikoto`s Evoluder abilities are less clear than Guy`s. She demonstrates that her nerve cells, at least, are capable of regeneration, and later shows high telepathic abilities (communicating with both Guy and Papillon Noir in spirit form numerous times throughout episode 8 of FINAL). Papillon at one point says that Mikoto became "an invincible life-form like the new machine species", which could be taken to mean that Mikoto is in fact incapable of being killed permanently, possessing a Zonuda-like regenerative ability.</description>
<picture>176759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2205" picture="186188.jpg">Hanba Tomoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19996" type="main character in" update="2015-08-25">
<rating votes="6">6.28</rating>
<name>Taiga Koutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taiga Koutarou is the loud, proud, and quite energetic president of the Space Development Corporation and chief of the Gutsy Geoid (later Galaxy) Guard. It is Taiga`s job to oversee GGG`s mission, and to approve the use of necessary procedures (Final Fusion, Symmetrical Docking) as well as more crucial and untested equipment (Goldion Hammer, Goldion Crusher, Projectile X and so on).
As Chief, his job is also to report to the GGG`s overseeing body (the Japanese Diet, then later the U.N) and also request more budget allocations as well as argue GGG`s case and purpose on occasion.
While GGG was based in Japan, his approval essentially represented the Prime Minister`s approval, and in space, it represented the approval of the U.N. Secretary General (according to the box containing the Gold Key).
He is apparently married and has two daughters(though it is not mentioned in the series or FINAL), and enjoys playing golf when not on duty as President or Chief. As such, he is handy with a golf club (the "Titanium-Head Driver" and later the "Taiga Wood").</description>
<picture>176761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19997" type="main character in" update="2015-08-25">
<rating votes="3">6.72</rating>
<name>Amami Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2191" picture="21747.jpg">Itou Maiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19998" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Amami Isamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176785.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20553" picture="23217.jpg">Shioya Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19999" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Amami Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2221" picture="83141.jpg">Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20000" type="main character in" update="2015-08-25">
<rating votes="21">8.76</rating>
<name>Shishiou Gai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A brave man with tremendous courage and enthusiasm, and the strength to never give up for the sake of life—even at the possible cost of his own.
Former astronaut and test pilot for the Space Development Corporation. In 2003, he had been in orbit testing an experimental space shuttle when an extraterrestrial object (later classified as EI-01) suddenly appeared in his flight path, smashing his shuttle out of the way. This left the shuttle disabled and Guy himself in a near-death state.
The alien mechanical lion, Galeon, would then appear and deal a crushing blow to EI-01, sending it out of orbit to land on Earth. Thereafter, Galeon would find the critically wounded Guy and return him to the Space Development Corporation. Adapting Galeon`s technologies, his father Leo Shishioh would create a cyborg body for his son (with a G-Stone-powered mechanical heart), saving his life and giving him superhuman strength.</description>
<picture>176758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20001" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-25">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Shishiou Reo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shishiou Reo is the former Chief Scientist of the Gutsy Geoid Guard, responsible for all of its G-Stone technologies. Also Guy`s father, he appeared on the surface to be somewhat flippant about his son`s involvement in GGG (though as a father, the only reason he let Guy fight was his request to do so).
Although he was 70 years old, he did not act it, and regularly flew around the Main Order Room in "Jet-Roller" roller skates (which also provided him with the "Leo Lariat" attack, in which he sped toward a target—that is, his older brother Liger—and smashed his elbow into him). He was not beyond going into the field, either, and in Episode 15 piloted LinerGao through a manual Final Fusion sequence (and continued to ride it through GaoGaiGar`s subsequent fight with EI-15).
Leo met his final fate piloting the Assault Reconnaissance Cutter Murakumo, in Jupiter orbit during GGG`s final battle with the 31 Machine Primevals; Murakumo was destroyed in the process and fell into Jupiter`s gravity well, where the spirit of Leo himself was saved by (and became one with) "THE POWER" generated by the planet. There, he was also reunited with his wife Kizuna (who had herself met a similar fate). As GGG`s final battle continued, Leo and Kizuna managed to release a vast amount of "THE POWER" from Jupiter, allowing the Strongest Brave Robot Corps to absorb it and destroy the remaining Primevals.
During the opening of the seventh episode of GaoGaiGar FINAL, a photograph of Leo and Kizuna is seen, with Jupiter in its background; this alludes to the viewer that Leo remains "alive"—albeit in spirit form—within Jupiter.</description>
<picture>176763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20003" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="3">6.72</rating>
<name>Soldato J</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Only known surviving member of the Soldato Battalion, a series of combat cyborgs developed by the Red Planet`s leader, Abel. They would function as commanders of the J-Ark fleet, and perform Fusion with them to fight the Z-Master. Abel`s extensive preparations would not be enough, however, as the failure to unite Soldato, Alma bioweapon, living computer, and J-Ark battleship into a cohesive team would lead to the failure of the world`s defenses and, eventually, the planet`s mechanization. As a Cyborg, Soldato J has impressive strength and speed. The green scarf attached to his armor can extend and harden into a pair of wings for flight, and the left gauntlet contains a Radiant Ripper, an energy sword. While normally used with both hands, the Radiant Ripper can be used while still attached to the gauntlet, as seen in FINAL.
As one of the two surviving members of the Battalion, Soldato J 002 fought alone (his J-Ark`s main computer—Tomoro 0117—had been lost to Zonder infection and his J-Ark was sent into space to protect its infant Alma onboard), going so far as to confront Arm Primeval, one of the leaders behind the offensive on his world. J would confront Arm alone, and barely lost their confrontation, forced to flee into the wasteland that was now his planet. He was subsequently captured by his own living computer—transformed into the Zonderian Pinchernone—and converted into the Zonderian Pizza, the memory of his proud past sealed away.
As Pizza, he and Pinchernone would accompany the Zonderian "terminal" program Pasder to the "Blue Planet"—Earth—with the order to infect all of humanity with Zonder Metal. Even as a Zonderian, however, Pizza would have brief flashes of the time before he was mechanized. He became a great rival of the GGG Mobile Unit commander Guy Shishioh; through his duels with Guy, his old pride began to recover, along with his a sense of his old purpose. In a burst of defiance, he protected his rival from a direct attack from Pasder, leaving him critically wounded. He would be saved by his Arma, who had landed on Earth and had adopted the identity of Ikumi Kaidou. Kaidou performed Purification on Pizza and Pinchernone, restoring to them their true forms and memories.
Following his restoration, Soldato J would dedicate himself to his original mission once again: to destroy the Z-Master. To this end he would re-unite with his team in his J-Ark (crashed within Mt. Aso in Kyuushuu, Japan) and wait for the arrival of the 31 Machine Primevals. Upon the Primevals` arrival on Earth, he showed just how powerful the original Red Planet fleet could have been had it been properly organized. They began an independent mission to destroy the Primevals—ignoring the battles of the Gutsy Galaxy Guard, going over their heads and even clashing with them head-on. As J and GGG realized they had a common goal, however, they began to grudgingly help each other to defeat the 31 Primevals.
During this time, J would also confront and destroy the other surviving member of the Soldato Battalion: Soldato J #019, who had since pledged his loyalty to the Z-Master and had his J-Jewel replaced with a Zonder Crystal (this story was told in the manga serial "Wings of Light and Darkness").
In the final battle with the Z-Master, J and Kaidou entered Heart Primeval and set "THE POWER" in the J-Ark to overload, creating a cascade reaction that would destroy the Z-Master from within (also critically damaging King J-Der in the process). Judging this to be a fair trade, J and his team were fully willing to sacrifice themselves in order to end the Zonder threat once and for all. It was revealed that the J-Ark survived the final fight, falling into a wormhole generated by "THE POWER" and emerging at a point 90 million light-years outside of the universe. There, the J-Ark began its slow restoration process. From their unique perspective, Tomoro 0117 determined that the universe was contracting in size; tracking down the source of the contraction, the J-Ark reappeared within Earth`s solar system in orbit of Jupiter, where they found an exhausted Mamoru Amami and a mysterious device called the Pas-Q Machine. As Mamoru asked Kaidou to take this device to Earth, Pia Decem of the 11 Planetary Masters of Sol attacked; Kaidou returned to Earth with the Machine, but J retreated to the Tri-Star System with Mamoru.
Soldato-J and his J-Ark covered Mamoru`s retreat to the G-Crystal but were themselves captured by the other Masters of Sol and imprisoned on the repli-Earth created by the Pas-Q Machine (at the island of Mont Saint Michel). They would thereafter be freed by Renais-Kerdif Shishioh and Mikoto Utsugi, only to face Palus Abel—the 11 Masters` leader whose program was based on Abel herself. She would soon after reveal that she had captured Ikumi Kaidou and was using him as the living computer core of Pia Decem Pit; unable to attack Pia Decem directly because of this, King J-Der was soon forced into a fight with a mind-controlled Guy Shishioh. The resulting clash between J-Quath and Goldion Hammer left both weapons destroyed. Palus Abel routed remote commands through Kaidou to shut down the J-Ark and Soldato J`s own J-Jewel; Pia Decem and Pillnus captured him and Renais Kerdif-Shishioh soon after, though they would escape through sheer accident—bringing Renais` G-Stone into proximity with Soldato-J`s J-Jewel restored them both, activating their Hyper Modes. It is at this point that J`s helmet is partially broken, allowing the only view of his eyes in the series. With the subsequently rectivated J-Ark, they proceeded to confront Palus Abel aboard the Pia Decem Pit.
Despite many fans using the translation "Soldat", the correct (and official) translation is Soldato. Soldato is an Italian word(like Arma and Pizza) and means "Soldier". Soldat, though, does mean "Soldier" in several languages as well, including Swedish
Soldato J appears to be a homage to Cyborg 002 of Cyborg 009, who together share a similar design, common number, personality, and fondness for flying. Sunrise and Toei Animation collaborated on a Cyborg 009 adaption in the late 1970`s, the era of which GaoGaiGar attempts to thematically honor.</description>
<picture>176791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77034" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-25">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Hyuuma Geki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77035" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-25">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Swan White</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4717" picture="186206.jpg">Narahashi Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77036" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-25">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Ushiyama Kazuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="274" picture="17101.jpg">Ishikawa Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77037" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-25">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Entouji Kousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4682" picture="27282.jpg">Kashiwakura Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77038" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-25">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Shishiou Raiga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77039" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-25">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Stallion White</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77043" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Kaidou Ikumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2221" picture="83141.jpg">Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77044" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Komori Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4717" picture="186206.jpg">Narahashi Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77045" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Sunou Takayasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176781.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4682" picture="27282.jpg">Kashiwakura Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77046" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Ushiyama Sueo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="274" picture="17101.jpg">Ishikawa Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77047" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Hatsuno Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4717" picture="186206.jpg">Narahashi Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77048" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Isogai Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4960" picture="153532.jpg">Yoshida Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77049" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Mesomeso</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176788.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77050" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Cain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176790.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4377" picture="26672.jpg">Chiba Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77051" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Polonaise</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2405" picture="23217.jpg">Shioya Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77052" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Primarda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2221" picture="83141.jpg">Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77053" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Pinchernone</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4682" picture="27282.jpg">Kashiwakura Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77054" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Pizza</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77055" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Pasder</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77056" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Pagliaccio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4960" picture="153532.jpg">Yoshida Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77057" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>GaoGaiGar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176798.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77058" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Gaigar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176799.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77059" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Galeon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176800.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77060" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Liner Gao</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176801.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77061" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Drill Gao</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176802.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77062" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Stealth Gao</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176804.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77063" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Stealth Gao II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>176803.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77064" type="appears in" update="2018-10-27">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Star GaoGaiGar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176805.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77065" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Hyouryuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4927" picture="51974.jpg">Yamada Shin`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77066" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Enryuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4927" picture="51974.jpg">Yamada Shin`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77067" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Chouryuujin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4927" picture="51974.jpg">Yamada Shin`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77068" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Fuuryuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4927" picture="51974.jpg">Yamada Shin`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77069" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Rairyuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4927" picture="51974.jpg">Yamada Shin`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77070" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Gekiryuujin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176811.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4927" picture="51974.jpg">Yamada Shin`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77071" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Gouryuujin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4927" picture="51974.jpg">Yamada Shin`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77072" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Genryuujin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4927" picture="51974.jpg">Yamada Shin`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77073" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Volfogg</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77074" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Gun Dober</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176815.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77075" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Gun Glue</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176816.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77076" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Big Volfogg</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77077" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Goldymarg</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176818.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77078" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Mic Sounders XIII</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77079" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Boom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176820.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77080" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>DP-L3</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176821.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77081" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>DP-C1</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176822.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77082" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>DP-R2</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176823.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77083" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>King J-Der</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176824.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77084" type="appears in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>J-Der</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>176825.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="104550" type="appears in" update="2019-07-20">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>J-Bird</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>67748.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="104611" type="appears in" update="2019-07-22">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>J-Carrier</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>67754.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="104616" type="appears in" update="2019-07-23">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>J-Ark</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>67755.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="9863" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風と雷(いかずち)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wind and Lightning</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze to Ikazuchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9864" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大東京消滅!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Great Tokyo Disappearance/Destruction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Tokyo Shoumetsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9865" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖なる左腕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Holy Left Arm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seinaru Hidari Ude</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9866" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1998-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inochi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9867" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">太陽が消える日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day the Sun Disappeared</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiyou ga Kieru Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9868" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その名は撃龍神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Name is GekiRyuuJin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Na wa Gekiryuujin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9869" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">太古からの帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">(Return from Ancient Times)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiko kara no Kikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9870" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆襲機界31原種</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CounterAttack! Machine World 31 Primevals</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakushuu! Kikai 31 Genshu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9871" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗黒の大決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Battle of Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ankoku no Daikessen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9872" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">緑の髪の少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boy with Green Hair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midori no Kami no Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9873" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">汚されし空へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Corrupted Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kegasareshi Sora e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9874" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逃亡者ゾンダー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fugitive Zonder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toubousha Zonder</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9875" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">滅びの声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Voice of Destruction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Horobi no Koe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9876" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゾンダー先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zonder Teacher</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zonder Sensei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9877" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遥かなる凱歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Far Away Victory Song</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Harukanaru Gaika</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9878" update="2005-02-17">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1998-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつか星の海で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Someday, in the Sea of Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuka Hoshi no Umi de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9879" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">火の鳥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Firebird</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hi no Tori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9880" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青と赤</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue and Red</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ao to Aka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9881" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! 機界四天王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crash! The Big Four of Destruction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Kikai Shitennou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9882" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷点下への出航(たびだち)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departure to the Freezing Point</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyoutenka e no Tabidachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9883" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星の子供たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Children of the Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi no Kodomo-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9884" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">GGG, 木星へ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">GGG, Towards Jupiter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">GGG, Mokusei e!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9885" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者復活!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heros` Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha Fukkatsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9886" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終焉序曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prelude to the Coming of Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuen Jokyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9887" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒の300を追え!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drive away the Black 300</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro no 300 o Oe!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9888" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束は光の彼方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Promise Made Beyond the Light</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku wa Hikari no Kanata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9889" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亡ぶべき右腕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Right Arm Must Be Destroyed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Horobubeki Migi Ude</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9890" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1998-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">機界昇華終結</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Machine World Digestion Termination</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikai Shouka Shuuketsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9891" update="2008-07-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者王誕生!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">King of Braves is Born!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha Ou Tanjou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9892" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マイク13</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mic 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mic 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9893" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カインの遺産</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legacy of Cain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cain no Isan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9894" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金色の破壊神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Golden God of Destruction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konjiki no Hakaishin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9895" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">機界最強7原種</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Magnificent 7 Primevals</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikai Saikyou 7 Ganshu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9896" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">素粒子Z0(ゼットゼロ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Elementary Particle Z0</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soryuushi Z0</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9897" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はずされた鍵(プロテクト)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protection Disabled!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hazusareta Protect</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9898" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">正午の悪魔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Demon of Midday</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougo no Akuma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9899" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 暁に死す!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Braves, Death at Dawn!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Akatsuki ni Shisu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9900" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻竜神・強龍神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">GenRyuuJin, GoRyuuJin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genryuujin, Gouryuujin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9901" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">次元を越えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cross the Dimentions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigen o Koete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9902" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧が呼ぶ渓谷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Misty Valley</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiri ga Yobu Keikoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9903" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狙われたGGG(スリージー)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">GGG in the Cross-hair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nerawareta GGG</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9904" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばGGG(スリージー)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adieu GGG</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba GGG</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9905" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9906" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇気ある者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That with Courage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuki Aru Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9907" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イゾルデの門</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gate of IZORUDE</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isolde no Mon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9908" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光届かぬ世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A World Devoid of Light</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari Todokanu Sekai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9909" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その名は超竜神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Name is ChoRyuuJin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Na wa Chouryuujin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9910" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カイン来迎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Coming of Cain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cain Raigou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9911" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空間を制する者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conqueror of Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuukan o Seisuru Mono</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
