<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9588" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-12-06</startdate>
<enddate>2014-12-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">The Last: Naruto the Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">THE LAST NARUTO THE MOVIE</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Last: Naruto the Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">The Last : Naruto le film</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Наруто: Последний фильм</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10961" type="Sequel">Boruto: Naruto the Movie</anime>
<anime id="12661" type="Sequel">Boruto: Naruto Next Generations</anime>
<anime id="4880" type="Prequel">Naruto Shippuuden</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="502713">This honestly could have been a 9/10 for me, but the story is just to conveniently made to bring those two together, there are also plenty if gimmicks that serve no other purpose either (like why Tonari wanted to marry her and why she willingly when along with him).

He didn`t realize his feelings and fall in love with her because of what happened, it was the reverse, things happened to make him realize and for some reason fall in love.

In the main series he never paid attention to Hinata, even her confessing to him and almost dying for him 200 episodes ago was basically meaningless and ignored, but suddenly in this movie it`s resolved.
And the way Naruto`s love for Sakura is explained away as just him not wanting to lose out to Sasuke is also bullsh*t, like anyone believes that.

Anyway, the romantic relationships in a fighting anime are never taken seriously or go anywhere (like in Bleach) so i guess i should be grateful they at least threw this together.
6/10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="430272">If you have been a fan of the series and have watched the love bud then this is a culmination of your efforts of waoting!! So good!! And the feels!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.naruto-movie.com/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="4455" type="Character Design">Suzuki Hirofumi</name>
<name id="3051" type="Character Design">Nishio Tetsuya</name>
<name id="12448" type="Music">Yaiba</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
<name id="2977" type="Original Work">Kishimoto Masashi</name>
<name id="5348" type="Direction">Kobayashi Tsuneo</name>
<name id="724" type="Animation Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="4455" type="Chief Animation Direction">Suzuki Hirofumi</name>
<name id="3051" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishio Tetsuya</name>
<name id="2977" type="Story Composition">Kishimoto Masashi</name>
<name id="2977" type="Character Design">Kishimoto Masashi</name>
</creators>
<description>The moon is beginning to fall, and at the rate it`s going, it is doomed to fall on the Earth. The countdown for the survival of the planet begins. Among the havoc, Hinata`s younger sister http://anidb.net/ch75185 [Hanabi] is captured by the mysterious enemy, http://anidb.net/ch70984 [Ootsutsuki Toneri], who mistakes her for the elder sister. http://anidb.net/ch226 [Naruto] must overcome great danger on a mission to save Hanabi and the world along with http://anidb.net/ch7256 [Hinata], http://anidb.net/ch8608 [Sai], http://anidb.net/ch8615 [Shikamaru], and http://anidb.net/ch7698 [Sakura]. Finally realizing what and who he must protect, Naruto embarks on his final story.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1124">5.92</permanent>
<temporary count="1134">7.04</temporary>
<review count="1">4.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>209462.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16184</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16870</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.naruto-movie.com/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Last:_Naruto_the_Movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>THE_LAST_-NARUTO_THE_MOVIE-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1106</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349882</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17756</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-last-naruto-the-movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3145" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-14">
<name>impact event</name>
<description>An impact event is a collision between celestial objects causing measurable effects. Impact events have physical consequences and have been found to regularly occur in planetary systems, though the most frequent involve asteroids, comets or meteoroids and have minimal impact. When large objects impact terrestrial planets like the Earth, there can be significant physical and biospheric consequences, though atmospheres mitigate many surface impacts through atmospheric entry. Impact structures are dominant landforms on many celestial solid objects and present the strongest empirical evidence for their frequency and scale. In fiction, an impact event is a common way to end the world as we know it, either through the impact itself or through its aftermath, and it may happen either naturally or through human hands; this may include man-made objects, such as space debris and fictional space colonies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="226" type="main character in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="1440">6.74</rating>
<name>Uzumaki Naruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60771.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="240" type="appears in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="740">4.36</rating>
<name>Uzumaki Naruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7248" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="1671">8.57</rating>
<name>Hatake Kakashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatake Kakashi is the leader and teacher of Team 7, consisting of http://anidb.net/ch7196 [Uchiha Sasuke], http://anidb.net/ch7194 [Haruno Sakura], and http://anidb.net/ch240 [Uzumaki Naruto]. He is initially portrayed as a detached and apathetic figure, but as the series progresses, his loyalty to his friends and students becomes increasingly apparent. Kakashi`s past has been extensively explored in the series, resulting in a gaiden being devoted to his past experiences. Kakashi has appeared in several pieces of Naruto media, including three of the four featured films in the series, all of the original video animations, and several video games.</description>
<picture>54614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7256" type="main character in" update="2011-05-26">
<rating votes="471">8.04</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hyuuga Hinata is a member of Team 8 who suffers from a lack of self-confidence throughout the series. She is very shy and always reluctant to speak her mind or to do something that might antagonize another character, causing her difficulties whenever she is on a mission. This results in her effective expulsion from her clan even though she is the eldest daughter of the Hyuga clan`s leader and the heiress to the clan. Hinata`s inability to stand up for herself caused her father to disown her at a young age, leaving her in the care of her teacher, Kurenai Yuhi. Masashi Kishimoto had originally intended Hinata to be a regular member of the Hyuga clan but instead made her a ninja. Soon after her introduction, Hinata begins training to become stronger, both to overcome her own weaknesses and to prove her worth to her father. Her efforts begin to prove successful towards the end of Part I, as her father takes a greater interest in her training.
Source: wikipedia.org</description>
<picture>29538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7260" type="appears in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="325">7.91</rating>
<name>Gaara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7698" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="784">2.77</rating>
<name>Haruno Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruno Sakura is the sole female member of Team 7. Kishimoto created her as the heroine of the series, although he has admitted that he has little perception of what an ideal heroine should be. As a child, Sakura was taunted by other children because of her large forehead, a feature Kishimoto has tried to emphasize in Sakura`s appearances. She was comforted by Ino Yamanaka. As the two continued to grow, however, they became increasingly distant due to their shared affection for Sasuke Uchiha. During most of Part I, Sakura is infatuated with Sasuke, and spurns the advances of Naruto Uzumaki. After Sasuke leaves the village, she resolves to become stronger by training with Tsunade. In Part II, she displays highly developed skills from her training, and a more open disposition towards Naruto.</description>
<picture>2928.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="234" picture="244740.jpg">Nakamura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7719" type="appears in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="504">3.28</rating>
<name>Uchiha Sasuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7723" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="176">7.54</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hyuuga Hinata is a member of Team 8 who suffers from a lack of self-confidence throughout the series. She is very shy and always reluctant to speak her mind or to do something that might antagonize another character, causing her difficulties whenever she is on a mission. This results in her effective expulsion from her clan even though she is the eldest daughter of the Hyuga clan`s leader and the heiress to the clan. Hinata`s inability to stand up for herself caused her father to disown her at a young age, leaving her in the care of her teacher, Kurenai Yuhi. Masashi Kishimoto had originally intended Hinata to be a regular member of the Hyuga clan but instead made her a ninja. Soon after her introduction, Hinata begins training to become stronger, both to overcome her own weaknesses and to prove her worth to her father. Her efforts begin to prove successful towards the end of Part I, as her father takes a greater interest in her training.
[i]
Source: wikipedia.org[/i]</description>
<picture>54662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8606" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="419">6.45</rating>
<name>Tsunade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsunade, as well as her former teammates http://anidb.net/ch7213 [Jiraiya] and http://anidb.net/ch8603 [Orochimaru], is a former student of the http://anidb.net/ch8865 [Third Hokage]. She is also the granddaughter of the http://anidb.net/ch8859 [First Hokage], and so many characters in the series refer to her with the Japanese honorific "hime" (meaning "princess"). Despite her connections to past Hokage, Tsunade hates the position when she is first introduced. After her brother and boyfriend died in pursuit of their dreams to become Hokage, she lost faith in the title and the concept of dreams. She regains her faith in both after meeting http://anidb.net/ch240 [Naruto Uzumaki], who consistently overcomes any obstacle in his own dreams of being Hokage. As a result, Tsunade accepts the position of Fifth Hokage to protect http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure] on behalf of everyone she has loved. Despite the importance of her position, Tsunade tends to avoid her duties, instead leaving them for her assistants. She will fulfil her role to address matters important to the village, and throughout Part II leads Konoha in combating http://anidb.net/ch8599 [Akatsuki]. When Konoha is invaded by http://anidb.net/ch11993 [Pain], she uses up all her energy summoning http://anidb.net/ch17274 [Katsuyu], her slug summon, to protect the villagers, and stays in a coma for a long time causing her to be dismissed as Hokage temporarily. Tsunade possesses a number of traits that set her apart from other characters in the series, such as being a compulsive gambler with terrible luck. On the rare occasions that she hits a winning streak she perceives it as a bad omen, and makes it a point to fortify her defences when it occurs. Additionally, although she is in her fifties, she constantly assumes the appearance of a twenty-year-old woman, retaining only her characteristically large breasts. Despite her odd personality Tsunade is a talented ninja; she has superhuman strength that allows her to reduce buildings to rubble and can heal injuries that most others would consider incurable. Her healing abilities are such that she has devised a method of regeneration for herself, making her all but invincible in battle. At the conclusion of Part I, Tsunade takes http://anidb.net/ch7194 [Haruno Sakura] as an apprentice, teaching her how to use both of her trademark abilities.</description>
<picture>27913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8608" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-28">
<rating votes="127">4.91</rating>
<name>Sai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sai is introduced during Part II of the series as http://anidb.net/ch7719 [Uchiha Sasuke]`s replacement in Team 7. Having been a member of The Foundation since he was a child, Sai has been trained to not possess or desire any type of emotion or camaraderie. After spending time with http://anidb.net/ch226 [Uzumaki Naruto], however, he begins to crave bonds with other people, which has since become his primary role in the series. Sai`s attempts to form bonds involve giving pet names to others; however, he often says what he actually thinks of a person, resulting with him choosing names such as "fatso" and "ugly". He eventually learns from his mistakes and attempts the opposite approach, for instance, calling http://anidb.net/ch8616 [Yamanaka Ino] "pretty lady". When not making an attempt to bond with others, Sai spends his time painting and drawing, and has produced thousands of works. His artistic talents extend to his choice of attacks in battles: he can infuse chakra with his inking brush to make his drawings come to life.</description>
<picture>30810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8610" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="126">6.61</rating>
<name>Rock Lee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4757" picture="46951.jpg">Masukawa Youichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8613" type="appears in" update="2010-04-28">
<rating votes="50">5.92</rating>
<name>Shizune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizune is a http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure] ninja introduced in the series as http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Tsunade]`s assistant. She left Konohagakure with Tsunade after the death of her uncle, and over the years, Tsunade taught her medical techniques. Despite her medicinal affinity, many of the attacks she uses in the series are poison-based, including using concealed poisoned needles or emitting toxic gas from her mouth. Shizune is one of the few characters that Tsunade trusts with absolute certainty, as she identifies details that Tsunade tends to overlook. In Part II of the series, Shizune`s concern for details causes her to question Tsunade`s judgment, creating interference with Tsunade`s plans and temporarily straining the relationship between the two.</description>
<picture>28660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4725" picture="27575.jpg">Nemoto Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8614" type="appears in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="72">5.01</rating>
<name>Yuuhi Kurenai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurenai Yuhi is the leader of Team 8.</description>
<picture>27914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4754" picture="180151.jpg">Ochiai Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8615" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="331">8.55</rating>
<name>Nara Shikamaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nara Shikamaru was in the same class as http://anidb.net/ch226 [Naruto] at the Ninja academy and is now part of a team with http://anidb.net/ch8616 [Ino] and http://anidb.net/ch8617 [Chouji]. He is very laid back to the point of being lazy; he often sees missions as troublesome. He is quite close to his team leader, http://anidb.net/ch7742 [Asuma], and the pair regularly plays shougi together. Shikamaru specialises in jutsu which manipulate shadows, but his true strength lies in his ability to think up the best strategies for defeating an enemy.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>30812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8616" type="appears in" update="2011-01-06">
<rating votes="65">5.01</rating>
<name>Yamanaka Ino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamanaka Ino is the only female member of Team 10. She has known Haruno Sakura since they were children, befriending and helping her to develop her own identity. When they discovered that they both liked Uchiha Sasuke, Sakura ended their friendship so they could properly compete for his affection. The two eventually make amends and rekindle their friendship, but still maintain a competitive attitude towards each other. In the anime, when Sakura begins to excel in healing techniques, Ino becomes her surrogate apprentice, hoping to be more useful to her friends and teammates as an able medical ninja. In terms of combat abilities, Ino specializes in mind-altering techniques. To use these techniques, Ino transfers her consciousness to her target`s mind, gaining control over their body which she can then use to attack others.</description>
<picture>27921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8617" type="appears in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="72">3.06</rating>
<name>Akimichi Chouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akimichi Chouji is a rather large ninja who makes up one third of Team Asuma alongside http://anidb.net/ch8615 [Shikamaru] and http://anidb.net/ch8616 [Ino]. He has a very large appetite and regularly clears out http://anidb.net/ch7742 [Asuma]`s wallet when they go for Korean barbeque. Though he can always be seen eating something, he uses his size to his advantage in battle and gets exceptionally angry when anyone calls him fat. Chouji is able to utilise the ninja techniques of his family that allow him to increase the size of any part of his body.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>27977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8622" type="appears in" update="2015-01-26">
<rating votes="112">6.04</rating>
<name>Might Guy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Might Guy is the leader of Team Guy, consisting of http://anidb.net/ch32424 [Rock Lee], http://anidb.net/ch32420 [Hyuuga Neiji] and http://anidb.net/ch32425 [Tenten].
Guy, and by extension Lee, lives his life by his own "My Rules" philosophy, which involves setting tougher self-imposed penalties for failure so something good comes of it. For example, he vowed to walk 500 laps around Konoha on his hands if he lost a contest with Kakashi, and proceeded to do so upon losing, even though people eventually stopped paying attention. He also doesn`t hesitate to do things he doesn`t enjoy or that others might find embarrassing if it means his own self-improvement, as seen with his belief that one cannot dislike food regardless of its ingredients or taste. In addition, Guy values his youth to a great degree and dislikes the idea that he may not be as young as he once was. To help remedy this problem he spends large amounts of time with his younger teammates, hoping to acquire some of their youthful properties. Likewise, he often refers to himself as "Konoha`s Prideful Green Beast".
Guy is the self-proclaimed rival of http://anidb.net/ch7248 [Kakashi Hatake]. Kakashi, however, is indifferent to their rivalry, which annoys Guy to no end. Kakashi also seems to have a habit of unintentionally ignoring Guy when Guy is lecturing him, which usually results in Guy asking himself why Kakashi "has to act so cool". Guy randomly challenges Kakashi to contests of skill, and has acquired a record of 50 wins and 49 losses in doing so.</description>
<picture>54610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10292" type="appears in" update="2009-07-09">
<rating votes="12">5.57</rating>
<name>Teuchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6084" picture="186264.jpg">Asakura Eisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10329" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="23">4.33</rating>
<name>Hagane Kotetsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hagane Kotetsu is a Chuunin from http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure]. He spends most of the time with his partner, http://anidb.net/ch17145 [Kamizuki Izumo]. Kotetsu wears a bandage across his face over his nose. At one point, http://anidb.net/ch7742 [Asuma], Izumo and http://anidb.net/ch8615 [Shikamaru] asked him about this, and pointed out that he hadn`t worn it when he was a child. Later, he agreed to take the bandage off, but then Shikamaru said that knowing what was under it would only be troublesome, much to Kotetsu`s chagrin, so the reason for the bandage over his nose remains unknown.</description>
<picture>30876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6345" picture="30893.jpg">Kouno Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10930" type="appears in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="33">4.42</rating>
<name>Umino Iruka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60772.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10931" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="63">4.23</rating>
<name>Sarutobi Konohamaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sarutobi Konohamaru, named after Konohagakure, is the grandson of the Third Hokage. He strives to replace his grandfather as Hokage so the villagers of Konohagakure will recognize him by name, not as the Hokage`s grandson. He looks to Uzumaki Naruto as a mentor in this quest, emulating his work ethic, determination, and signature jutsu such as the Rasengan and a variety of other techniques. Konohamaru insists, however, that he will only become Hokage after Naruto has been Hokage first.</description>
<picture>36325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11993" type="appears in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="192">8.54</rating>
<name>Pain (Tendou)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pain (Deva Path) is the first of the Six Paths of Pain to be shown, was the body of http://anidb.net/ch20618 [Yahiko]. It was the most often seen and used of the six paths, and acted as Nagato`s representative during Akatsuki meetings. Its main abilities revolved around manipulating gravity, allowing it to repel or attract objects. The Deva Path was permanently incapacitated after its chakra receivers were removed from its body following its defeat by Naruto Uzumaki`s Rasengan. Konan took this body, along with Nagato`s body, after he died, and returned them to Amegakure.
As the Deva Path was the body of Yahiko, it had retained all of his physical features from when he was alive, most notably his medium length spiky orange hair. As the Deva Path, the body possessed Nagato`s Rinnegan, bore six piercings, a metal bar through each ear, three studs through the side of its upper nose, and one spike stud on each end of the bottom lip. It also had three piercings on each wrist, at least one on its upper wrist and some just under his neck. He also wore a beaded necklace, which is quite similar to the one worn by the Sage of the Six Paths. Underneath his Akatsuki robes, the Deva Path bears a faint scar at his stomach, most likely when Yahiko jumped onto the kunai to commit suicide under Hanzou`s order.
The Deva Path was the only path to be seen interacting with other Akatsuki members besides Konan. When all six paths were in active use, Nagato tended to speak only through the Deva Path, and showed the tendency to sacrifice other paths to keep it safe, suggesting that Nagato had some partiality to the path or that it was merely the most valuable.
The Deva Path was regarded as Pain`s most powerful and cherished of the six Paths. Its main abilities revolved around gravity manipulation, allowing it to repel or attract objects or people. However, it could not perform these techniques in rapid succession, leaving it vulnerable for a short period of time after each use. This period of time between usages varied from five seconds to several minutes, depending upon the force of the repulsion or attraction that the Deva Path had used. When performing a large-scale attack, Nagato had to first sever his connections with the other paths and then employ his chakra only to the Deva Path for the attack. However this is considerably risky as the other Pains were healing considerably sluggishly when the Naraka Path administered his jutsu. The Deva Path`s Chibaku Tensei allowed it to release a black orb of energy that could attract all surrounding matter to form a huge makeshift terrestrial body. The Deva Path`s most infamous and one of his greatest feats was singlehandly wiping out Konohagakure with one powerful Shinra Tensei.
In addition to gravity manipulation, Nagato was able to use a number of other miscellaneous jutsu through the Deva Path, something none of the other bodies had been shown doing. He was able to use the Shapeshifting Technique through the Deva path to make body doubles of others with human sacrifices. Other techniques used included astral projection, barriers to protect hideouts, and control rain, a possible throwback to Yahiko (who wanted to be able to stop the rain in Amegakure), which even allowed him to sense the chakra of everyone in Amegakure, making stealthy entrances by enemies impossible. In addition, like most of the other paths, it possessed considerable strength and speed, as seen with its fight with Jiraiya and Kakashi.
As Pain`s main body, the Deva Path was the primary body used for performing the Sealing Technique: Illusionary Dragon Nine Consuming Seals, which Akatsuki used to seal the tailed beasts. The members would convene to forcibly extract the beast from its host`s body over a three day period, depending on the number of people assisting with the sealing, and would then store it in a giant statue. He was not the only one who could use this technique, however. Madara Uchiha and the remaining Akatsuki members have been shown to initiate the extraction without using the Deva Path while it was occupied with invading Konoha.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>54552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12237" type="appears in" update="2014-09-01">
<rating votes="46">8.94</rating>
<name>Kurama</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The nine-tailed demon fox (九尾の妖狐, Kyuubi no Youko) is the most powerful of the tailed beasts. It is regarded as an age-old natural disaster, as a single swipe of one of its tails can raise tsunamis and flatten mountains. Twelve years before the start of the series, the fox attacked http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure]. Its attack was stopped by the http://anidb.net/ch8866 [Fourth Hokage], who gave his life to seal the fox into his son, http://anidb.net/ch240 [Uzumaki Naruto]. Throughout the series, Naruto tries to gain dominance over the fox, as harnessing its great strength allows him to perform jutsu that would normally be impossible for a ninja of his age. At the same time the fox tries to gain control over Naruto, provoking his rage and thus allowing its violent personality to influence and consume him. As Naruto draws upon more of the fox`s power the seal keeping it trapped within him weakens, and in the event the seal is broken the fox will be released.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>37113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13998" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="42">7.50</rating>
<name>Killer Bee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Killer Bee is a ninja from the village of Kumogakure. He is introduced during Part II as one of the two hosts that have yet to be captured by the criminal organization Akatsuki, the other being series protagonist http://anidb.net/ch226 [Uzumaki Naruto]. The host of the ushi-oni-like http://anidb.net/ch14124 [eight-tailed beast], Killer Bee has complete control over the beast sealed within him. In battle he uses its great strength to increase the lethality of his professional wrestling-styled attacks. He is also a talented swordsman capable of using up to seven swords at once. Killer Bee is the brother of http://anidb.net/ch16171 [Aa], the current Raikage of http://anidb.net/ch12205 [Kumogakure], and as such is expected to be the guardian of the village. When Akatsuki attacks him, he pretends to be captured to escape this job and pursue a career as an enka music singer.</description>
<picture>54554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16171" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="22">5.64</rating>
<name>Aa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aa is the Fourth Raikage and the leader of http://anidb.net/ch12205 [Kumogakure]. He is also the older brother of http://anidb.net/ch13998 [Killer Bee], the jinchuuriki of the Eight-Tailed Giant Ox. As it is hinted that Killer Bee is a member of the Yotsuki clan, A is likely a member, as well. Knowing http://anidb.net/ch7721 [Nii Yugito]`s and Killer Bee`s immense powers if they were to ever transform into their full demon forms, he forbade at least Killer Bee from doing so.</description>
<picture>54553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11025" picture="43745.jpg">Tezuka Hideaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17145" type="appears in" update="2010-04-29">
<rating votes="13">3.99</rating>
<name>Kamizuki Izumo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamizuki Izumo is a Chuunin from http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure]. He spends most of the time with his partner, http://anidb.net/ch10329 [Hagane Kotetsu]. Izumo is almost always seen alongside Kotetsu, and is characterized as being the more responsible and conscientious of the two. In Shippuuden Episode 81, he angrily burst into the Jounin lounge to drag his partner back to work. Similarly, in another omake, he admonished Kotetsu`s lack of pride in his work when the latter complained that they were simply the http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Fifth Hokage]`s errand-boys or "gophers", before adding sagely that guarding the Leaf and the villagers was "the best mission you can get" as a shinobi.</description>
<picture>47093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1441" picture="18827.jpg">Tsuboi Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17274" type="appears in" update="2010-04-30">
<rating votes="10">5.19</rating>
<name>Katsuyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsuyu is the slug queen summoned by http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Tsunade]. The name Katsuyu apparently comes from Slug (蛞蝓) in on`yomi. Compared to http://anidb.net/ch12000 [Gamabunta] and Manda, the summons of http://anidb.net/ch7213 [Jiraiya] and http://anidb.net/ch8603 [Orochimaru] respectively, Katsuyu is quiet and more subservient to her master. She addresses Tsunade with the highly respectful honorific "-sama", and, in the English versions, calls her Mistress or Milady. Katsuyu tends to also use honorifics like "-kun" and "-san" on other villagers. http://anidb.net/ch7698 [Sakura] and http://anidb.net/ch8613 [Shizune] show her considerable respect, addressing her as "Katsuyu-sama". In the English dub, she is referred to as "Lady Katsuyu".</description>
<picture>47181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28513" type="appears in" update="2011-02-12">
<rating votes="10">3.39</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Hiashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hyuuga Hiashi is the head of the Hyuuga clan. He is also the father of Hyuuga Hinata and Hyuuga Hanabi, as well as the older twin brother of the late Hyuuga Hizashi, and the paternal uncle of Hyuuga Neji.</description>
<picture>65568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="562" picture="17888.jpg">Tsuda Eizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28785" type="appears in" update="2014-11-27">
<rating votes="27">7.35</rating>
<name>Terumi Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Terumi Mei is the Fifth Mizukage of Kirigakure. She became Mizukage in recent years, after the dreadful reign of Yagura ended.</description>
<picture>54548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2879" picture="170992.jpg">Hino Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29714" type="appears in" update="2016-03-18">
<rating votes="5">7.86</rating>
<name>Oonoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oonoki is the Third Tsuchikage of Iwagakure. He is called Oonoki of Both Scales.</description>
<picture>72400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32421" type="appears in" update="2011-05-18">
<rating votes="24">4.77</rating>
<name>Inuzuka Kiba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inuzuka Kiba is one of the main supporting characters of the series. He is a chuunin-level shinobi of Konohagakure`s Inuzuka clan. He and his partner, Akamaru are both members of Team Kurenai.</description>
<picture>71784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70984" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-04">
<rating votes="4">3.09</rating>
<name>Ootsutsuki Toneri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75185" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-15">
<rating votes="4">3.61</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Hanabi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2344" picture="37361.jpg">Asai Kiyomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76638" type="appears in" update="2015-08-04">
<rating votes="45">3.99</rating>
<name>Uzumaki Boruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77567" type="appears in" update="2015-11-13">
<rating votes="23">7.97</rating>
<name>Uzumaki Himawari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>179344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38354" picture="150733.jpg">Kuwahara Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78297" type="appears in" update="2015-11-14">
<rating votes="1">2.88</rating>
<name>Gekkou Hayate</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>179393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78312" type="appears in" update="2015-11-14">
<rating votes="1">4.55</rating>
<name>Kugutsu Jijogao</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>179410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78313" type="appears in" update="2015-11-14">
<name>Tenmonkata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>179411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32197" picture="4765.png">Shida Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78314" type="appears in" update="2015-11-14">
<name>Kunoichi Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>179412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43212" picture="173435.jpg">Takada Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78315" type="appears in" update="2015-11-14">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kunoichi Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>179413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43211" picture="173434.jpg">Hashizume Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88898" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-18">
<rating votes="6">4.22</rating>
<name>Haruno Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64964.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="234" picture="244740.jpg">Nakamura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="161497" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2014-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>"Two years have passed since the fated battle between Naruto and Sasuke in the Village Hidden in the Leaves. A comfortable peace has fallen over the village and the winter festival approaches with a bit more excitement than usual. Seasons of war have transformed Naruto and his friends into elite young warriors, but now they grow into the adults they were meant to be, forming bonds beyond friendship. Naruto and Hinata approach this next stage with trepidation and find their progress stalled when a mysterious and dangerous man appears with a disturbing message: the end of the world is upon them. Once again Naruto and his friends are sent to investigate and stop the impossible, a falling moon! What is the tragic fate that connects this disaster with Hinata`s Hyuga Clan? And to what lengths will Naruto go to speak the words that will change his life? The Last is the final story of Naruto as you knew him, the hero who was once an outcast, and the first chapter of the bond that will define his future."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791429</identifier>
<identifier>the-last-naruto-the-movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169199" update="2015-06-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169200" update="2015-06-24">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169203" update="2015-06-24">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170772" update="2015-10-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2014-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170773" update="2015-10-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
