<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="959" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-08-26</startdate>
<enddate>2003-11-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fullmetal Panic? Fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Стальная тревога? Фумоффу</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Пълна метална паника? Фумоффу</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Full Metal Panic Fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Стальна тривога: Фумоффу</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">FMP?</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">FMP? F</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">FMPF</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">FMP:F</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">fmp fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">フルメタル・パニック? ふもっふ</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">全金属狂潮2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Full Metal Panic? Fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Full Metal Panic? Fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Full Metal Panic? Fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Full Metal Panic? Fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Стальная тревога: Фумоффу</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">풀 메탈 패닉 후못후</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Full Metal Panic? Fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Full Metal Panic? Fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Full Metal Panic? Fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Full Metal Panic? Fumoffu</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">Сталева тривога? Фумоффу</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">全金属狂潮 校园篇</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Fumoffu</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="17" type="Parent Story">Fullmetal Panic!</anime>
<anime id="2710" type="Parent Story">Fullmetal Panic! The Second Raid</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2165" approval="90" total="147">School Rumble</anime>
<anime id="10399" approval="11" total="21">Amagi Brilliant Park</anime>
<anime id="894" approval="3" total="13">R.O.D: The TV</anime>
<anime id="139" approval="1" total="7">Photon</anime>
<anime id="10918" approval="1" total="7">Ore Monogatari!!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="46">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="293766">Fullmetal Panic? Fumoffu was made up entirely of episodes that were originally suppose to serve as filler episodes but were taken out and made into it`s own little side story instead. And boy am very glad they decided not to just get rid of them =). This series was hilarious! No story line, no linear scenarios, just all comedy. If you love a good laugh, then this is perfect for you =).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="281436">I would not recommend this for people who haven`t seen the series. If you wanna watch this make sure you have seen the series first so you know what is going on. This Add-On Extra series is pretty much all about comedy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="163177">Wow! Very funny. You will be very happy when you watch this anime. The characters are super!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="615767">If you were expecting a continuation on the first two seasons like I was, be prepared to be disappointed. This season has so little to do with the main story, you could almost watch it as a standalone. A great anime for the comedy, but doesn`t quite hold a candle to the first two seasons.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="144655">great comedy</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="255852">School Life/Comedy, and sometimes it feels like the reason for the original FMP is just for this series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="421194">Short anime, but highly entertaining</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="391926">it`s sooooooooo funny,must must must see!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="427215">This anime is good, but not great.  It did have perhaps the funniest moment of any show I`ve ever seen- but that doesn`t make up for its other downfalls.  FMP! and TSR are both better, although FMP! is much better than TSR.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="346737">LAWL !!!!! XD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="163364">pure lol</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="642367">Hilarious spin-off to the Full Metal Panic universe! I laughed so much watching this series. One of the funniest anime I have ever seen. If you want a light-hearted diversion from the mecha action from the original storyline, then this is for you. Not saying the mecha action was bad or anything, BTW. All the episodes are hilarious in their own respects. A must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="207428">best comedy anime I`ve ever seen!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="101376">It`s a good comedy of full metal panic you don`t want to miss it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="276891">Best anime comedy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="228752">ROFL while watching guaranteed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="319333">I absolutely loved this, I mean it`s funny as hell, the male leadcharacter is just so damn awesome. I highly recommend this to everyone :), I wish there were more episodes but it still rocks!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="335089">I never laught that muhc in my life</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="626835">Best comedy anime i ever seen :D,must watch,it`s Masterpiece</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.fujitv.co.jp/b_hp/fullmeta/</url>
<creators>
<name id="736" type="Animation Work">Kyoto Animation</name>
<name id="535" type="Series Composition">Shimo Fumihiko</name>
<name id="537" type="Series Composition">Gatou Shouji</name>
<name id="537" type="Original Work">Gatou Shouji</name>
<name id="533" type="Direction">Takemoto Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
<name id="4314" type="Character Design">Horiuchi Osamu</name>
<name id="7421" type="Original Work">Shiki Douji</name>
</creators>
<description>It is back-to-school mayhem with http://anidb.net/ch1458 [Chidori Kaname] and her battle-hardened classmate http://anidb.net/ch1456 [Sagara Sousuke] as they encounter more misadventures in and out of Jindai High School. But when Kaname gets into some serious trouble, Sousuke takes the guise of http://anidb.net/ch36402 [Bonta-kun] — the gun-wielding, butt-kicking mascot. And while he struggles to continue living as a normal teenager, Sousuke also has to deal with protecting his superior officer http://anidb.net/ch1457 [Teletha Testarossa], who has decided to take a vacation from http://anidb.net/ch6219 [Mithril] and spend a couple of weeks as his and Kaname`s classmate.
Source: ANN
Note: Because of a then current kidnapping event, TV Tokyo did not broadcast what were supposed to be part 2 of episode 1 (A Hostage with No Compromises) and part 1 of episode 2 (Hostility Passing-By). A Hostage with No Compromises was replaced by part 2 of episode 2 (A Fruitless Lunchtime) and thus, episode 2 was skipped, leaving the episode count at 11. The DVD release contained all the episodes in the intended order.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="13015">8.22</permanent>
<temporary count="13212">8.52</temporary>
<review count="21">8.29</review>
</ratings>
<picture>129526.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>155</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>72</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1252</identifier>
<identifier>qaftlx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.fujitv.co.jp/b_hp/fullmeta/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Full_Metal_Panic?_Fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>フルメタル・パニック#.E3.83.95.E3.83.AB.E3.83.A1.E3.82.BF.E3.83.AB.E3.83.BB.E3.83.91.E3.83.8B.E3.83.83.E3.82.AF.3F_.E3.81.B5.E3.82.82.E3.81.A3.E3.81.B5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>115</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>241928</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01NHDHN3L</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="362" parentid="2793" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-24">
<name>dancing</name>
<description>Dance is when people move their body to music. There are many kinds of dance, like ballet or waltz. Dancing can be done for fun but can be also an art.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2621" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>bullet time</name>
<description>Bullet time refers to a simulation of variable speed (i.e. slow motion, time-lapse, …) and is characterized both by its extreme transformation of time and space to show normally imperceptible and un-filmable events, such as flying bullets.
Most infamous scene using this technique, Neo dodging bullets in The Matrix film.</description>
<picurl>211279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2754" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>rugby</name>
<description>Rugby is a style of football game named after Rugby School in the United Kingdom. It is seen most prominently in two current sports, rugby league and rugby union. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3004" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-17">
<name>skilled main character</name>
<description>The main character in the show is very skilled in one or more tasks, often to the amazement of those around him/her.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3647" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-05">
<name>drastic change in sequel</name>
<description>This anime differs greatly in genre and/or overall mood from its prequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-02">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your month and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6577" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-17">
<name>student government</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1456" type="main character in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="902">8.94</rating>
<name>Sagara Sousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sagara Sousuke is a mercenary soldier who is assigned to the elite SRT of Mithril, a secret paramilitary organization. His call sign is Uruz 7. A 17-year-old novice, but has been through many wars since childhood including Helmajistan. A specialist with a long war record, he is extremely skilled. In the use of AS, ranks in the top two in the SRT. Since being scouted by Mithril in Southeast Asia, has been transferred to various locations as a mercenary soldier. When assigned to the SRT, he joined up with Kurz and Mao. Sousuke has known Commanding Officer Kalinin of the main fleet since long before he joined Mithril.</description>
<picture>65944.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1457" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="532">8.33</rating>
<name>Teletha Testarossa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Teletha Testarossa serves as the fleet commander of the West Pacific Ocean Battle Group Tuatha de Danaan, which is under the command of the Combat Division of the secret military organization Mithril. While she is only 16 years old, she is a talent that is indispensable to the West Pacific Ocean Battle Group with her gift as a commander, rare intellect, pride, and competence to match. The delicate, yet gutsy manoeuvring she previously conducted off the coast of Khanka proved that she is an excellent commander and ship`s captain. There are none who harbour any doubts about her abilities. The name of the battle group "Tuatha de Danaan" comes from Celtic mythology and it means "peoples of the goddess Danu". The West Pacific Ocean Battle Group is a brave clan, who serve the goddess Tessa.</description>
<picture>65945.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1458" type="main character in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="734">8.25</rating>
<name>Chidori Kaname</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chidori Kaname is a second-year student in Group Four at Jindai High School. Attentive and takes interest in others, loves to cook. Popular with others, she serves as class representative and student council vice-president. Kaname`s family lives in New York; her father is the United Nations` Environmental High Commissioner. Has a sister, Ayame, who is 11 years old. Her mother passed away three years ago. Kaname returned to Japan alone when she was in middle school, and has lived by herself in Tokyo ever since.</description>
<picture>65955.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1459" type="appears in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="202">7.10</rating>
<name>Melissa Mao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Melissa Mao is serving as the SRT`s second-in-command next to Gail McAllen, she serves in Mithril under the call sign Uruz-2. An expert in engineering, she assisted in the development of the M9 and is also an expert in electronic warfare and AS. Independent and incorrigible. Believes in a woman`s flexibility and cooperation, and takes care of things in a sisterly manner. Passed through Uruz 6 and was promoted to Number Two in SRT as Uruz 2. In the three-man team format of SRT, she often works with Sousuke and Kurz, and is their reliable "big-sister" figure.</description>
<picture>65947.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1460" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="149">7.07</rating>
<name>Kurz Weber</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurz Weber is a member of Mithril and has the rank of Sergeant in the SRT (Special Response Team) of the TDD-1 Tuatha de Danaan Pacific Battle Group. He has the call sign Urzu-6 and his ID number is B-3127. He is an SRT Arm Slave pilot and designated marksman, equally proficient with sniper rifles and Arm Slave long range precision cannons. He is a handsome blond, who once became popular as a model and made the cover of the fashion magazine "Monthly Tokyo Walker - The Tag." But, his speech is full of vulgarities. He has a flippant personality that makes it difficult to believe that he is a skilled sniper.</description>
<picture>65946.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1461" type="appears in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="41">3.28</rating>
<name>Richard Mardukas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The executive officer of the Tuatha de Danaan. He holds Tessa, the battle group commander, in high esteem and trusts her, serving as her aide and assisting her with regards to the battle group. A born and bred English gentleman, he is a loyal subject who serves his queen, Tessa. Due to his overly serious, inflexible and humorless nature, some of the people in Mithril address him familiarly as "Dick". (Naturally, he dislikes it.)</description>
<picture>65949.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1462" type="appears in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="85">6.29</rating>
<name>Andrey Sergeivich Kalinin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The combat commander, who leads the land troops on the Tuatha de Danaan. Kalinin is a skilled strategist and he swiftly makes cool and realistic judgments. At the same time, he does not forget to be considerate of his subordinates. He is a seasoned soldier, who has seen numerous battlefields.</description>
<picture>65948.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6219" type="appears in" update="2009-04-18">
<rating votes="33">7.26</rating>
<name>Mithril</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Mithril is a paramilitary (non-governmental) organization possessing advanced technologies and weapon systems superior to that of any national armed forces. It was founded around 1992-1993, following the detonation of a nuclear warhead in northern Iraq in the then waning Gulf War. It is named after the fictional metal, Mithril, from the The Lord of the Rings written by J. R. R. Tolkien. The organization`s purpose to halt regional conflicts, in addition to securing the Whispered. As such, it is one of the few organizations aware of the Whispered and Black Technology.
Mithril remains an extremely secretive organization, its existence unknown to all but the most senior of military and political personnel. Its motives, funding, structure, and personnel are all kept secret. Its secrecy is vital for its continued existence, as Mithril is a specialist organization dependent on fast surgical strikes with small numbers. They do not possess the numbers or capacity to withstand a conventional war of numbers.
The story of Full Metal Panic primarily follows one section of Mithril, the Pacific Fleet Battle Group Tuatha de Danaan.</description>
<picture>23505.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14079" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="87">4.95</rating>
<name>Tokiwa Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tokiwa Kyouko is Chidori`s humble best friend who brings around her trusty camera. She is constantly trying to bring Chidori and Sagara together, however impossible it may seem given Sagara`s tendency to blow things up at whim.</description>
<picture>65956.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12341" picture="41426.jpg">Kimura Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14360" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-23">
<rating votes="39">3.18</rating>
<name>Kazama Shinji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazama Shinji is Sousuke`s Arm Slave loving classmate. He shares the same amount of passion to AS as Sousuke and could be considered Sousuke`s best school friend besides Kaname. His father is Kazama Shintaro and a secretary of Narashino`s Assault Machine Troop. Shinji`s love for AS began when his dad failed to become an AS pilot. As a result of his father`s failure, Shinji strives to discover the result of the failure and to fulfill his father`s dream of becoming a pilot. There is no indication as to what happened to his mother, but it`s assumed that Shintaro is a widower before the series started.</description>
<picture>143509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14361" type="appears in" update="2010-01-26">
<rating votes="3">3.43</rating>
<name>Jindai Koukou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="15005" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-20">
<rating votes="24">6.21</rating>
<name>Mikihara Ren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikihara Ren is the secretary of Jindai High School`s student council, and a good friend of Kaname. She is also the daughter of a Yakuza oyabun, and her father`s kobun are "trained" by Sousuke in the Bonta-kun suit in a hilarious episode.</description>
<picture>84301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27717" type="appears in" update="2011-01-23">
<rating votes="4">1.65</rating>
<name>Pony Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A man with a ponytail fetish who attacks young girls around Jindai High School, giving them a ponytail hair-do fixed with glue. Kyouko becomes one of his targets.</description>
<picture>64313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27718" type="appears in" update="2011-01-23">
<rating votes="2">1.25</rating>
<name>Pony Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36140" type="appears in" update="2011-09-01">
<rating votes="7">5.00</rating>
<name>Mukai Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="490" picture="17481.jpg">Kikuchi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36141" type="appears in" update="2013-09-23">
<rating votes="9">4.66</rating>
<name>Sakamoto Shouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36142" type="appears in" update="2013-09-23">
<rating votes="4">3.13</rating>
<name>Kojima Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36144" type="appears in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="27">4.34</rating>
<name>Kagurazaka Eri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65957.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1917" picture="151688.jpg">Natsuki Rio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36146" type="appears in" update="2013-09-26">
<rating votes="6">2.79</rating>
<name>Uchida Mayuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="490" picture="17481.jpg">Kikuchi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36147" type="appears in" update="2013-09-23">
<rating votes="10">5.24</rating>
<name>Kudou Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1429" picture="18686.jpg">Konno Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36150" type="appears in" update="2013-09-23">
<rating votes="14">3.88</rating>
<name>Inaba Mizuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143501.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5216" picture="29203.jpg">Yoshida Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36398" type="appears in" update="2011-09-06">
<rating votes="3">4.00</rating>
<name>Saeki Ena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="490" picture="17481.jpg">Kikuchi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36399" type="appears in" update="2011-09-06">
<rating votes="2">5.05</rating>
<name>Tsuboi Takako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10375" picture="186266.jpg">Arima Mizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36400" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="10">6.77</rating>
<name>Hayashimizu Atsunobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65954.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36401" type="appears in" update="2011-09-06">
<rating votes="3">2.72</rating>
<name>Wakana Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1361.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36402" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-05">
<rating votes="15">8.03</rating>
<name>Bonta-kun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>52805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36403" type="appears in" update="2011-09-06">
<rating votes="3">2.19</rating>
<name>Onodera Koutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20305" picture="223542.jpg">Okada Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60028" type="appears in" update="2013-09-23">
<rating votes="5">3.33</rating>
<name>Isomura Tomomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143524.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60068" type="appears in" update="2013-09-26">
<rating votes="4">3.52</rating>
<name>Tanabe Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143596.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60159" type="appears in" update="2013-10-02">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Akutsu Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1871" picture="20967.jpg">Asano Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60160" type="appears in" update="2013-10-02">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Akutsu Yoshiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143787.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43303" picture="174447.jpg">Hamada Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60163" type="appears in" update="2013-10-02">
<rating votes="2">3.29</rating>
<name>Kogure-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3312" picture="24691.jpg">Ikemizu Michihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60164" type="appears in" update="2013-10-02">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Nishino Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nishino Kozue is an infirmary doctor.</description>
<picture>143794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1429" picture="18686.jpg">Konno Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60165" type="appears in" update="2013-10-02">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Fujisaki-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60170" type="appears in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Masatami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60171" type="appears in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Washio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143820.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14755" picture="242189.jpg">Sawa Ritsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60172" type="appears in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Hyoudou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143821.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60173" type="appears in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="2">3.29</rating>
<name>Samejima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60176" type="appears in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Mizuhoshi Iori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mizuhoshi Iori is an Art teacher at Jindai High.</description>
<picture>143829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60177" type="appears in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Mizuhoshi no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mother of teacher Mizuhoshi Iori.</description>
<picture>143831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4002" picture="77706.jpg">Naka Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60178" type="appears in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="2">3.29</rating>
<name>Fuwa-senpai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60189" type="appears in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="3">5.34</rating>
<name>Tsubaki Issei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60190" type="appears in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Sasaki Hiromi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143848.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1871" picture="20967.jpg">Asano Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60191" type="appears in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Oonuki Zenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60207" type="appears in" update="2013-10-04">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Karate Doukoukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Karate club.
Consist of:
* Waffle (ワッフル)
* Marron (マロン)
* Chocolat (ショコラ)</description>
<picture>143850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60212" type="appears in" update="2013-10-04">
<rating votes="3">5.41</rating>
<name>Amemiya Takami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143873.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4522" picture="26784.jpg">Shimokawa Mikuni</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60213" type="appears in" update="2013-10-04">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Gen-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3400" picture="24480.jpg">Uemura Kihachirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60214" type="appears in" update="2013-10-04">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Gen-san no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5960" picture="188720.jpg">Ootori Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60236" type="appears in" update="2013-10-06">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Gouda Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gouda Yuu is a captain of Jindai High School rugby club.</description>
<picture>143911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60237" type="appears in" update="2013-10-06">
<rating votes="2">3.29</rating>
<name>Garasuyama Koukou Rugby Buchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain of Garasuyama High School rugby club.</description>
<picture>143912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3225" picture="24205.jpg">Watabe Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60254" type="appears in" update="2013-10-06">
<name>Shibata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3970" picture="25848.jpg">Nishiwaki Tamotsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60255" type="appears in" update="2013-10-06">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Mikihara Kanji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikihara Kanji is the head of the Mikihara Gang and Ren`s father.</description>
<picture>143929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4683" picture="27279.jpg">Koyama Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60256" type="appears in" update="2016-01-06">
<rating votes="2">4.75</rating>
<name>Ryousan Gata Bonta-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Mass-Produced type Bonta-kun.</description>
<picture>143930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2413" picture="22272.jpg">Mizuta Wasabi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60257" type="appears in" update="2013-10-06">
<rating votes="1">1.31</rating>
<name>Ryuujin Kai Kumichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Head of Ryuujin Gang.</description>
<picture>143931.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3229" picture="186246.jpg">Hazumi Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60258" type="appears in" update="2013-10-06">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Nanba Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60259" type="appears in" update="2013-10-06">
<rating votes="2">3.29</rating>
<name>Obaasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2040" picture="186173.jpg">Suzuki Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80433" type="appears in" update="2016-02-23">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>TDD-1 Tuatha de Danaan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The TDD-1 Tuatha de Danaan is the world`s most advanced submarine and is http://anidb.net/ch6219 [Mithril]`s flagship. It is classified as an assault landing submarine and houses a variety of http://anidb.net/t912 [Arm Slaves], aircraft, and other small vehicles. In addition to its revolutionary hull design, the Danaan possesses a sophisticated artificial intelligence called http://anidb.net/ch80514 [Dana]. In a sealed area of the ship called the Lady Chapel, a TAROS device is installed for http://anidb.net/t403 [Whispered] use.
It was originally an abandoned Soviet submarine but was procured and rebuilt with http://anidb.net/ch1457 [Teletha Testarossa]`s knowledge.
Source: Fullmetal Panic! Wikia</description>
<picture>183154.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="80514" type="appears in" update="2016-02-23">
<rating votes="2">2.60</rating>
<name>Dana</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dana is the artificial intelligence in control of the http://anidb.net/ch80433 [Tuatha de Danaan].</description>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="10407" update="2018-07-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="39">9.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">南から来た男 / 空回りのランチタイム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man from the South / A Fruitless Lunchtime</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`homme venu du sud / Une pause déjeuner mouvementée</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`uomo venuto dal sud / Lunchtime sprecato</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">남쪽에서 온 남자 / 타협 무용의 호스티지</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minami kara Kita Otoko / Karamawari no Lunchtime</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10622" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="32">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鋼鉄のサマー・イリュージョン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Illusion of Steel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`illusion d`acier de l`été</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Summer Illusion d`acciaio</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">강철의 섬머 일루전</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Ilusões De Aço do Verão!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutetsu no Summer Illusion</title>
<summary>Kaname’s having tea with a wealthy young man when Sousuke shows up looking for her. Things get awkward after accusations of stalking and perverted behavior force Sousuke to infiltrate the guy`s house.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750533</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="10857" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="31">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">芸術のハンバーガー・ヒル / 一途なステイク・アウト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hamburger Hill of Art / Single Minded Stakeout!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La montagne d`arts de hamburgers / Une surveillance exclusive</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Hamburger Hill artistico / Una fedele stake out</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">예술의 햄버거 힐 / 하루만의 스테이크 아웃</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Monte Hambúrguer Da Arte! - O Vigia Ingênuo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Geijutsu no Hamburger Hill / Ichizu na Stake-Out</title>
<summary>Sousuke’s career as an artist’s model gets off to a rough start when he learns he may have to show some skin. And when Kaname is threatened by Yakuza thugs, Sagara uses Bonta-kun to save her!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750537</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11118" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="28">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">押し売りのフェティッシュ / 暗闇のペイシェント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hard Sell Fetish / The Patient of Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le fétichiste importun / Les patients des ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Fetish del far comprare sotto minaccia / Patient delle tenebre</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">강매의 페티쉬 / 암흑의 페이션트</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Fetiche Da Venda Forçada! - O Paciente Da Escuridão!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshiuri no Fetish / Kurayami no Patient</title>
<summary>While Kaname works with the cops to catch a pervert, Sousuke tries to protect her - and quickly becomes a suspect in the case! Later, Kaname and Mizuki try to scare Sagara in an abandoned hospital.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750541</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11663" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="26">8.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">純で不純なグラップラー / 善意のトレスパス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pure Yet Impure Grappler / Trespassing on Good Faith</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le combattant pur mais impur / Intrusion de bonne foi</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Grappler puro e impuro / Trespass con buone intenzioni</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A Pura Porém Impura Batalha! - Invadindo Em Boa Fé!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jun de Fujun na Grappler / Zen`i no Trespass</title>
<summary>When Sousuke takes on the Karate Club, the first three fights are no problem - the club president is another story. And when the janitor is injured during the brawl, one of the guys has to help him with his duties.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750547</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11814" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="35">9.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やりすぎのウォークライ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The War Cry of Excessiveness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cri de guerre exagéré</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Warcry esagerato</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Grito De Guerra Do Exagero!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yarisugi no War Cry</title>
<summary>The Jindai High Rugby Club will be disbanded unless Sousuke and Kaname can whip them into shape. It’ll be a tough mission - the club is made up of a bunch of losers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750549</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11892" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="33">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女神の来日 (受難編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Goddess Comes to Japan (Part 1: The Suffering)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une déesse arrive au Japon (partie 1) : La souffrance</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`arrivo in Giappone della dea (capitolo della sofferenza)</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Uma Deusa Chega Ao Japão! (Parte 1: O Sofrimento!)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Megami no Rainichi (Junan Hen)</title>
<summary>Tessa decides to take some time off and goes to Sousuke`s school for two weeks. Unfortunately, between work and homework, Sousuke’s feeling pretty stressed out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750551</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="12072" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="33">9.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女神の来日 (温泉編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Goddess Comes to Japan (Part 2: The Hot Spring)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une déesse arrive au Japon (partie 2) : Les sources chaudes</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`arrivo in Giappone della dea (capitolo delle terme)</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Uma Deusa Chega Ao Japão! (Parte a: As Termas!)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Megami no Rainichi (Onsen Hen)</title>
<summary>When Tessa, Sousuke, and Kaname head to the hot springs, Kurz undertakes a special mission: peeking into the girls’ bath. Luckily, Sagara has already planned for this and planted a trap.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750553</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="12345" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="25">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仁義なきファンシー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fancy Without Honor or Humanity</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une fantaisie sans morale</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Fancy senza codice d`onore</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Uma Fantasia Sem Honra Ou Humanidade!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinginaki Fancy</title>
<summary>Ren’s dad - a Yakuza boss - hires Sousuke to train his men how to fight. The gangsters’ new skills are put to the test when a rival organization kidnaps Ren and Kaname!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750561</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="12505" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="27">8.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ままならないブルーバード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uncontrollable Bluebird</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le bluebird incontrôlable</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il blue bird che non fa quello che dici</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Incontrolável Pássaro Azul!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamanaranai Blue Bird</title>
<summary>The Sociology Club conducts an experiment to find out which school club flirts the best. Sousuke helps out Shinji in the Photo Club, but it’s soon apparent he has no idea how to handle the opposite sex.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750563</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="12844" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="39">9.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">五時間目のホット・スポット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">5th Period Hot Spot</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le moment critique du 5e cours</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`hot spot della quinta ora</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Região De Conflito Do 5º Período!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gojikanme no Hot Spot</title>
<summary>Sousuke orders a new scope for his pistol, but receives a strange bottle instead. Unfortunately, the contents are a biological weapon. Even worse, the bottle is opened up in the school!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750569</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="13090" update="2018-07-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="19">9.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">南から来た男 / 妥協無用のホステージ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man from the South / A Hostage with No Compromises</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`homme venu du sud / Un otage sans compromis</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`uomo venuto dal sud / Hostage senza negoziati</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Homem Que Veio Do Sul! - Um Refém Sem Compromissos!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minami kara Kita Otoko / Dakyou Muyou no Hostage</title>
<summary>After Sousuke blows up his shoe locker, a strange letter is found in the rubble. Later, Kaname is kidnapped by a gang of high school punks!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750527</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="13112" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="18">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すれ違いのホスティリティ / 空回りのランチタイム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hostility Passing-By / A Fruitless Lunchtime</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une hostilité passagère / Une pause déjeuner mouvementée</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Hostility non ricambiata / Lunchtime sprecato</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Hostilidade Passageira! - Um Almoço Sem Resultados!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surechigai no Hostility / Karamawari no Lunchtime</title>
<summary>After Sousuke causes a lunchtime riot, he and Kaname must man the bread counter and serve the students. Meanwhile, a mad dash ensues when Sagara forgets to bring Kaname’s study notes to school.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750529</identifier>
<identifier>full-metal-panic-fumoffu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="38108" update="2018-02-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38109" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2003-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196611" update="2018-05-18">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2003-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
