<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9622" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-04-29</startdate>
<enddate>2013-07-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Miyakawa-ke no Kuufuku</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Miyakawa Family`s Hunger</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">宮河家の空腹</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4777" type="Same Setting">Lucky Star</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4492" approval="2" total="7">Binbou Shimai Monogatari</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://miyakawahungry.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="677" type="Series Composition">Machida Touko</name>
<name id="6366" type="Original Work">Yoshimizu Kagami</name>
<name id="121" type="Direction">Yamamoto Yutaka</name>
<name id="1560" type="Animation Work">Ordet</name>
<name id="19117" type="Animation Work">Encourage Films</name>
<name id="2560" type="Music">Maeyamada Ken`ichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Spin-off of http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star].
http://anidb.net/ch10926 [Miyakawa Hikage] is an elementary school girl, living with her older sister http://anidb.net/ch10925 [Hinata]. Every day they have to struggle with the poverty and financial ruin that go along with an otaku spending lifestyle.
Note: The series originally received a streaming on the Ustream service. Later it was bundled on a DVD with the limited-edition 10th volume of the original Lucky Star manga on October 26, 2013, to commemorate the 10-year anniversary of the Lucky Star series.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="597">4.36</permanent>
<temporary count="599">6.17</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>136059.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15276</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17637</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ustream.tv/channel/宮河家の空腹</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://miyakawahungry.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>宮河家の空腹</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3005</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345230</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16141</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="32" type="appears in" update="2019-12-28">
<rating votes="653">8.96</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Kagami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukasa`s elder twin sister. Konata`s close friend. Her thought process is normal, so she often pokes fun at Konata. She may be the most right-minded character. An aloof-chummy type, who is warm-hearted only when she has gotten to know you.</description>
<picture>18662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2999" type="appears in" update="2013-10-22">
<rating votes="974">9.11</rating>
<name>Izumi Konata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who loves manga, anime, and video games. Because of this, her thought process is largely influenced by her favourite works... She has great athletic ability, but is an indoor person who rarely utilises this talent.</description>
<picture>18649.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3000" type="appears in" update="2019-12-28">
<rating votes="230">7.12</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Tsukasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kagami`s younger twin sister and close friend of Konata`s. She has a tolerant attitude and shrugs aside Konata`s silliness. Perhaps she just simply goes with the flow. A typical friendly, soothing character. Is actually a mayonnaise fiend?</description>
<picture>18650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="425" picture="17296.jpg">Fukuhara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3010" type="appears in" update="2018-07-22">
<rating votes="70">6.67</rating>
<name>Kogami Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Host of radio show "Lucky Channel". An idol currently appearing on TV and radio! At first sight, she looks like the cute type of character, but at 14 years old, she has 11 years of experience in the entertainment business, so she is also a veteran entertainer, who is strict about etiquette! She seems greatly displeased with Minoru Shiraishi, a newcomer recently experiencing a wave of success.</description>
<picture>18660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1429" picture="18686.jpg">Konno Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6639" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-02">
<rating votes="73">7.52</rating>
<name>Anizawa Meito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anizawa Meito, also known as Anime Tenchou, is the manager of the Animate Ikebukuro shop (However, he appeared in the (old) Oomiya shop and the comic market booth in the Anime and appeared in the Akihabara shop in the PS2 Video Game), he was originally the mascot of Animate and Hero of Anime Tenchou.
He and his staff consider Konata their most valued customer, known as "Legendary Girl A" (伝説の少女A ,Densetsu no Shoujo A), and go to great lengths to sell their merchandise to her, often to the point of using espionage and military-style strategies, and at one point, Meito himself uses "Geass" on Konata to persuade her to buy a DVD from him; however when she tries to pay it, she fell short only three yen. Their attempts usually fail miserably. His appearance is heavily stylized, compared to the other characters, and he is known for his passionate yelling and highly energetic movements and poses. He appeared as a special guest during the Lucky Channel segment in episode seventeen, during which he and Minoru parody Mobile Fighter G Gundam`s Domon Kasshu, referencing the fact that Meito`s voice actor also played the character. He also appeared in episode twelve, fighting against another sales manager (about how valuable "so-called leftovers" can be after they ran out of rare and limited edition "thingies") in a dramatic way. Meito`s colleagues at Animate are all similarly enthusiastic about selling their merchandise. In 2002, Gainax produced a single original video animation, where Meito Anisawa and his fellow employees are the focus.</description>
<picture>29604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6640" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-04">
<name>Hoshii Lamica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hoshii Lamica is the clerk (Laminate card and Boys Love commodity charge) of the Animate Ikebukuro shop (However, she appeared in the (old) Omiya shop in the anime). She is the heroine of Anime Tenchou.</description>
<picture>32523.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6647" type="appears in" update="2009-06-19">
<rating votes="5">8.73</rating>
<name>Nyamoo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nyamoo is a mysterious creature that looks like a cat head with a tail. He is handled as a self-portrait of the creator, Kagami Yoshimizu.</description>
<picture>3053.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="10925" type="main character in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="12">3.43</rating>
<name>Miyakawa Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyakawa Hinata is a young girl with long salmon pink hair, which she ties just a bit to the left of her forehead with a rabbit clip; she has pink droopy eyes and is a meganekko. She makes a living through a job at a local doujin shop. However, she remains poor, as all her money is spent on manga and doujinshi.</description>
<picture>60546.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="22626" picture="59507.jpg">Shimagata Maina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10926" type="main character in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="17">6.70</rating>
<name>Miyakawa Hikage</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyakawa Hikage is the younger sister of http://anidb.net/ch10925 [Miyakawa Hinata] and is in the fourth grade; she is the youngest character in Lucky Star. She attends the Sakura-en Public Elementary School, and is in class 4-1. She is not an otaku like her older sister, and as such carries the typical tsundere personality. Hikage lives in poverty because of her older sister and wants to grow up so she can get a job on her own; ironically, though, her dream is to eat meat. It is also because of her poverty caused by her sister that she starts to have distaste over otaku. Hikage likes to play gachapon, shopping, and travelling. Hikage`s appearance in the game has her with long light-purple hair; her hairstyle is distinctive, as she thinly braids her hair to the right, and uses that as a ribbon to tie her remaining hair. Her eyes are light blue and are slanted upward. Her appearance is a little different in the anime and manga, as she has short, blue hair instead of long, purple hair.</description>
<picture>60545.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="36504" picture="134684.jpg">Kawasaki Kotoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54545" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-08">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Mizushima Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36503" picture="134685.jpg">Oda Karin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54546" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Koike Erika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134535.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36502" picture="134686.jpg">Iwasaki Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54547" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="2">1.90</rating>
<name>Oosawa Kazuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54548" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="2">5.16</rating>
<name>Utsumi Yukina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134536.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36505" picture="134683.jpg">Sowa Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54549" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="2">5.16</rating>
<name>Koizumi Marina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36501" picture="134687.jpg">Yamada Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69938" type="appears in" update="2014-09-13">
<name>Koneko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62165.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="150208" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150236" update="2013-04-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決められた運命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimerareta Unmei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150399" update="2013-05-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150400" update="2013-05-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150401" update="2013-05-06">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150402" update="2013-05-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150403" update="2013-05-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151109" update="2013-06-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151110" update="2013-06-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151111" update="2013-06-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151112" update="2013-06-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151535" update="2013-07-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157610" update="2014-01-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
