<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9663" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-07-02</startdate>
<enddate>2013-09-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Inu to Hasami wa Tsukaiyou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Inuhasa</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">犬とハサミは使いよう</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dog &amp; Scissors</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">狗与剪刀的正确用法</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="434490">Average series with a story that goes nowhere, unfortunately. The setting was sort of interesting, though I doubt it will get a second series. For fans only, and even then, there are better.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="430272">not much of a plot to speak of but it was funny at times. Nothing too special. But a decent watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="328481">Well some ppl say bad and some say good, they all r true...as for me I can enjoy this show even there`s much better anime than this...recommended for those who seeking some light story</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="430122">It`s a short anime. Entertaining at times, but ultimately mediocre. Not a terrible watch, but definitely not memorable. Struggles to find a genre, with elements of comedy, mystery and drama, it fails in each category.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="130855">it`s a nice anime, I don`t know why it got a low rate.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://inuhasa.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9221" type="Character Design">Satou Youko</name>
<name id="1543" type="Series Composition">Nemoto Toshizou</name>
<name id="15891" type="Direction">Takahashi Yukio</name>
<name id="36136" type="Music">Matsuda Akito</name>
<name id="38001" type="Original Work">Sarai Shunsuke</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch54086 [Harumi Kazuhito], is a high school boy obsessed with reading books. One day, he is killed in the middle of a robbery — and resurrected as a dachshund dog. Unable to read in his new form, the hapless Kazuhito now belongs to http://anidb.net/ch54087 [Natsuno Kirihime], a sadistic girl who uses scissors like a weapon.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1351">3.21</permanent>
<temporary count="1366">5.89</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>136460.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15101</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17831</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://inuhasa.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dog_&amp;_Scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>犬とハサミは使いよう</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3019</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>346191</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16168</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="638" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>telepathy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1634" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-13">
<name>obsessive -- DO NOT USE -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is meant to be split and deleted. Please help by tagging all relevant characters with more specific tags and then deleting this tag from them or from their anime, as applicable. Depending on the context, such tags may include, among others: any of the http://anidb.net/t48 [complexes], http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku], http://anidb.net/t1538 [passionate], http://anidb.net/t1699 [persistent], http://anidb.net/t2034 [psychopath], or http://anidb.net/t1208 [yandere].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2019" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-16">
<name>suicidal</name>
<description>The character has suicidal tendencies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2406" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-13">
<name>talking animal</name>
<description>Talking animals are a common theme in mythology and folk tales, as well as children`s literature. Fictional talking creatures often are anthropomorphic, possessing human-like qualities but appearing as a creature. An animal that only knows how to say its name (for example, 99.9% of all http://anidb.net/t2493 [Pokemon]), are not talking animals.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3233" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-13">
<name>cooking curry</name>
<description>Japanese curry, usually eaten as curry rice, and often pickled vegetables, served on the same plate and eaten with a spoon, is one of the most popular dishes in Japan, where people eat it 125 times a year according to a survey made in 2005.
As such Japanese series will often devote a whole episode to the characters cooking and eating curry dishes.</description>
<picurl>160828.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3772" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-09-03">
<name>library</name>
<description>In a traditional sense, a library is a large collection of books, and can refer to the place in which the collection is housed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4085" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-17">
<name>unlikely duo</name>
<description>Comedy element: There is usually not only a difference in gender but also in appearance, character, and background concerning the main characters of this anime. Making it very unlikely for them to appear in the same context. Non-the-less they share the same adventure, as in "opposites attract".
These differences are exploited to come up with all sorts of wacky situations.
Examples: A demon-killer or Hero and the daughter of the Demon King. A girl from a normal family and a very intelligent and attractive boy from a very rich background (Shoujo). A very energetic outgoing girl and her very calm almost introverted best friend.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4148" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-11">
<name>late for school</name>
<description>A common device for a series opening or Establishing Character Moment. Things begin in a frantic rush which usually results in taking short cuts, such as eating breakfast on the run. The classic image is of someone running down the street with a slice of toast hanging out of their mouth, dragging their backpack with one hand while trying to put on their jacket or sweater one-handed with the other, bumping into important people in a manner that gets the plot started.
Basically, they`re never on time for school. While some are Heavy Sleepers, it would appear that they may have simply set their alarm clocks so as to give them insufficient time to get to class. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>161002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4566" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-08">
<name>transforming weapons</name>
<description>This anime features transforming weapons, this can either be cars or household appliances that transform into weapons, such as transformers or weapons that themselves transform into bigger badder shapes to deal more and more damage.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6066" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>improvised weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be split and deleted. Please apply any applicable http://anidb.net/tag/?parentid=7405&amp;reltb=chartb [weaponized object tags] to the relevant characters, or create new tags if necessary, and delete this tag from the anime/character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="54086" type="main character in" update="2013-05-09">
<rating votes="9">5.01</rating>
<name>Harumi Kazuhito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136446.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54087" type="main character in" update="2014-03-04">
<rating votes="25">6.82</rating>
<name>Natsuno Kirihime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54088" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-12">
<rating votes="9">3.62</rating>
<name>Harumi Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54089" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-09">
<rating votes="8">5.57</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Suzuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54090" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-09">
<rating votes="5">4.36</rating>
<name>Oosawa Hami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32939" picture="237666.jpg">Kakuma Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54091" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-09">
<rating votes="8">4.77</rating>
<name>Akizuki Maxi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36230" picture="242785.jpg">Serizawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55730" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-09">
<rating votes="4">5.96</rating>
<name>Honda Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55731" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-09">
<rating votes="5">6.56</rating>
<name>Honda Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55732" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-09">
<rating votes="7">4.13</rating>
<name>Moribe Sachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55733" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-09">
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<name>Inukai Kiyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55734" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-09">
<rating votes="4">5.00</rating>
<name>Himehagi Momiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136456.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57627" type="appears in" update="2013-07-01">
<name>Reporter</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32035" picture="151695.jpg">Muranaka Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57628" type="appears in" update="2013-07-01">
<name>Announcer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24404" picture="68958.jpg">Murakami Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57629" type="appears in" update="2013-07-01">
<name>Chiyadou Motoharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6125" picture="223612.jpg">Hayashi Kazuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57630" type="appears in" update="2013-07-01">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Honda Fumio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57631" type="appears in" update="2013-07-01">
<name>Munakata Wanriki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57632" type="appears in" update="2013-07-10">
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<name>Nakahara Touji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57633" type="appears in" update="2013-07-01">
<rating votes="2">7.16</rating>
<name>Harumi Kazuhito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57845" type="appears in" update="2013-08-20">
<rating votes="2">3.92</rating>
<name>Sumiya Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57846" type="appears in" update="2013-07-10">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Hotokezaka Daimon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57891" type="appears in" update="2013-07-16">
<name>Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140056.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21821" picture="56272.jpg">Kimura Akitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58258" type="appears in" update="2013-07-30">
<name>Maguro Eater</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31804" picture="223704.jpg">Ueda Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59047" type="appears in" update="2013-08-20">
<name>Kyoudan Member</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141728.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59048" type="appears in" update="2013-08-20">
<rating votes="2">3.92</rating>
<name>Hamono-sou Okami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59218" type="appears in" update="2013-08-27">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Oosawa Shuuzan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59893" type="appears in" update="2013-09-17">
<name>Kure Mayuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13872" picture="223706.jpg">Yamaguchi Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="151525" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬も歩けば棒に当たる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Every Dog Has His Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu mo Arukeba Bou ni Ataru</title>
<summary>One day, the young man Harumi Kazuhito is suddenly killed during a robbery.
However, through sheer tenacity, the bookworm is resurrected as a dachshund dog.
With red eyes and silver scissors in her hand, Natsuno Kirihime, a dark haired sadist clad in completely in black appears before him.
Moreover, she understands him as a dog and is his favorite author, Akiyama Shinobu herself...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627913</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151530" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">溺れる者は犬をも掴む</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drowning Men Clutch at Dogs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oboreru Mono wa Inu o mo Tsukamu</title>
<summary>Kazuhito is caught in a trap and captured. When he regains consciousness, he finds himself in his room at Sumitani Hall, wrapped in a mat and accompanied by Madoka... who appears to be acting strangely... Could Madoka be the killer behind the slasher incident?! Before long, Natsuno saves Kazuhito before he is forced to taste fear, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627919</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151531" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛んで火に入る冬の犬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Winter Dog Flies into the Fire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tonde Hi ni Iru Fuyu no Inu</title>
<summary>After seeing her in a dream, Kazuhito recalls his younger sister Harumi Madoka. His nostalgia is cut short when Akiyama Shinobu`s editor Hiiragi Suzuna appears, a massive masochist with huge breasts prone to fantasizing. What`s worse, Natsuno is in a slump?! As they discuss how to get over her slump, the subject of a mysterious slasher case arises.
However, lurking in the shadows of the incident are glimpses of Akiyama Shinobu`s book and Madoka...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627917</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151532" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬は熱いうちに打て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strike While the Dog Is Hot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu wa Atsui Uchi ni Ute</title>
<summary>Kazuhito ends up living with the massive sadist Natsuno Kirihime. Now spending his days in fear of attacks with scissors, one day, a remark from Natsuno sends Kazuhito back to the apartment he lived in as a human. As Kazuhito experiences nostalgia for his old life, Natsuno begins describing the movements of Nakahara Toji, the man who committed the robbery. "It`s only a wild fantasy, but it`s the story of you and the man who killed you..."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627915</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151533" update="2013-07-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151534" update="2013-07-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151955" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">湯に入りて犬に入らざれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dogs in Moderation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yu ni Irite Inu ni Irazare</title>
<summary>Japanese swords, spears, knives, wakizashi... the sacred land of blades, Blade Hall.
At the elegant Shinise Ryokan they are met by the landlady and good friend of their landlord. While Natsuno traveled far to sharpen the dull blade of her favorite scissors Hasajiro, she secretly had another motive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627927</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151956" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬も鳴かずば撃たれまい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dog Would Not Be Shot but for Its Cries</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu mo Nakazuba Utaremai</title>
<summary>Another incident?! Natsuno`s bra has disappeared. To think she had been wearing it...
They call Suzuna and search her apartment. It`s not in her room or in the gym.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627925</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151957" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨降って犬固まる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rain Settles the Dog</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ame Futte Inu Katamaru</title>
<summary>Honda Bookseller`s is in big trouble?! One of Kazuhito`s favorite stores, Honda Bookseller`s.
The owner is Honda Fumio, terrible at business and good with people.
But for him to go bankrupt and escape in the night... wouldn`t be inconceivable.
A concerned Kazuhito heads to Honda Bookseller`s with his favorite bag, but is captured by the runaway Honda Yayoi and gets caught up in her escape from home.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627923</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151958" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虎穴に入らずんば犬を得ず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nothing Ventured, No Dog Gained</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koketsu ni Irazunba Inu o Ezu</title>
<summary>Madoka kicks her way through an apartment window in pursuit of Kazuhito. Natsuno`s true identity is revealed.
For Madoka, she is her brother`s killer--Akiyama Shinobu. Natsuno attempts to speak for Kazuhito and convey his thoughts, but Madoka takes Kazuhito in her arms and leaves through the window, escaping into the night.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627921</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152491" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬とハサミは使いよう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dogs and Scissors Require Good Handling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu to Hasami wa Tsukaiyou</title>
<summary>Kazuhito lives his life with the massive sadist Natsuno, the mysterious masked author Akiyama Shinobu. However, believing it to be her chance, Suzuna encourages Natsuno to hold a signing. Telling her to work more publicly, she enters her into a cosplay event.
When Madoka and Hami come to visit, they become involved as well...
Next, in an attempt to inebriate the stubborn Natsuno, she reaches for strong alcohol...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627935</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152492" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬振り合うのも多生の縁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Dog by Chance Is Preordained</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu Furiau no mo Tashou no En</title>
<summary>Various customers come to visit Honda Bookseller`s. So many people, so many minds, each with their own color, and each with their own book.
There Daimon and his men in black suddenly appear, buying up all of Akiyama Shinobu and Himehagi Momiji`s books.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627933</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152493" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光陰犬の如し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time Flies Like a Dog</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouin Inu no Gotoshi</title>
<summary>In the library`s anteroom, they find Natsuno`s stalker Fujimaki Hotaru--her classmate Osawa Hami.
She and Kazuhito had once exchanged promises--that she would become an author and he would be her first reader. Having become an author, Hami returned to see Kazuhito. "Welcome home, Kazuhito-kun."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627931</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152494" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬無いところに煙は立たず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There Is No Smoke Without Dog</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu Nai Tokoro ni Kemuri wa Tatazu</title>
<summary>For some time, Natsuno has suspected she is being watched. One day while she is out, someone breaks into Natsuno`s perfectly secure room and removes a single book.
It happens to be the book she just purchased at Sakura`s recommendation, the winner of the full-length novel special award, Heiando`s newest author Fujimaki Hotaru`s "Keisei Love Story."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627929</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156027" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627907</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156028" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627855</identifier>
<identifier>dog-scissors</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156029" update="2013-11-16">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156030" update="2013-11-16">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156031" update="2013-11-16">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
