<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9671" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-07-27</startdate>
<enddate>2013-07-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Toriko: Bishokushin no Special Menu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版トリコ 美食神の超食宝[スペシャルメニュー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Toriko the Movie, Secret Recipe of Gourmet God</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8142" type="Parent Story">Toriko (2011)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.toriko-movie.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="21534" type="Original Work">Shimabukuro Mitsutoshi</name>
<name id="15768" type="Direction">Zako Akifumi</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch31080 [Teppei] asks http://anidb.net/ch19496 [Toriko] to investigate the former 1st Biotope, also known as Acacia`s Kitchen, and find the special hidden menu detailing the full-course meal of the legendary Bishokushin http://anidb.net/ch29703 [Acacia].
The quest to uncover the secret of the special menu takes Toriko, Teppei, http://anidb.net/ch19497 [Komatsu], http://anidb.net/ch25830 [Rin] and http://anidb.net/ch25834 [Terry Cloth] through the dangerous Hungry Triangle to eventually land on the island where Acacia`s Kitchen is located. On the island they discover a bounty beyond anything they could have imagined: rare species of animals, Regal Mammoths, terrifying monsters, strange ruins and a giant refrigerator.
Source: Toriko Wiki</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="123">5.59</permanent>
<temporary count="124">6.82</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>135646.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15111</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17699</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toriko-movie.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>トリコ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345626</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16267</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07DQBBL2P</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1162" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="1891">9.23</rating>
<name>Sakata Gintoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakata Gintoki is the main character of the story. He has naturally permed hair, which he blames for his lack of a love-life. He rides a motor scooter and wields a bokuto, which has "Lake Touya" inscribed on it. His job, as is written on his business card, is a "free-lancer", meaning he`ll take any job for nearly any price. He enjoys reading http://anidb.net/cr5372 [Shounen Jump] comics and he has a sweet tooth and will go into crazed combat if he does not have his sweets (he has glycosuria).
In the past, he was a Joui (someone who attempted to overthrow Amanto to protect the government). The reason Gintoki does not join http://anidb.net/ch1165 [Katsura Kotarou] again to fight the aliens is that he does not like to fight alongside "gloomy terrorists".</description>
<picture>137509.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1163" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="274">6.18</rating>
<name>Shimura Shinpachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinpachi Shimura works under Gintoki to learn the ways of the samurai. He used to stay at his family`s doujo. However, it seems more like he`s just trying to help Gintoki pay the rent than to learn. Shinpachi is the captain of the "Otsu`s Imperial Guard," a pop-singer`s fan club, and takes his role seriously. Other members of the fan club treat him with utmost respect, something he isn`t treated with usually.</description>
<picture>29353.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1164" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-04-20">
<rating votes="700">8.68</rating>
<name>Kagura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Although she appears to be a normal, cute, human girl in Chinese-style clothing, she actually belongs to the Yato Clan, one of the strongest and most bloodthirsty of the Amanto races, although Kagura rejects that part of herself. The Yato are said to have "transparent" (snow-white) skin that is highly sensitive to sunlight, so Kagura carries a purple parasol at all times. The parasol is also the Yato clan`s weapon of choice; Kagura`s is bulletproof and fires bullets from its tip. Because of her Yato blood, she is super-strong and can stop a speeding motorscooter with one hand. Although stronger than most humans, she cannot control her strength perfectly. Her super-human strength makes her extremely bad with pets. Most of her pets, with the exception of Sadaharu, have met with an untimely demise by her hands.</description>
<picture>29350.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19496" type="main character in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="72">7.09</rating>
<name>Toriko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Gourmet Hunter with an abnormally large appetite (A food serving for 500 people could only get him 1/10 full). He is known as one of the "Four Heavenly Kings", and his nickname is "The Glutton". Despite having a huge appetite and massive power, he doesn`t indiscriminately kill and eat any animal; he only kills those animals he decides to eat. He has immunity to seventy different poisons, created by injecting himself with a near fatal dose of each poison and causing his body to create antibodies. He also has an animal-like sense of smell. He has adopted the Battle Wolf`s new born pup and named it Terry Cloth. Like the other Kings, Toriko started of as a chain animal.</description>
<picture>73363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19497" type="main character in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="27">3.32</rating>
<name>Komatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A six-star, (initially five), chef who works for Hotel Gourmet, part of the prestigious IGO (International Gourmet Organization). He is timid, but greatly interested by what he finds in his travels with Toriko. As a result, he tries to overcome his fear and does his best to help. He is a highly skilled and competent chief and has a large knowledge of foods that he knows which foods would work well together. Because he is otherwise normal, he`ll write a will whenever he come along on Toriko`s hunts. Currently, he is the only chef in the world who knows the complete recipe of the Century Soup. He keeps a Wall Penguin as a pet, which is also a key element of the soup.</description>
<picture>73364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57315" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-20">
<rating votes="2">5.60</rating>
<name>Coco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57316" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-20">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Sunny</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57317" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-20">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Zebra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138785.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34211" picture="126923.jpg">Matsuda Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57456" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-24">
<name>Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38118" picture="139627.jpg">Maya Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57457" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-24">
<name>Girim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34374" picture="127853.jpg">Kitaooji Kin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="147897" update="2013-10-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>80</length>
<airdate>2013-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
