<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9676" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-07-07</startdate>
<enddate>2013-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Genshiken Nidaime</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Genshiken Second Season</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Genshiken Gen2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">げんしけん 二代目</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Genshiken Second Generation</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">现视研 二代目</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9934" type="Prequel">Genshiken Nidaime no Roku</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9093" approval="1" total="7">Moyashimon Returns</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="44864">I`m torn. The parts with the original cast and especially Madarame are great but the new cast is just alright. Their first and most overwhelming character trait is being a fujoshi. Everything else is not as important. In fact, this is pretty much Fujoshi the Anime in some respects so if you`re not into that you`re going to have a hard time enjoying this series.

Hato, which is without a doubt the focus of the entire show is not really that interesting. There`s no much otaku talk and everything is BL focused, which is a shame. I wish the author had balanced it more.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="326899">After two or three episodes I just asked myself  "What da F**k am I watching ?" 
But still Genshiken story continued to drift into total disorientation and weirdness even thou I thought it can`t be weirder. Nevertheless this is amazing series, recommended for character development fans. Loved it to the last episode !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="97537">True Genshiken. Progressively stranger...</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://genshiken-2daime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7866" type="Character Design">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="3465" type="Series Composition">Yokote Michiko</name>
<name id="1508" type="Direction">Mizushima Tsutomu</name>
<name id="7866" type="Chief Animation Direction">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="5808" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kaiya Toshihisa</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="974" type="Original Work">Kio Shimoku</name>
<name id="36348" type="Music">Fukuhiro Shuuichirou</name>
</creators>
<description>Another college semester begins and the returning members of Genshiken attempt to recruit new club members. Three new members join the club, attracted by Ogiue`s BL drawings. She welcomes the new members but fears the club will become a "rotten girls" haven for yaoi fans and is getting a bit too far removed from its original purpose.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1199">6.60</permanent>
<temporary count="1205">7.26</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>236966.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15288</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18465</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>19889</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://genshiken-2daime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/genshiken-2daime/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nisamerica.com/genshiken-2nd-gen</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Genshiken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>げんしけん#.E3.81.92.E3.82.93.E3.81.97.E3.81.91.E3.82.93.E4.BA.8C.E4.BB.A3.E7.9B.AE</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3017</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345811</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16161</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2519" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="89">4.89</rating>
<name>Sasahara Kanji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The wishy-washy Sasahara Kanji is a freshman at Suioh University. He joins the Genshiken after a little persuasion from Kousaka Makoto and quickly engulfs himself in the otaku universe</description>
<picture>17825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16124" picture="45254.jpg">Kobashi Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2520" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="88">4.38</rating>
<name>Kousaka Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Makoto is an all-out otaku who joined Genshiken at the same time as Sasahara. He is a happy-go-lucky type who is mostly oblivious to the world around him.
Kousaka and his childhood friend Kasukabe both enroll at the university at the same time and become lovers shortly after the start of the story.</description>
<picture>17826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1437" picture="18823.jpg">Oohara Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2521" type="main character in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="165">8.29</rating>
<name>Madarame Harunobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Madarame often tries to play the role of a tough, military otaku but never quite manages to pull it off. Kasukabe often pick on him because of this.
When the original president resigns, Madarame takes over and thus become the second president in the history of Genshiken.</description>
<picture>17827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2522" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="58">5.70</rating>
<name>Tanaka Souichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tanaka is a master of cosplay. He can create any outfit in a week, often in less time if necessary but he never cosplays himself. At conventions he uses the alias Fukurou.
Later in the anime he starts going out with Kanaka Oono</description>
<picture>17828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="465" picture="56019.jpg">Kondou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2523" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="57">3.45</rating>
<name>Kugayama Mitsunori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kugayama is a stuttering, taciturn person. Initially he is the only person in Genshiken who can draw reasonably well but he usually never do more than rough sketches.</description>
<picture>17829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7108" type="main character in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="200">6.62</rating>
<name>Oono Kanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>American high school, joining the Genshiken at the beginning of the Fall term. Normally soft-spoken and easily embarrassed, Ohno is surprisingly upfront when it comes to one of her two main passions: cosplay. With a nice figure and large bosom, Ohno and her cosplaying (using costumes sewn personally by Tanaka, whom she begins dating) quickly become Genshiken`s main attraction at student fairs. Ohno`s other main passion is yaoi involving muscular, middle-aged, exceedingly bald men. One of the reasons Ohno joins Genshiken in the first place is because only they would accept her fetish. She is also close to Saki, as Saki was the first one to find out about Ohno`s preference for older men.</description>
<picture>138881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8963" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1976">8.57</rating>
<name>Senjougahara Hitagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hitagi, the main character of Hitagi Crab, is a weak-looking girl with an "incurable disease". She is in the same class as http://anidb.net/ch8962 [Koyomi], but he has almost never heard her speak.
When she was in the first year of high school, she encountered a mysterious crab, after which she became weightless. Ever since, she has avoided contact with everyone else, threatening everyone who discovers her secret. She called herself a tsundere and always speaks in an abusive style.</description>
<picture>31036.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19422" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="40">4.20</rating>
<name>Kasugano Haruka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55663.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19427" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="131">8.23</rating>
<name>Kasugano Sora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55662.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="33096" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-06">
<rating votes="38">3.02</rating>
<name>Kuchiki Manabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>6347.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34315" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="46">7.88</rating>
<name>Princess of the Crystal</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76992.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34669" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="5">6.90</rating>
<name>Penguin Ichigou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76997.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34670" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="8">8.90</rating>
<name>Penguin Nigou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76998.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34671" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="8">8.34</rating>
<name>Penguin Sangou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76999.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38621" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-12-29">
<rating votes="20">6.05</rating>
<name>Amou Kanade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1789.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="38624" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-07-25">
<rating votes="48">7.34</rating>
<name>Kazanari Tsubasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who has the power to use Symphogear armor, which uses music to fight off against aliens known as Noise. She was formally a part of a duo known as ZweiWing, but her partner, Kanade, sacrificed herself fighting the Noise and she has since been fighting the Noise alone. After the death of her partner Kanade, to whom she is rather attached with after witnessing Kanade`s urge to fight the noise, Tsubasa became quiet, cold and aloof. She is very reluctant to work with Hibiki, refusing to accept her as Kanade`s replacement, but she and Hibiki eventually get to be good friends. She is also a rather popular pop idol. Her first name means "Wing", while her family name means "Crying Wind".
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>137871.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55614" type="main character in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="17">5.60</rating>
<name>Yoshitake Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoshitake is a first year female student who decided to join Genshiken after seeing Ogiue`s poster drawing demonstration and sensing the fujoshi aspects of it and recognizing Ogiue as a fujoshi. She is slender, wears glasses, is bright and cheerful, but is also a bit manipulative as seen when she got everyone to cosplay, a feat even Oono could not accomplish. Yoshitake became one of Ogiue`s paid assistants when Ogiue needed help getting her professional manga ready by the deadline.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>137519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55615" type="main character in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="8">2.65</rating>
<name>Yajima Mirei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yajima is a first year female student who also decided to join Genshiken after seeing Ogiue`s manga poster drawing demonstration. She too is a fujoshi, though not as blatant about it as Yoshitake. She is of stocky build and tends to wear men`s clothing. She has a very hard time accepting Hato`s cross-dressing even though she knows the whole story behind it and routinely tells him to stop it. Yajima is also one of Ogiue`s paid assistants on Ogiue`s professional manga, doing the erasing of pencil lines and general page cleanup.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>137518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55616" type="main character in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="17">5.33</rating>
<name>Hato Kenjirou (Onna)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hato is a first year male student and the last to join during Ogiue`s first membership drive. Although he is heterosexual, Hato shares the fujoshi love of yaoi and boy`s love manga and doujinshi, making him a "fudanshi." Because of this, Hato decided to adopt a female persona, complete with a near perfect female voice, and only attends Genshiken meetings as a girl, though he attends classes as a guy. Even after the members of Genshiken learn his secret, Hato continues to cross-dress for the meetings, leading Genshiken to draft former member Madarame into letting Hato change at his apartment.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>137516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32939" picture="237666.jpg">Kakuma Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55617" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-18">
<rating votes="4">4.01</rating>
<name>Hato Kenjirou (Otoko)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hato is a first year male student and the last to join during Ogiue`s first membership drive. Although he is heterosexual, Hato shares the fujoshi love of yaoi and boy`s love manga and doujinshi, making him a "fudanshi." Because of this, Hato decided to adopt a female persona, complete with a near perfect female voice, and only attends Genshiken meetings as a girl, though he attends classes as a guy. Even after the members of Genshiken learn his secret, Hato continues to cross-dress for the meetings, leading Genshiken to draft former member Madarame into letting Hato change at his apartment.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>141657.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10380" picture="38227.jpg">Yamamoto Kazutomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55618" type="main character in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="12">7.28</rating>
<name>Ogiue Chika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fifth president of Genshiken and former member of the Manga Society, Ogiue is a girl who seemingly hates otaku, particularly female ones, but is arguably more perverse a yaoi fan than Oono. She managed to draw in three new members to Genshiken (not counting Sue) thanks to her large artwork demonstration. She has hired the four first-year club members to be her assistants for her professional manga work.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>137517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56010" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-01">
<rating votes="24">6.95</rating>
<name>Susanna Hopkins</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Susanna Hopkins is one of Oono`s friends from her time in America. She took a liking to Genshiken when she came to visit Japan, and now she`s finally studying abroad and joining as a member. Her nickname is Sue or Susie. She loves Japanese anime and manga, and often shouts lines from them. She`s taken a liking to Ogiue ever since seeing her doujinshi.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>138880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37280" picture="136935.jpg">Oozora Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56011" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-11">
<rating votes="14">6.13</rating>
<name>Kasukabe Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56014" type="appears in" update="2013-08-18">
<rating votes="3">4.00</rating>
<name>Angela Burton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141659.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36943" picture="223626.jpg">Kobayashi Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56482" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-18">
<rating votes="4">3.66</rating>
<name>Asada Naoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33648" picture="212610.jpg">Tada Konomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56483" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-05">
<rating votes="5">2.83</rating>
<name>Yabusaki Kumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the girls in the Manga Society at the time Ogiue attempted to join, she seems to harbor strong feelings of resentment towards Ogiue. Criticizing Ogiue for slipping into her Tohoku dialect when she doesn`t speak formally, Yabusaki herself speaks in a highly pronounced Kansai dialect, which she says scares those from Kantou. When Ogiue is rejected as a vendor for the next ComiFes, Yabusaki (grudgingly) invites her to become a guest artist in her own circle`s doujinshi. Though she appears only towards the end of the manga, she shows up much earlier in the anime, in episode 3 of season 2.</description>
<picture>153078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1961" picture="222838.jpg">Yonezawa Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56484" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-18">
<rating votes="14">4.40</rating>
<name>Sasahara Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9124" picture="186845.jpg">Hayama Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56485" type="appears in" update="2013-09-09">
<rating votes="3">7.26</rating>
<name>Kaminaga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58807" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<name>Yoshitake Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38417" picture="141691.jpg">Saotome Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59003" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<rating votes="1">3.90</rating>
<name>Danshi (Yajima no Doukyuusei)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31633" picture="165833.jpg">Nomiya Kazunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59008" type="appears in" update="2013-09-09">
<name>Harima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142723.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30309" picture="80361.jpg">Saitou Hironori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59009" type="appears in" update="2013-08-18">
<name>Nakajima Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32949" picture="243218.jpg">Hino Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59010" type="appears in" update="2013-08-18">
<name>Shigeta Mina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27898" picture="171568.jpg">Ogasawara Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59011" type="appears in" update="2013-08-18">
<name>Mikami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29971" picture="79257.jpg">Tamaru Hiroomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59012" type="appears in" update="2013-09-09">
<name>Kouhai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34070" picture="130103.jpg">Furukawa Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59013" type="appears in" update="2013-08-18">
<name>Mimasaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5605" picture="29786.jpg">Akutsu Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59585" type="appears in" update="2013-09-09">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Konno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9405" picture="228517.jpg">Yamaoka Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59586" type="appears in" update="2013-09-09">
<rating votes="2">3.13</rating>
<name>Fuji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142717.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59587" type="appears in" update="2013-09-09">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Sawatari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37986" picture="139351.jpg">Yuuki Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59588" type="appears in" update="2013-09-09">
<name>Hato Yuuichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60332" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<name>Katou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katou is a mysterious girl in the manga society, who always wears her hair over her face. At some point, she takes an interest in becoming friends with Ogiue, and sets out to do just that in spite of her fellow members` dislike of the girl. In reality, she is quite good looking, but few seem to know this because of the way she conceals her features.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32215" picture="223325.jpg">Sasamoto Natsue</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="151544" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">因果地平の彼方で, モエをさけぶ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shout "Moe!" Beyond the Event Horizon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inga Chihei no Kanata de, Moe o Sakebu</title>
<summary>The girls try to apologize to Madarame about what happened at Comic Festival. Yoshitake brings someone new to visit Genshiken, which leads to Yajima and Hato having an awkward day.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641843</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151545" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">業 NEXT!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go Next!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gou Next!</title>
<summary>Angela is interested in Madarame, but Hato thinks she`s being too aggressive. Hato meets Kousaka for the first time, and is forced to reveal his true feelings about Madarame.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641841</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151546" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HIGE TO BOIN</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beards and Boobs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hige to Boin</title>
<summary>Ogiue overworks herself to finish both of her manga projects in time. Hato-kun learns the difference between cross-dressing and cosplay. And at Comic Festival, a visitor from Ogiue`s past pays Genshiken`s booth a visit.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641839</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151547" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">腐り姫の夢[デイドリームビリーバー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Daydream Believer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daydream Believer</title>
<summary>Is it time for Hato x Mada? Or will it be Mada x Hato? Maybe Hato-kun just needs to have a long talk with herself about this.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641837</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151548" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の脚を越えてゆけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cross Over My Legs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Ashi o Koete Yuke</title>
<summary>Merei Yajima is struggling to accept Hato`s crossdressing. Hato is a guy, but he`s more attractive, nicer, and more talented than she is, and she feels inferior. Finally she makes a demand: That he stop wearing women`s clothes altogether.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641835</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151549" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">道の向こう, 約束の場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Other Side of the Path. The Promised Place.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michi no Mukou, Yakusoku no Basho</title>
<summary>The Shiiou University Society for the Study of Modern Visual Culture is also known as Genshiken. This comes from its Japanese name, the Gendai Shikaku Bunka Kenkyuukai.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>637185</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151673" update="2015-06-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151674" update="2015-06-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152483" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの部室で待ってる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Waiting in the Club Room</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Bushitsu de Matteru</title>
<summary>Why has Hato-kun stopped coming to Genshiken`s club meetings? Ogiue senses that he needs help, and looks into her own past to find the way.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641857</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152484" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホワイト ゲート キーパー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Gate Keeper</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">White Gate Keeper</title>
<summary>Ogiue does her best to help Hato learn how to drawn normal manga. The school`s culture festival begins, bringing with it many visitors from the past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641849</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152485" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルートはあってもループはない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s a Route, but There`s No Loop</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Route wa Atte mo Loop wa Nai</title>
<summary>Yoshitake despairs in the face of Ogiue and Hato`s talent. Hato has a long talk with Madarame about... H-games? Huh.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641847</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152486" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">KOIBANA3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">KOIBANA3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koibana 3</title>
<summary>Ogiue wants to publish a special edition of "Mebaetame" for the school festival. Genshiken`s members swap tales of their (incredibly depressing) high school romances.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641845</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152749" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋と仕事とチーズケーキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love, Work, and Cheesecake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi to Shigoto to Cheesecake</title>
<summary>Everyone tries to help Madarame cheer up after his grueling confession (for certain small values of "cheering up"). Ohno tries to figure out what will happen to her, and her cosplay, when she graduates.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641855</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152750" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いい最終回だった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Was a Good Last Episode</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ii Saishuukai Datta</title>
<summary>Kasukabe arrives, forcing everyone out of their comfort zones. She agrees to meet Madarame in the Genshiken club room, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641853</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152751" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">snow man</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Snow Man</title>
<summary>Hato`s old crush Kaminaga sees his art, and wants an explanation. Madarame is sent out to spy, but he`s unmovable, until...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641851</identifier>
<identifier>genshiken-second-season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155222" update="2013-10-22">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155223" update="2013-10-22">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155224" update="2015-06-14">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155225" update="2015-05-16">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第一回 こんなに可愛い子が女の子のはずがない件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiikkai: Konna ni Kawaii Ko ga Onnanoko no Hazu ga Nai Ken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155236" update="2013-10-23">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第一回 スーさんがなんか強い件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiikkai: Sue-san ga Nanka Tsuyoi Ken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155237" update="2013-10-23">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155238" update="2013-10-23">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155239" update="2013-10-23">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155984" update="2013-11-14">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第一回 波戸ちゃんがつるつるな件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiikkai: Hato-chan ga Tsurutsuru na Ken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155985" update="2013-11-14">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155986" update="2013-11-14">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155987" update="2013-11-14">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157115" update="2015-06-11">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2013-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第一回 そろそろ斑目総受けは飽きた会議</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiikkai: Sorosoro Madarame Sou Uke wa Akita Kaigi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157116" update="2014-01-07">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1m</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157117" update="2014-01-07">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1l</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157118" update="2014-01-07">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1k</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157119" update="2014-01-07">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1j</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
