<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9687" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-09-07</startdate>
<enddate>2013-09-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Space Pirate Captain Harlock</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">SPACE PIRATE CAPTAIN HARLOCK</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Harlock: Space Pirate</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Space Pirate Captain Harlock</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Albator Corsaire de l`Espace</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Космический пират Харлок</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Capitão Harlock: Pirata do Espaço</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Capitão Harlock: Pirata do Espaço</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Căpitanul Harlock: Pirat Spațial</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="725" type="Alternative Setting">Uchuu Kaizoku Captain Harlock</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="314076">Good sci-fi movie with a dark atmosphere. CGI &amp; animation wise, it is the best 3D anime I`ve seen (yes, latter can be much worse).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="376057">Visually stunning. Great CGI and that it. Must say, for all ppl who watch old series, this is a big miss. And for the new fans please don`t start with this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="159758">Different from canonical Harlock, but still good. Changed personalities. Yattaran, old good Yattaran, what they do to you...  But immortal hero? My ass =</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="35309">Very good to whom never seen nothing of captain Harlock and for who not know him. But whom already seen the series and know who is/what is, maybe will be a bit disappointing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="600311">Amazing!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="257572">This was my first touch with Harlock`s universe, so the story was a little bit rushed for me but overall it was a good watch. It`s a must see because of CG. Visually stunning!!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://harlock-movie.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1834" type="Animation Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="1107" type="Original Work">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
<name id="150" type="Direction">Aramaki Shinji</name>
<name id="4642" type="Music">Takahashi Tetsuya</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="881">6.14</permanent>
<temporary count="884">7.07</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>154201.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15170</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17269</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://harlock-movie.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Space_Pirate_Captain_Harlock_(film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>キャプテンハーロック_-SPACE_PIRATE_CAPTAIN_HARLOCK-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345374</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16531</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1700" parentid="2872" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>pirate</name>
<description>Pirates are people who attack ships on the high seas to rob others of their treasure. Well, at least usually. Other people calling themselves pirates are not unheard of, usually focusing on the freedom and romance involved in the piracy-related tropes and cliches. They may or may not be after the One Piece or a spaceship full of diamonds, too, if that`s what they see as treasure. Real-life pirates were extremely common a few centuries ago, and countries even sponsored their own pirates, called "privateers", to attack ships with flags of other countries. Nowadays, however, very few actual pirates still exist, and they rely more on terrorism and guerrilla warfare than anything else, demanding ransom in exchange for hostages instead of openly attacking the enemies with their swords. Another, more modern meaning for the word refers to people who illegally download copyrighted works they are not entitled to have a copy of. Be whichever it may, there are pirates around here. Arr, avast! Thar be pirates in these dark waters, matey!</description>
<picurl>126791.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3309" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-12">
<name>space pirates</name>
<description>Depending how you view the future, lawlessness will always be present in society. There`s always going to be a shadier, nastier way of doing business, and that will almost certainly follow humanity to the stars. Thus, sci-fi authors will include Expies of modern and historic (un)organized crime—be they space mafia, gangs, or—in our case—pirates.
It`s not as anachronistic as it might seem. After all, pirates themselves have made a Real Life comeback in Somalia, and it`s a lucrative enough "business" that it`s taken a multinational military response to fight back. Surely an established society in outer space with significant trade and commerce would suffer similar problems!
... Well, maybe. The major problem with space pirates preying on space commerce is that space is vast. The challenge of catching commercial shipping in open space is orders of magnitudes more difficult than catching them on the open seas. Sometimes, this is cleverly worked around and justified. Most of the time, however, it isn`t.
There are two kinds of Space Pirates in science fiction. The normal version are violent criminals with a spaceship, who attack other spaceships, just like present-day pirates. Once you have shipping between different solar systems/planets, pirates preying on said shipping are bound to show. Simple as that. Done this way, piracy actually makes sense, provided there`s an enabling factor. That could be anything from the technology of the setting creating trade lanes (via a Portal Network, predictable Faster Than Light Travel routes thanks to Negative Space Wedgies, or timed space flights between planets to reduce time spent between planets, as in Real Life), to using a variant of the method employed by modern pirates (say, smaller ships striking at commercial shipping in the orbit of a planet).
The other version does a Recycled In SPACE on every eighteenth century pirate cliche ever. Reasons for including this version will typically be along the lines of "Because Space Is An Ocean, it has to have Pirates" rather than making any meaningful attempt at justifying their existence. They have Cornish accents, beards, say "Arr!" a lot, have parrots (probably robot) and false limbs (probably cybernetic) and wear tricorn hats and eyepatches (or have cybernetic eyes). They may even have ships shaped like boats.
One of the best known space pirates is http://anidb.net/ch2087 [Captain Harlock] from the same named popular http://anidb.net/a725 [TV anime series].
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>41919.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4465" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>stereoscopic imaging</name>
<description>This anime was shown in cinema rooms with stereoscopic 3D capabilities, released on Blu-ray 3D, or available for other stereoscopic 3D capable devices like the Nintendo 3DS or the Sharp AQUOS "NERV Edition" SH-06D smartphone. It was either produced in stereo 3D (e.g. "Baby Princess 3D Paradise Love") or produced in 2D and later converted from 2D to 3D (e.g. "Koukaku Kidoutai Stand Alone Complex: Solid State Society"). At any rate, it was at some point officially available with stereoscopic 3D depth effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="60823" type="main character in" update="2013-10-27">
<rating votes="9">8.10</rating>
<name>Captain Harlock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1984" picture="21284.jpg">Oguri Shun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60824" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-27">
<rating votes="6">5.37</rating>
<name>Yama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38661" picture="144879.jpg">Miura Haruma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60825" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-27">
<rating votes="7">6.81</rating>
<name>Miime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9703" picture="36416.jpg">Aoi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60826" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-27">
<rating votes="8">5.56</rating>
<name>Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144883.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69632" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-24">
<rating votes="3">2.93</rating>
<name>Nami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69633" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-24">
<rating votes="3">6.21</rating>
<name>Tori-san</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38660" picture="144878.jpg">Fukuda Ayano</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69870" type="appears in" update="2014-09-07">
<rating votes="4">8.37</rating>
<name>Arcadia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>160557.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69871" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-07">
<rating votes="3">2.16</rating>
<name>Isora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69874" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-07">
<rating votes="3">5.93</rating>
<name>Yattaran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harlock`s first mate on the Arcadia, he is usually portrayed as comic relief in the series, but when a battle against alien threats become imminent he will be at the captain`s side. He is also a brilliant mathematician and has a major interest in building plastic model kits of ships (he was even seen building a scale model of the Arcadia in one episode). Yattaran is based on manga artist Shintani Kaoru (best known for Area 88) who, in his early career worked for Matsumoto building models for reference.</description>
<picture>160560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36066" picture="220265.jpg">Furuta Arata</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="147833" update="2013-03-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152600" update="2013-08-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2013-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
