<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="97" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-09-24</startdate>
<enddate>2000-10-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sol Bianca: Taiyou no Fune</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">太陽の船 ソルビアンカ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">太陽の船ソルビアンカ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Taiyou no Fune Sol Bianca</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Bianca</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Sol Bianca ~太陽の船~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sol Bianca: The Legacy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Sol Bianca - The Legacy</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Sol Bianca L`eredità Perduta</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Sol Bianca: Сокровища погибших планет</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1350" type="Alternative Setting">Sol Bianca</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.anime-int.com/works/solbianca/ova2/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2163" type="Character Design">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="732" type="Work">AIC</name>
<name id="1905" type="Music">Nagaoka Seikou</name>
<name id="4503" type="Direction">Ochi Hiroyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Can five young women take on the armed might of an entire solar system and win? If they are the treasure-hungry crew of the interstellar pirate ship Sol Bianca, the odds are just about even.
Outfitted with a dazzling array of power armour, energy whips and the artificially intelligent, dimension-warping Sol Bianca herself, this quintet of larcenous ladies gives no quarter in their non-stop onslaught against a ruthless dictator who has the misfortune to possess a priceless treasure coveted by the buccaneering battle maids. The liberation of an entire civilization, and the obliteration of a few dozen cities are purely incidental, as http://anidb.net/ch30759 [Janny], http://anidb.net/ch30757 [Feb], http://anidb.net/ch30758 [April], http://anidb.net/ch30761 [May] and http://anidb.net/ch30760 [June] cut a starship sized swath of destruction towards the object of their money-grubbing hearts` desire.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="514">4.52</permanent>
<temporary count="522">6.47</temporary>
<review count="1">8.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>223966.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1444</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>383</identifier>
<identifier>ajnzwk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20130605112930/http://www.anime-int.com/works/solbianca/ova2/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sol_Bianca:_The_Legacy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>太陽の船_ソルビアンカ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2601</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>90380</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3189</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7051</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3309" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-12">
<name>space pirates</name>
<description>Depending how you view the future, lawlessness will always be present in society. There`s always going to be a shadier, nastier way of doing business, and that will almost certainly follow humanity to the stars. Thus, sci-fi authors will include Expies of modern and historic (un)organized crime—be they space mafia, gangs, or—in our case—pirates.
It`s not as anachronistic as it might seem. After all, pirates themselves have made a Real Life comeback in Somalia, and it`s a lucrative enough "business" that it`s taken a multinational military response to fight back. Surely an established society in outer space with significant trade and commerce would suffer similar problems!
... Well, maybe. The major problem with space pirates preying on space commerce is that space is vast. The challenge of catching commercial shipping in open space is orders of magnitudes more difficult than catching them on the open seas. Sometimes, this is cleverly worked around and justified. Most of the time, however, it isn`t.
There are two kinds of Space Pirates in science fiction. The normal version are violent criminals with a spaceship, who attack other spaceships, just like present-day pirates. Once you have shipping between different solar systems/planets, pirates preying on said shipping are bound to show. Simple as that. Done this way, piracy actually makes sense, provided there`s an enabling factor. That could be anything from the technology of the setting creating trade lanes (via a Portal Network, predictable Faster Than Light Travel routes thanks to Negative Space Wedgies, or timed space flights between planets to reduce time spent between planets, as in Real Life), to using a variant of the method employed by modern pirates (say, smaller ships striking at commercial shipping in the orbit of a planet).
The other version does a Recycled In SPACE on every eighteenth century pirate cliche ever. Reasons for including this version will typically be along the lines of "Because Space Is An Ocean, it has to have Pirates" rather than making any meaningful attempt at justifying their existence. They have Cornish accents, beards, say "Arr!" a lot, have parrots (probably robot) and false limbs (probably cybernetic) and wear tricorn hats and eyepatches (or have cybernetic eyes). They may even have ships shaped like boats.
One of the best known space pirates is http://anidb.net/ch2087 [Captain Harlock] from the same named popular http://anidb.net/a725 [TV anime series].
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>41919.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4136" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-03-05">
<name>sudden loli companion appearance</name>
<description>The main character meets a preadolescent girl in an unexpected way becoming a friend / partner of the main character.
(The term loli is short for Lolita meaning a girl in preadolescent age. Typical attributes are moe, cute, and innocent.)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4459" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-22">
<name>undefeatable spaceship</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30757" type="main character in" update="2011-04-03">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Feb</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30758" type="main character in" update="2011-04-03">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>April</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30759" type="main character in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Janny</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3062" picture="170303.jpg">Saeki Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30760" type="main character in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>June</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4428" picture="26693.jpg">Miyajima Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30761" type="main character in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>May</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4037" picture="174276.jpg">Konishi Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="6369" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1999-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">EL EMBLEMA ~紋章~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">El Emblema: The Emblem</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`emblème</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">El Emblema: Monshou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6370" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2000-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">LA TIERRA ~地球~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">La Tierra: Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Terre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">La Tierra: Chikyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6371" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2000-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">LA MOVREX ~恋人たち~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">La Movrex: Lovers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`amoureux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">La Movrex: Koibito-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6372" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2000-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">EL ARREGLO ~掃除人~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">El Arreglo: The Cleaner</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Règlement de compte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">El Arreglo: Soujinin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6373" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1999-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">LA REMINISCENCIA ~記憶~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">La Reminiscencia: Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Réminiscence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">La Reminiscencia: Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6374" update="2018-11-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2000-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BARCO DEL SOL ~太陽の船~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Barco Del Sol: The Ship Of The Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le vaisseau solaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Barco Del Sol: Taiyou no Fune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90475" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121089" update="2018-11-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1999-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
