<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9717" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-09-16</startdate>
<enddate>2013-12-09</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Diabolik Lovers</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Влюбените демони</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">DIABOLIK LOVERS</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Diabolik Lovers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Diabolik Lovers</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">魔鬼恋人</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11068" type="Sequel">Diabolik Lovers More, Blood</anime>
<anime id="11491" type="Side Story">Diabolik Lovers (2015)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9436" approval="3" total="4">Brothers Conflict</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="230760">If you like to see abusive but good looking men, a 100% submissively heroine and a almost not existing story - this is for you ;-)

The charakter design is promising but unfortunately that`s all there is.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="741160">Well i recomended for the people who actually played the games, and mostly is for fanservices purpose, or if you like the sxm relationships, it only have story in the first maybe two episodes than until like the ten episode, the other is how the boys are and sucking her blood</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://anime-dialover.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="788" type="Animation Work">Zexcs</name>
<name id="13979" type="Character Design">Yahiro Yuuko</name>
<name id="15587" type="Series Composition">Nagatsu Haruko</name>
<name id="24131" type="Original Work">Otomate</name>
<name id="6734" type="Direction">Tagashira Shinobu</name>
<name id="27786" type="Music">Hayashi Yuuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a visual novel of the same name by Rejet and Otomate, for the female market.
http://anidb.net/ch57971 [Komori Yui] is a positive-thinking girl who nevertheless is troubled by seeing spirits and experiencing poltergeist phenomena. In her second year in high school, she transfers to a new school — a night school for entertainers and celebrities — due to her father`s work. There are rumours that vampires exist among the student body, and Yui ends up living with the six sadistic Sakamaki vampire brothers.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="690">1.72</permanent>
<temporary count="710">4.33</temporary>
<review count="1">2.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>139745.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15150</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20919</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17513</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://anime-dialover.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Diabolik_Lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>DIABOLIK_LOVERS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3145</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>346649</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16471</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9846</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="56898" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-19">
<rating votes="15">5.43</rating>
<name>Sakamaki Ayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12784" picture="171452.jpg">Ushida Hiroko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56899" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-19">
<rating votes="16">2.29</rating>
<name>Sakamaki Kanato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56900" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-19">
<rating votes="12">5.32</rating>
<name>Sakamaki Laito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="137" picture="214428.jpg">Sasamoto Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56901" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-19">
<rating votes="11">5.36</rating>
<name>Sakamaki Shuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4860" picture="211311.jpg">Sasajima Kaoru</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56902" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-19">
<rating votes="10">5.36</rating>
<name>Sakamaki Reiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11153" picture="188722.jpg">Nishigaki Yuka</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56903" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-19">
<rating votes="10">5.06</rating>
<name>Sakamaki Subaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57971" type="main character in" update="2014-01-09">
<rating votes="16">3.35</rating>
<name>Komori Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140183.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38248" picture="140190.jpg">Suegara Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62347" type="appears in" update="2013-12-14">
<rating votes="3">5.47</rating>
<name>Richter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61370.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4741" picture="45560.jpg">Konno Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62348" type="appears in" update="2013-12-14">
<rating votes="5">3.05</rating>
<name>Cordelia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61371.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2011" picture="233461.jpg">Tomonaga Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62349" type="appears in" update="2013-12-14">
<rating votes="4">2.28</rating>
<name>Beatrix</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61372.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="154075" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<summary>Yui asks the triplets about the woman in the purple dress who she spotted in the garden, and learns the grusome truth about what befell their mother. Yui runs out of the house in horror and collapses sobbing in the garden, only to be approached by Subaru, who demands she keep her distance from him, or else. Yui spends a sleepless night in her chamber, made less restful by the arrival of an unwanted guest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644169</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154076" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<summary>A mysterious woman gives Yui a chance to look into the past, when Ayato and his brothers were young boys.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644167</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154077" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<summary>Yui refuses to accept that she should suddenly stop showing compassion towards her fellow man merely because they are vampires, and allows herself to be led to one of Kanato`s most favorite places in his little world. As she views his family`s collection of wax figures all in bridal wear, she finds herself eerily aware that things are not as benign as they appear. Kanato confirms her suspicions and gleefully sets to adding her to their collection, until he is interrupted by a summons.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644163</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154078" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<summary>Kanato finds Yui in the rose garden as she tries to sort out the new information about who betrayed her and gave her up as a sacrifice. 
He beckons her to follow him so he may show off a graveyard containing the grave of his mother. 
Assuming he would like some time alone, Yui attempts to leave which only infuriates Kanato with misplaced anger. 
Reeling from this experience, Yui wanders through the estate, and becomes worried when she hears groans coming from Reiji`s room. 
Much to her folly, she enters the room to see if he needs help
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644161</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154079" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<summary>Yui accidentally displeases teddy bear-holding Kanato by incorrectly guessing what he wants from her, and he punishes her for her lack of comprehension skills by displacing her school bag, which in turn causes her to displease Raito by being in the wrong place at the wrong time. Raito proceeds to punish her using decidedly less childish methods, and mocks her for believing in something that can`t physically save her from the evil that is him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644159</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154080" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<summary>Life with the six brothers becomes even stranger as Yui loses her appetite and becomes `marked` as Ayato`s possession. She is temporarily released from her duties as his personal plaything and sippy cup so she may get bathed. She enters the enormous bathroom to draw a bath for herself only to find Shu listlessly soaking in it, fully clothed. Then she learns to her sorrow that she doesn`t have a single ally in the entire household.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644157</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154081" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<summary>Yui awakens in a lovely bed wearing a lovely nightgown, with no memory of how she came to be there dressed that way. As she ponders this, she finds herself suddenly surrounded by the five younger brothers who start to argue over dibs on her. The eldest arrives and curtly informs her she must get ready for night school. She is instructed to behave herself or to face punishment, but she is confused as to what being behaved entails as she is compelled to submit to Ayato`s every whim instead of attending class.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644155</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154082" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<summary>A girl finds herself in a house full of bloodthirsty vampires. Unable to escape and with traditional anti-vampire weapons being useless, she becomes lost within the labyrinth of hallways.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644153</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155334" recap="true" update="2013-10-30">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6.5</title>
<summary>This is a recap of the 1st 6 episodes.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644165</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155366" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<summary>Cordelia flaunts her reanimation amongst the members of the Sakamaki household, who immediately want her and her lover, Richter, out of their home, once and for all.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644175</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155367" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<summary>Cordelia and Richter savor one another`s company for the first time in ages, until Ayato interrupts, demanding to know what they have done to Yui.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644173</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155368" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<summary>Yui experiences more chest pains and leaves the mansion in the middle of the night to seek answers from Shu. At first, he is unhelpful but quickly becomes interested in obliging her request for answers by forcibly tasting her blood to verify that it has indeed changed somehow. As she finally gets an answer to the question most prominent on her mind, whether or not her father knowingly sacrificed his daughter to these monsters, that answer becomes irrelevant in so many ways as the awakening is nigh.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644171</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156630" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<summary>The struggle between Yui and Cordelia for control over the body comes to a head. The boys hatch a plan to get rid of Cordelia for good.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>646501</identifier>
<identifier>diabolik-lovers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184629" update="2017-02-16">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="184630" update="2017-02-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
