<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9723" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-08-25</startdate>
<enddate>2009-08-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">30th Gundam Perfect Mission</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">30th GUNDAM PERFECT MISSION</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="715" type="Other">Kidou Senshi Gundam</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7454" approval="2" total="2">All That Gundam</anime>
</similaranime>
<creators>
<name id="726" type="Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="1531" type="Direction">Yonetani Yoshitomo</name>
</creators>
<description>* A short promotional video released in celebration of the 30th anniversary of the Gundam series. It was included on Gundam OP/ED Collection 20th and 21st Century song collection DVDs.
An FF-X7 is guided into orbit with the assistance of every main protagonist Gundam for the first thirty years of the franchise`s history.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="204">3.93</permanent>
<temporary count="206">5.54</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>134182.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15758</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7113</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>GUNDAM_PERFECT_MISSION</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4542" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-25">
<name>no dialogue</name>
<description>The anime either has no spoken dialogue or no dialogue at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1489" type="appears in" update="2011-11-30">
<rating votes="41">8.99</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X10A Freedom Gundam</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The ZGMF-X10A Freedom Gundam is one of the new Gundam designs built by ZAFT. The Freedom Gundam is equipped with a wide variety of powerful weapons for use in its HiMAT (High Mobility Aerial Tactics) mode. One of these weapons is the twin "Balaena" plasma beam cannons, which are stored in the wings and mounted over the shoulders during use. The Freedom Gundam`s other main armament consists of twin hip-mounted "Xiphias" rail cannons. Other standard armaments include head vulcans, twin beam sabers and a beam rifle. The Freedom Gundam is also capable of using something far more powerful: the METEOR support system. This mobile weapons platform is designed specifically for use by the Freedom Gundam and ZGMF-X09A Justice Gundam and is stored aboard the support ship Eternal. By using the METEOR, the Freedom Gundam can deliver a blitzkrieg attack utilizing various cannons, missile launchers and two long beam swords.
The Freedom Gundam is first used in May C.E. 71 when Kira Yamato steals it with the help of Lacus Clyne. Kira uses his new suit to travel to Earth and join the battle between ZAFT and the Alliance at Alaska. Following the battle, Kira rejoins his comrades on the Archangel and travels to Orb after Murrue Ramius decides to defect from the Alliance. There, Kira fights to protect Orb from the Alliance and is later joined by his old friend and former enemy Athrun Zala piloting his new ZGMF-X09A Justice Gundam. Following the defeat of Orb, Kira returns to space and is joined by Lacus Clyne and her stolen support ship Eternal, which provides Kira with his METEOR support system. Along with Athrun, Kira uses his METEOR to save the PLANTs from destruction by nuclear missiles. At the war`s end on September 27, the Freedom Gundam is heavily damaged in a battle against Rau Le Creuset`s ZGMF-X13A Providence Gundam. After the war, the Freedom Gundam is secretly repaired and hidden in Orb. In late C.E. 73, the Freedom Gundam is reactivated by Kira to fight off a squad of UMF/SS0-3 ASH mobile suits used by a group of special ops Coordinators sent to assassinate Lacus. In early C.E. 74, PLANT Supreme Council Chairman Gilbert Durandal orders the destruction of the Archangel and Freedom Gundam after their interference in several battles between the Alliance and ZAFT. Soon after, ZAFT then initiates "Operation Angel Down," and during that battle the Freedom Gundam is destroyed by Shinn Asuka`s ZGMF-X56S Impulse Gundam.</description>
<picture>77823.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1726" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>F91 Gundam F91</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This prototype machine, created by the military research institute SNRI, is the latest product of the Federation Forces` miniaturized mobile suit development program. The F91`s capabilities exceed those of any contemporary mobile suit, but its full potential can only be expressed with a Newtype pilot at the controls. In its high-performance mode, the F91`s face mask opens to help cool the bio-computer installed in its head, ventilator fins are deployed from its shoulders, and it can dissipate excess heat via the Metal Peel-off Effect. Thanks to its high generator output the F91 can drive multiple beam weapons, including a beam rifle, a beam shield, and a pair of powerful Variable-Speed Beam Rifle (VSBR) units.
Another new technology incorporated in the Gundam F91 was the bio-computer system developed by Doctor Monica Arno. This system acted as a sort of "reversed" psycommu system, relaying information directly to the pilot`s mind rather than vice versa. The bio-computer, however, could be used by normal pilots, and it gave the pilot many advantages by directly providing him with tactical and sensor data, piloting suggestions, and so on. Thus, the bio-computer allowed the pilot to react more quickly and decisively to any battle situation, and it also made a novice pilot`s job easier in terms of adapting to the new mobile suit.
The F91 prototype, originally manufactured by SNRI in UC 0116, was slowly upgraded and modified over the next several years. Its final assembly, which incorporated the bio-computer system, was cut short when the Crossbone Vanguard force began conquering the Frontier Side area in March UC 0123. The F91`s parts were stowed aboard the Federation Forces` training ship Space Ark, and during an escape to the Frontier I colony, the Space Ark crew rescued a group of civilian students who were also fleeing. Since the ship`s complement was made up of trainees - and a skeleton crew, at that - a pilot was needed to pilot the F91 when it was completed. Seabook Arno, one of the rescued civilians, was selected for the job, based on his rather shaky credentials of being an engineering student and the son of bio-computer engineer Doctor Arno. Although reluctant to become a soldier, Seabook soon found himself performing his duties well, adapting to the F91 easily and scoring three enemy MS kills on his first sortie.
The Gundam F91 would perform superbly during the conflict, and its abilities would soon have another surprise in store for Seabook. Being a very high-performance unit, the F91`s weapons and systems generated a tremendous amount of heat. This heat was normally dissipated through a seat of radiator fins built into the mobile suit`s shoulders; however, excessive amounts of heat would sometimes still remain throughout the mobile suit`s body. Another method of getting rid of this heat was by "shedding" the heated outermost layer of the Gundam`s armour; this had the rather dramatic effect of creating "after-images" of the mobile suit while it was moving. While confronting Crossbone Vanguard leader Carozzo Ronah`s deadly XMA-01 Rafflesia mobile armor, Seabook would find this ability useful in tricking his enemy into attacking targets that were not where they appeared to be.</description>
<picture>16295.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2556" type="appears in" update="2009-01-19">
<name>RX-78NT-1 Gundam NT1 Alex</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The RX-78NT1 is the fourth Gundam unit created by the Federation Forces during the One Year War. Redesigned for use by ace pilot Amuro Ray, whose success in battle was seen as evidence of his Newtype powers, this Gundam was given the designation "NT1." Unlike Zeon`s Newtype weapons, the Gundam NT1 doesn`t have a psycommu interface; instead, its designers concentrated on making it highly responsive and maneuverable. Its special features include magnet-coated joints for increased responsiveness, a new type of panoramic cockpit display, and pop-up gatling guns in its forearms. The Gundam NT1 can also be fitted with optional Chobham armor for extra protection, increasing its overall weight to a massive 95 tons.</description>
<picture>17884.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6690" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">9.23</rating>
<name>MSZ-006 Zeta Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This machine is the culmination of the AEUG`s secret "Zeta Project," whose goal was to create a transformable mobile suit capable of operating in every environment from weightless space to Earth`s gravity. By transforming into a streamlined Wave Rider form, the Zeta Gundam can ride the shockwaves of atmospheric re-entry and then cruise through Earth`s atmosphere. As a mobile suit, it combines the movable frame technology of the Gundam Mk.II with the lightweight Gundarium Gamma alloy of the Rick Dias, not to mention an extraordinary level of firepower. In the hands of the young Newtype pilot Kamille Bidan, one of its principal designers, the Zeta Gundam proves to be the most powerful weapon in the rebels` arsenal.</description>
<picture>24478.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6691" type="appears in" update="2015-02-08">
<name>MSZ-006 Zeta Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This machine is the culmination of the AEUG`s secret "Zeta Project," whose goal was to create a transformable mobile suit capable of operating in every environment from weightless space to Earth`s gravity. By transforming into a streamlined Wave Rider form, the Zeta Gundam can ride the shockwaves of atmospheric re-entry and then cruise through Earth`s atmosphere. As a mobile suit, it combines the movable frame technology of the Gundam Mk.II with the lightweight Gundarium Gamma alloy of the Rick Dias, not to mention an extraordinary level of firepower. In the hands of the young Newtype pilot Kamille Bidan, one of its principal designers, the Zeta Gundam proves to be the most powerful weapon in the rebels` arsenal.</description>
<picture>24479.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8577" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="12">6.53</rating>
<name>GN-0000 00 Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The successor unit to the GN-001 Gundam Exia and since its name is "00" that could possibly mean this Gundam is also the successor of the 0 Gundam. As the premier unit in Celestial Being`s 4th Generation of Mobile Suits, "00" (pronounced Double-O) possesses many of the previous generations` standard features, including the GN Drive and Trans-AM System, as well as introducing newer innovation such as the revolutionary Twin Drive System. The system utilizes two GN Drives with compatible GN particles production as the basis for the system`s operation, with their productive synergy generating GN particle emissions which exceed anything produced by a single unit.
The 00 Gundam`s arsenal consists of a small assortment of weapons, including GN Beam Sabers and GN Sword II`s--a refinement to the GN-001 Gundam Exia`s existing Seven Sword technology: in particular, the GN Long &amp; Short Blades. Drawing inspiration from the GN Sword, this weapon incorporates a beam rifle configuration to the melee-oriented GN Blade function giving it much needed projectile-fire capability, along with the traditional hand-held approach for more overall versatility. The GN-Sword II firepower is powerful enough to take out an Ahead mobile suit in one shot.
A tactical drawback of the Twin Drive System is the way the GN Drives are mounted upon 00`s shoulders. They aren`t shielded and depend on the pilot`s capabilities to compensate 00`s weaknesses/deficiencies. Should 00 Gundam lose a GN Drive in combat, it can still operate, but have difficulty of executing higher functions because the unit has high GN particle requirements.</description>
<picture>27779.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8579" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="11">8.07</rating>
<name>GN-0000+GNR-010 00 Raiser</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Because 00 is a experimental MS, the unit also suffers from power stability issues and requires constant maintenance. 00`s Twin Drive System was imperfect and requires 0 Raiser (00 Raiser) to safely execute Trans-Am and provide protection upon the GN Drives. 00 Raiser became the mainstay form of 00 Gundam to effectively combat A-Laws and Innovators enemy mobile units. As 00 Raiser, the unit has greater GN particle generation and the use of the Raiser System.
The Raiser System allows 00 Raiser to execute powerful attacks such as a mega beam saber called Raiser Sword, hyper vector close range combat, and utilize Trans-Am with greater power and duration. 00 Raiser originally needed both its GN Swords to produce Raiser Sword, but was later upgraded with GN Sword III. The new sword was able to utilize the power of the Raiser System to generate a refined Raiser Sword. The power of 00 Raiser is further enhanced with the neural interface of an Innovator pilot. The Innovator pilot can execute Trans-Am Burst, which results in a massive burst of GN particles within a large area of space. Overall, 00 Raiser is a Gundam that exceeds in performance to all mobile suits.
00 Gundam can combine with GNR-010 0 Raiser to become 00 Raiser, the binders detach and combine onto 00`s GN Drive shoulder mounts and it`s main body combines with back of 00 Gundam, giving it an mechanical/angelical-like form. Its primary function is to stabilize the operation of the Twin Drive System and Trans-Am System, allowing the 00 to effectively harness its massive particle production (which is too much for the 00`s frame alone) and utilize its full potential. With the constant need for 00 Gundam`s full capabilities, 00 Raiser became the mainstay form in combat. In its 00 Raiser form, 00 can generate 300%+ GN particle efficiency.
00 XN Raiser is the combination of a variant version of 0 Raiser and 00 Gundam. The docking system and appearance is similar, however there are notable differences. In flight mode, XN Raiser has the appearance of a X-Wing-like configuration. XN Raiser carries a pair of GN Buster Sword IIIs and have a series of extended wing-fins for aerodynamic flight. The GN Buster Sword IIIs act as a second pair of wings while in flight. XN Raiser`s binders doesn`t dock into 00`s twin GN Drives, they instead fold up during docking mode. The entire system docks onto 00 Gundam`s back as a weapons backpack.</description>
<picture>27781.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10986" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="9">8.30</rating>
<name>RX-78-2 Gundam</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Gundam is one of three prototype mobile suits secretly developed by the embattled Earth Federation. After suffering tremendous losses to Zeon`s mobile suits earlier in the war, the Federation set out to create its own, using the very latest advanced technology. The Gundam is the most successful of these prototypes, a close-combat mobile suit protected by tough Luna Titanium armour, and armed with both lethal beam sabers and a devastating beam rifle as powerful as a battleship cannon. It`s also equipped with an advanced computer which learns from its pilot, ultimately enabling it to operate the Gundam automatically. In the hands of accidental pilot Amuro Ray, this one prototype mobile suit proves to be the equal of any Zeon weapon.</description>
<picture>32757.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10992" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="5">1.80</rating>
<name>FF-X7 Core Fighter</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This tiny aerospace fighter doubles as a cockpit for the Earth Federation`s Gundam, Guncannon, and Guntank mobile suits. Thanks to the Core Block system used in these prototype mobile suits, the cockpit module can eject and unfold into a fighter plane, allowing the pilot and vital test data to escape to safety. While it`s armed with four vulcan guns and a pair of missile launchers, only a truly reckless pilot would deliberately take a Core Fighter into battle.</description>
<picture>32763.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11027" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">7.82</rating>
<name>SCV-70 White Base</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>This Pegasus-class mobile assault carrier, the besieged home of our crew of young heroes, is the first Earth Federation warship designed to carry mobile suits into battle. Its decks can hold up to nine mobile suits and fighters, and its armament includes a main gun turret, two mega particle cannons, a battery of missile launchers, and countless anti-aircraft guns. Thanks to its Minovsky craft system, the White Base can survive the heat of atmospheric re-entry, and then float effortlessly across the surface of the Earth. The soldiers of the Principality of Zeon, unaware of its true name, give the White Base the nickname "Trojan Horse."</description>
<picture>32840.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12682" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<rating votes="3">3.52</rating>
<name>WD-M01 Turn A Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The WD-M01 Turn A Gundam is a mecha from the Correct Century (正暦 Seireki) calendar system in the anime Turn A Gundam. It is mainly piloted by the hero of the series, and acted as the symbol of the earth militia forces against the superior moonrace.
∀ Gundam is designed by Syd Mead, for the series Turn A Gundam. The original design of the mecha was rejected by Yoshiyuki Tomino due to its exotic appearance and Tomino decided that he wanted a figure that is closer to the previous Gundam designs. The old design was renamed and used for the Mobile Suit Sumo instead. The design is still exotic to Gundam anime fans, however, Syd Mead designed ∀ Gundam using real world industrial design aspects, which was aimed to make it look simple and realistic. The shield was designed by Syd Mead with little constraint form the production team, it needs to be big enough so that the suit can hide behind it, making it easier for the anime production staff to draw. Syd Mead imagined it to be like a clam shell and finally settled with a design that looked like MS-14 Gelgoog`s shield.
The System-∀99 (WD-M01) ∀ Gundam (also known as "Turn A") first appeared in the show when the Moonrace`s Diana Counter army arrived on Earth and attacked the city of Nocis; which at the time was holding a Coming of Age ceremony for Loran Cehack and Sochie Heim, who danced and offered prayers in front of the "White Doll" statue. When the Moonrace forces attack, the "White Doll" statue crumbled, revealing the Turn A. Loran and Sochie take shelter inside the cockpit, which activates and automatically fires at the unaware Moonrace forces. After several battles with the Moonrace, the Turn A became the symbol of the struggle to resist the Moonrace`s attempts at colonizing Earth.</description>
<picture>231941.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13514" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<name>RX-0 Unicorn Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A pure white MS produced by the "UC Project," part of the Federation Space Force`s reorganization plan. The entire movable frame of this experimental machine forms a psycoframe, and its responsiveness is extremely high. It also incorporates a special "Laplace Program" OS and a system known as "NT-D (Newtype Drive, called Newtype Destroyer System by Full Frontal)." When NT-D is activated, the internal frame expands and the entire figure is transformed. In the process, the armor separates along its seams, and slides are released. A red glow can be seen where the internal frame is exposed by the gaps in the armor, and this is believed to be a psycoframe luminescence phenomenon. The machine`s performance, in particular its mobility, is dramatically increased when NT-D is active. In its normal mode, it sports a head resembling that of mass-produced MS like the GM. Equiped with beam magnum, hyper bazooka, NT-D type shield, four beam saber and beam gatling gun as an option.</description>
<picture>39659.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13516" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<name>RX-0 Unicorn Gundam (Destroy Mode)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Unicorn`s appearance when the `NT-D` system is activated. In this form, the psycoframe built into the entire body`s movable frame reads the pilot`s thoughts (psycowaves) and directly influences the unit`s movements. In other words, the MS can ultimately be controlled by thought alone. However, when compared to one`s idea of how a human body works, the stress of gravity on a 20 meter MS (more than 10 times the size) is extraordinary. Aided by the psycommu, the pilot`s mind can only endure about five minutes of operation, after which a limiter is believed to activate, returning the MS to normal Unicorn form. Furthermore, the system activates not according to the pilot`s discretion, but automatically when certain conditions, as yet unexplained, are met. In this mode, the mobile suit becomes taller and its head transforms to one having standard Gundam features.</description>
<picture>39661.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15077" type="appears in" update="2010-02-17">
<rating votes="1">9.08</rating>
<name>GX-9900 Gundam X</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The GX-9900 Gundam X (GX) is one of three advanced mobile suits created by the United Nations Earth Space Force to fight against the Space Revolutionary Army. The Gundam X was the most powerful of the three models mainly because of its powerful weapon, the Satellite Cannon, which was specifically designed to destroy space colonies. Three GX units are known to have survived the 7th Space War. One was found and piloted by 15-year-old Garrod Ran, who later joined the crew of the Frieden. The second was found by the New United Nations Earth, which studied it and develop the Double X. The third was found by Vultures Rick Arel and Rosa II, aboard a sunken UNE submarine.</description>
<picture>43120.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38041" type="appears in" update="2011-10-23">
<name>XXXG-00W0 Wing Gundam-0</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The XXXG-00W0 Wing Gundam Zero (aka Wing Zero, Zero, Wing Zero ver EW, Wing Zero Custom) is a mobile suit that appears in Mobile Suit Gundam Wing and Mobile Suit Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz. Though having many pilots during its lifetime, the unit is most famously piloted by Heero Yuy.</description>
<picture>72694.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39139" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<rating votes="8">6.84</rating>
<name>XXXG-00W0 Wing Gundam-0</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77782.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="45234" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>MSZ-010 ZZ-Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>88502.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53294" type="appears in" update="2013-03-01">
<rating votes="4">6.33</rating>
<name>ZGMF-X42S Destiny Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>132927.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53567" type="appears in" update="2013-03-08">
<name>GF13-017NJII God Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133314.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53956" type="appears in" update="2013-03-22">
<rating votes="3">10.00</rating>
<name>RX-93 v Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>134071.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54002" type="appears in" update="2013-03-20">
<name>RX-78GP01-Fb Gundam GP01Fb Zephyrantes Full Burnern</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133874.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54003" type="appears in" update="2013-03-20">
<name>RX-79(G) Gundam Ground Type</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133875.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54004" type="appears in" update="2013-03-20">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>LM314V21 V2 Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133876.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54005" type="appears in" update="2013-03-20">
<name>FA-010S Full-Armor ZZ-Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133877.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54006" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-03-20">
<name>RX-78GP03 Gundam GP03 Dendrobium Orchis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133878.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="148165" update="2013-03-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
