<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9729" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-04-28</startdate>
<enddate>2013-04-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Koitabi: True Tours Nanto</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">恋旅~True Tours Nanto</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8453" approval="4" total="4">Nakaseru Sora ni Aitai: Toyama, Miwaku no Muttsu no Monogatari</anime>
<anime id="9559" approval="3" total="4">Otona Joshi no Anime Time 2</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="434710">Short and sweet love stories.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.koitabi-nanto.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1385" type="Animation Work">P.A. Works</name>
<name id="6549" type="Character Design">Yoshida Yuuko</name>
<name id="2241" type="Direction">Nishimura Junji</name>
<name id="36136" type="Music">Matsuda Akito</name>
</creators>
<description>Youji and Chiaki — http://anidb.net/ch53995 [Youji] decided on a job transfer, away from the mountains close to the beach. In his mind he already has steeled himself for a breakup with http://anidb.net/ch53996 [Chiaki], after having been together for five years. When suddenly mentioning the job transfer, Chiaki flat-out says she cannot handle a long-distance relationship, breaking up with him. They make one last effort to save their relationship by visiting Toyama, where they had their first date.
Haruki and Aoi — http://anidb.net/ch53997 [Haruki] creates small wooden sculptures as an apprentice under the watchful guidance of his master sculptor father, and brings them to his reliable childhood friend http://anidb.net/ch53998 [Aoi]`s family shop, to be sold. One day classmate http://anidb.net/ch61819 [Shiori] directly asks Aoi about her feelings for Haruki, which initially Aoi denies. Shiori then confesses her love to Haruki. And so both Aoi and Haruki have to rethink their previously comfortable friendship.
Takumi and Natsuko — http://anidb.net/ch53999 [Takumi] works at a large ski centre, where he maintains the cable cars in the off-season. http://anidb.net/ch54000 [Natsuko], practices race driving on the large ski resort parking lot. One day their romance blossoms on a cable car ride up into the beautiful mountains.
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="276">5.59</permanent>
<temporary count="277">6.51</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>136611.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15189</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17635</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.koitabi-nanto.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>恋旅〜True_Tours_Nanto</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345226</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16137</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4610" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-22">
<name>commercial</name>
<description>This title is used to sell and/or promote a real-life product or service. Not to be confused with "product placement" or "subliminal advertising" — this features *direct* promotion for such element.
Depending on the setting, some could even be considered as "animated infomercials".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6093" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>short story collection</name>
<description>An anthology is a collection of literary works chosen by the compiler. It may be a collection of poems, short stories, plays, songs, or excerpts by different authors.
An omnibus format release is not just one continuous story, but several short stories. They may feature a different cast between each story, and the authors may differ.
In genre fiction, anthology is used to categorize collections of shorter works such as short stories and short novels, by different authors, each featuring unrelated casts of characters and settings, and usually collected into a single volume for publication. The complete collections of works are often called complete works or Opera Omnia (Latin language equivalent).
Source: EN Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="53995" type="main character in" update="2013-03-19">
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<name>Sugawa Youji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="606" picture="18011.jpg">Masuda Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53996" type="main character in" update="2013-03-19">
<rating votes="2">9.44</rating>
<name>Aizawa Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53997" type="main character in" update="2013-03-19">
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<name>Yokokawa Haruki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53998" type="main character in" update="2013-03-19">
<rating votes="2">9.44</rating>
<name>Shindou Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53999" type="main character in" update="2013-03-19">
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<name>Nishi Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="605" picture="226544.jpg">Ishii Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54000" type="main character in" update="2013-03-19">
<rating votes="2">8.20</rating>
<name>Ishikura Natsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61818" type="appears in" update="2013-11-26">
<name>Haruki no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruki`s father.</description>
<picture>146383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61819" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-26">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Hishida Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiori is Aoi`s friend and classmate.</description>
<picture>146385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="607" picture="241611.jpg">Watanabe Tomomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61820" type="appears in" update="2013-11-26">
<name>Aoi no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoi`s mother.</description>
<picture>146384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="608" picture="18012.jpg">Takahashi Rieko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="147775" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">耀司と千晶 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Youji and Chiaki, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youji to Chiaki: Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150294" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">匠と夏子 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Takumi and Natsuko, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takumi to Natsuko: Kouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150295" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">匠と夏子 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Takumi and Natsuko, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takumi to Natsuko: Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150296" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">晴喜と葵 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haruki and Aoi, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haruki to Aoi: Kouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150297" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">晴喜と葵 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haruki and Aoi, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haruki to Aoi: Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150298" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">耀司と千晶 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Youji and Chiaki, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youji to Chiaki: Kouhen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
