<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9782" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-07-07</startdate>
<enddate>2013-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Uchouten Kazoku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Uchoten Kazoku</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">有頂天家族</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Eccentric Family</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">La famille excentrique</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">有顶天家族</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12417" type="Sequel">Uchouten Kazoku 2</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="334" approval="17" total="23">Heisei Tanuki Gassen Ponpoko</anime>
<anime id="9992" approval="11" total="12">Kyousougiga (2013)</anime>
<anime id="7243" approval="2" total="8">Yojouhan Shinwa Taikei</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="106569">Uchouten Kazoku could be PA Works` best show so far (2013) but in order to enjoy it you need to be VERY familiar with Japanese adult mindset and culture. Animation doesn`t get any more Japanese than this.

Not everything is explained upfront because average Japanese adults already have knowledge of those things and are to be able to connect the dots.

On top of that, if the notion of powerful men having mistresses don`t sit right with you, then you won`t get what this show is about.

Definitely not for kids, it just won`t make sense to them. I don`t think this show can be dubbed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="430122">The most interesting anime I have seen in a long time. Unique characters, story, and a wonderful and satisfying ending. Some may hate it, but it`s the one anime that has separated itself from most. I whole-heartily recommend it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="472569">I really like the story (as expected from tatami galaxy writer). and the directing is great too. it shows the feelings and family matters in a good way. it was the only show that got me to follow it this season. Its one of those animes that can only entrain people with special tastes not everyone. also the character design might tick off some people. (personally i think its a new way and i really like it) 
If you enjoy shounen its not for you, if you also enjoy romance, i doubt its not gonna entertaining for you. but if you like a new topic and story which is kinda new and not a goddamn copy , give it a try</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="260717">It`s weird -- nothing stands out. Animation is stiff, drawings are simple, they must`ve been working on a limited budget...

but there`s something genuine and sincere about this anime, about the culture and world they build up, about the people who live and how they interact with each other. You`ll laugh, you`ll cry, it`s a slice of life. Highly recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="132520">this show is going to be one of the best of this season. it`s a must! absolutely brilliant.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="45729">Despite containing so many surface elements which are typically aimed at a young audience, at its core, this is an anime which only sensitive adults can appreciate. Because the story is more akin to a Tanizaki novel or a Kawabata novel than anything else.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="378436">Loveable characters and a well paced story. Everybody should watch this, though not everybody will like it.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://uchoten-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1385" type="Animation Work">P.A. Works</name>
<name id="11105" type="Original Work">Morimi Tomihiko</name>
<name id="3037" type="Direction">Yoshihara Masayuki</name>
<name id="12540" type="Character Design">Kawatsura Kousuke</name>
<name id="4313" type="Series Composition">Suga Shoutarou</name>
<name id="31562" type="Music">Fujisawa Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="12540" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawatsura Kousuke</name>
</creators>
<description>In Kyoto, there are three kinds of residents: humans, raccoon dogs, and tengu. http://anidb.net/ch54078 [Shimogamo Yasaburou] is the third son of the Shimogamo raccoon dog family. His father, http://anidb.net/ch55462 [Souichirou], had been the head of Kyoto raccoon dog community until he was eaten by the human members of Friday Club. While taking care of old tengu, fighting with other raccoon dogs, and playing with a psychic human girl, Yasaburou approaches the truth of his father`s death.
Source: Crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1664">7.39</permanent>
<temporary count="1667">7.48</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>230632.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15205</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17909</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://uchoten-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Eccentric_Family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>有頂天家族</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3029</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345841</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16195</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3086" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>parricide</name>
<description>Parricide, or the murder of family members, is the act of taking the life of of one or more of one`s own close family members, or even one`s entire family; that may include spouses, parents, grandparents, children, grandchildren, siblings, cousins, uncles, aunts, nephews, and nieces, among others.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3278" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>deception</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3915" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>child abuse</name>
<description>Story depicts child abuse, which is a very complex and dangerous set of problems that include child neglect and the physical, emotional, and sexual abuse of children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4577" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-19">
<name>family values</name>
<description>Family values are traditional or cultural values, generally conservative in nature, that pertain to the family`s structure, function, roles, beliefs, attitudes, and ideals. They encompass a set of beliefs, the most common of which is the classical "traditional family" involving a middle-class family with a breadwinner father and a homemaker mother, raising their biological children.
According to Merriam-Webster, family values are "values especially of a traditional or conservative kind which are held to promote the sound functioning of the family and to strengthen the fabric of society."
Source: English Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5889" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-05">
<name>magic weapons</name>
<description>The characters in this anime wield magic weapons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5915" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>French kiss</name>
<description>A kiss in which the tongue enters the partner`s mouth.</description>
<picurl>238326.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6252" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>feud</name>
<description>A feud, referred to in more extreme cases as a blood feud, vendetta, faida, beef, clan war, gang war, or private war, is a long-running argument or fight, often between social groups of people, especially families or clans. Feuds begin because one party (correctly or incorrectly) perceives itself to have been attacked, insulted or wronged by another. Intense feelings of resentment trigger the initial retribution, which causes the other party to feel equally aggrieved and vengeful. The dispute is subsequently fuelled by a long-running cycle of retaliatory violence. This continual cycle of provocation and retaliation makes it extremely difficult to end the feud peacefully. Feuds frequently involve the original parties` family members and/or associates, can last for generations, and may result in extreme acts of violence. They can be interpreted as an extreme outgrowth of social relations based in family honour.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="54078" type="main character in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="15">7.41</rating>
<name>Shimogamo Yasaburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54079" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Shimogamo Yasaburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54080" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="1">7.57</rating>
<name>Shimogamo Yasaburou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54081" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="7">3.58</rating>
<name>Shimogamo Yaichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oldest brother of Yasaburou and the most responsible brother of the four.</description>
<picture>137831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54082" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="8">7.04</rating>
<name>Shimogamo Yajirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54083" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="7">4.96</rating>
<name>Shimogamo Yashirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54084" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-06">
<rating votes="58">4.77</rating>
<name>Benten</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54085" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-12">
<rating votes="13">5.67</rating>
<name>Kurofuku no Ouji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Prince in Black is http://anidb.net/ch90964 [Tousen]`s transformed form when she plays billiards.</description>
<picture>137830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55460" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="27">6.60</rating>
<name>Ebisugawa Kaisei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ex-fiancé of Yasaburou. Engagement was called off by her father after the death of Yasaburou`s father. Despite this it seems she still intends to marry Yasaburou as she still maintains close contact with his family. She is seen on several occasions she was looking out for Yasaburou and also filled in Yasaburou`s daily responsibilities whenever he is not around. Till this day Yasaburou is the only one who hasn`t seen her face because she is maintaining the tradition where the bride and groom can not see the face of each other till the day of their marriage.</description>
<picture>142233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55461" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-06">
<rating votes="9">2.76</rating>
<name>Akadama-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55462" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Shimogamo Souichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4711" picture="244962.jpg">Ishihara Bon</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56694" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="8">3.38</rating>
<name>Ebisugawa Souun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56695" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-06">
<rating votes="4">4.73</rating>
<name>Yodogawa Kyouju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27784" picture="75326.jpg">Higuchi Takehiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56696" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="6">1.87</rating>
<name>Kinkaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137837.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37475" picture="137811.jpg">Nishiji Shuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56697" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="6">1.87</rating>
<name>Ginkaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137838.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21734" picture="63348.jpg">Hatakeyama Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57780" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Daikoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4764" picture="67960.jpg">Takahashi Ryoukichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57781" type="appears in" update="2013-09-16">
<name>Juroujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57782" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Ebisu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140993.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57923" type="appears in" update="2013-07-17">
<name>Billiards-ba Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57924" type="appears in" update="2013-07-17">
<name>Daigakusei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57925" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="1">9.54</rating>
<name>Shimogamo Tousen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch90964 [Tousen]`s tanuki form.
She is rarely in this form and only transforms into this after getting shocked by the thunderstorm.</description>
<picture>206270.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58114" type="appears in" update="2013-07-25">
<name>Iwayasan Konkobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58115" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Shimogamo Yashirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58116" type="appears in" update="2013-07-25">
<name>Baa-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12464" picture="42188.jpg">Miyazawa Kiyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58117" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="4">6.68</rating>
<name>Shimogamo Yajirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58265" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Shimogamo Souichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4711" picture="244962.jpg">Ishihara Bon</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58556" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Teikinbo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140992.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3094" picture="50367.jpg">Kanao Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58557" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Bishamon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58558" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Kottouya Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6125" picture="223612.jpg">Hayashi Kazuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58559" type="appears in" update="2013-08-05">
<name>Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59004" type="appears in" update="2014-10-05">
<name>Kin`you Club</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>"The Friday Fellows" are a group of seven humans impersonating the seven lucky gods:
1. Hotei (fat and happy god of abundance and good health)
2. Juroujin (god of long life)
3. Fukurokuju (god of happiness, wealth and longevity)
4. Bishamonten (god of warriors)
5. Benzaiten (goddess of knowledge, art and beauty, especially music) -&gt; shortend to Benten-sama
6. Daikokuten (god of wealth, commerce and trade)
7. Ebisu (god of fishers or merchants, often depicted carrying a sea bream)
It is tradition of the members of the Friday Fellows to eat a tanuki stew on new year. A different member each year has to catch and bring a tanuki to cook a stew from.</description>
<picture>141648.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59025" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Kinkaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37475" picture="137811.jpg">Nishiji Shuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59213" type="appears in" update="2013-08-26">
<name>Keikan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59214" type="appears in" update="2013-08-26">
<name>Tanuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32890" picture="89265.jpg">Nogawa Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59580" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Ebisugawa Kaisei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142708.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59581" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Shimogamo Yaichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142709.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59582" type="appears in" update="2013-09-08">
<name>Ebisugawa-ke</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>142710.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59583" type="appears in" update="2013-09-08">
<name>Shimogamo-ke</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>142711.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59868" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="2">8.81</rating>
<name>Shimogamo Yajirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143210.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60167" type="appears in" update="2013-10-02">
<name>Fukurokuju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33894" picture="151731.jpg">Yamagishi Haruo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60289" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Ginkaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21734" picture="63348.jpg">Hatakeyama Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90957" type="appears in" update="2017-08-17">
<name>Yasaka Heitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="544" picture="238510.jpg">Ogawa Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90959" type="appears in" update="2017-08-17">
<name>Nanzenji Shoujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206262.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90964" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="2">8.50</rating>
<name>Shimogamo Tousen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shimogamo Tousen is the matriarch of the Shimogamo family. She is very protective of her children and does her best to make up for the loss of their father. Whenever there is a lighting storm, she loses her ability to transform, due to severe astrapophobia.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>206271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93245" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Shimogamo Yaichirou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93253" type="appears in" update="2018-01-12">
<name>Shimogamo Yaichirou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93254" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Ginkaku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21734" picture="63348.jpg">Hatakeyama Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93255" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Kinkaku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37475" picture="137811.jpg">Nishiji Shuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93256" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Shimogamo Yasaburou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93257" type="appears in" update="2018-01-12">
<name>Suzuki Satomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As a teenager, Suzuki Satomi was abducted by Akadama-sensei, who taught her the ways of tengu and how to fly.</description>
<picture>211875.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93258" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Shimogamo Yasaburou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="148494" update="2013-03-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151717" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅葉狩り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Taking in Fall Colors</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les feuilles d`automne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Momijigari</title>
<summary>Professor Yodogawa chases down Benten and Yasaburo, and they check out some autumn foliage. When she ditches them, Yodogawa has a lot to say about his philosophy of eating and Yasaburo also gets told a story about a conversation between Yodogawa and Benten`s first tanuki hot pot victim (i.e. Shimogamo Soichiro), which he promptly reports to Yajiro.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641867</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151718" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金曜倶楽部</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Friday Fellows</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Club du Vendredi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kin`you Club</title>
<summary>Yasaburo had been hiding from Benten in Osaka, but thanks to Kinkaku and Ginkaku she catches him during a visit to Kyoto and makes him perform tanuki tricks for the Friday Fellows. It is revealed that Yasaburo`s mother was saved by a man who gave her onigiri and also that one of the Friday Fellows, Hotei, has loved tanuki ever since he saved one and fed it onigiri...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641865</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151719" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大文字納涼船合戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle of the Daimonji Leisure Cruisers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bataille navale au festival Daimonji</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daimonji Nouryousen Kassen</title>
<summary>During the traditional Daimonji leisure cruise, the Ebisugawas come to pick on the Shimogamo family. Yasaburo fights bravely, but loses the Fujin Raijin folding fan. Fearing Benten`s wrath, he goes into hiding after the inner parlor crashes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641863</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151720" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">薬師坊の奥座敷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yakushibo`s Inner Parlor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`arrière-salle de Yakushibô</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakushibou no Okuzashiki</title>
<summary>In order to uphold a Shimogamo family tradition, Yasaburo needs to do what Yaichiro could not and come up with a leisure cruiser for them to launch. He asks to borrow Yakushibo`s flying inner parlor, but ends up having to make a dangerous deal with Benten.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641861</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151721" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">母と雷神様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mom and Raijin, God of Thunder</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Maman et le dieu du tonnerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haha to Raijin-sama</title>
<summary>Yasaburo visits Yajiro, who lives in the bottom of a well as a frog and forgot how to transform back into himself. When a storm comes, the three non-frog Shimogamo brothers race to help their mother, who is terrified of thunder.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641859</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151722" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">納涼床の女神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goddess of the Noryoyuka</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Déesse des terrasses sur berge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nouryouyuka no Megami</title>
<summary>Since the Heian era relocation, humans, tanuki, and tengu have maintained a delicate balance. But none of that matter as a young tanuki is tasked by an older tengu to deliver a dangerous letter.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641747</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152525" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">銭湯の掟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bathhouse Rules</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les règles du bain public</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentou no Okite</title>
<summary>Yasaburo, Yashiro, and Yaichiro convince Prof. Akadama to take a much-needed bath, but they run into the Ebisugawa twins at the bathhouse. After a brief scuffle it is revealed that Yajiro was at least partly responsible for Shimogamo Soichiro`s death in the Friday Fellow`s hot pot.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641869</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152615" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父の発つ日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day of Dad`s Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour du départ de notre père</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi no Tatsu Hi</title>
<summary>Yajiro tells Yasaburo and Yaichiro his account of the night their father was eaten. Later Yasaburo hears a continuation of the story Yajiro doesn`t know: Soichiro bumped into Prof. Akadama on his way to the afterlife.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641871</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152759" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">偽叡山電車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The False Eizan Electric Railway</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le faux train Eizan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nise Eizan Densha</title>
<summary>Yashiro comes up with a plan to get Yajiro back in the game, leading to the trouncing of Kinkaku and Ginkaku. Yashiro stalls the Nise-emon decision meeting while Yasaburo saves Yaichiro, but their mom is still in danger of becoming Friday Fellow hot pot.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641879</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152760" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">捲土重来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Back in the Game</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Riposte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kendochourai</title>
<summary>After Yasaburo gets a hand from Benten to escape Soun and his Elite Guard, the Ebisugawas manage to nab him anyway through a clever Kinkaku-Ginkaku plot. Meanwhile, Kaisei helps Yashiro escape the Electric Brandy factory and Yaichiro is handed over to the Friday Fellows as the primary ingredient for their year-end hot pot.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641877</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152761" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夷川早雲の暗躍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Behind-the-Scenes Dealings of Ebisugawa Soun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Manœuvres de Sôun Ebisugawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ebisugawa Souun no An`yaku</title>
<summary>The meaning of Kaisei`s mysterious apology becomes clear as the Ebisugawa plot to boil Yaichiro in a hot pot is revealed on the day of the Nise-emon election. The day is also the anniversary of Soichiro`s death, for which it turns out Soun was responsible.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641875</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152762" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夷川の娘・海星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaisei, Daughter of Ebisugawa</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kaisei, la fille des Ebisugawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ebisugawa no Musume Kaisei</title>
<summary>Yasaburo gets interrupted while warming his butt and sent to convince Prof. Akadama to attend the council where the new Nise-emon will be decided. He later succeeds in his quest for warmth, but over the wall splitting the men`s and women`s baths, he receives an ominous apology from Kaisei; her brothers are plotting something.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641873</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154325" update="2017-06-16">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">有頂天家族</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eccentric Family</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La famille excentrique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchouten Kazoku</title>
<summary>Tanuki and human worlds collide as both the Nise-emon ceremony and Friday Fellow year-end bash descend into chaos. The scale of the disturbance increases when Prof. Akadama starts brandishing the Fujin Raijin folding fan, but by New Year`s everything settles down and Yasaburo and co. are able to calmly consider their hopes for the future.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641881</identifier>
<identifier>the-eccentric-family</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157787" update="2014-01-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157788" update="2014-01-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
