<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9808" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-07-03</startdate>
<enddate>2013-09-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sen`yuu. (2013)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Senyuu 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">戦勇. (2013)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Senyu (2013)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">战勇。第2期</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9393" type="Prequel">Sen`yuu.</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://senyu.tv/</url>
<description>A vast conspiracy pierces through the Demon and Human Worlds. The Demons wanted to bring back the Demon King, and the Human King wanted to be the King who brought forth the hero who would seal him. Traitors and betrayers are everywhere as multiple sides collide. After 3 months, self-proclaimed hero http://anidb.net/ch48373 [Alba] is back for more elegant and clever retorts.
"There`s nothing elegant about retorts!"
And there`s the first of season two.
Source: Crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="803">5.64</permanent>
<temporary count="804">6.77</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>137824.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15295</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17391</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>18523</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/senyu/index2.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://senyu.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>戦勇。</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3058</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15646</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2633" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>prison</name>
<description>A building used to house convicted criminals and accused persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="48373" type="main character in" update="2012-12-06">
<rating votes="11">5.30</rating>
<name>Aruba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129130.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48374" type="main character in" update="2012-12-06">
<rating votes="18">7.98</rating>
<name>Ross</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50293" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-31">
<rating votes="6">2.84</rating>
<name>Foyfoy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50294" type="main character in" update="2012-12-31">
<rating votes="10">6.45</rating>
<name>Ruki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50295" type="appears in" update="2012-12-31">
<rating votes="8">5.23</rating>
<name>Rudolf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51000" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-17">
<rating votes="6">6.29</rating>
<name>Hime-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52140" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-19">
<rating votes="10">6.13</rating>
<name>Ares</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52141" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-19">
<rating votes="6">3.46</rating>
<name>Januar Ein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52142" type="appears in" update="2013-04-02">
<rating votes="8">4.22</rating>
<name>Mii-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130882.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52195" type="appears in" update="2013-01-19">
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<name>Ou-sama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3337" picture="211147.jpg">Ogino Seirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52572" type="appears in" update="2013-02-02">
<name>Hime-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131700.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53570" type="appears in" update="2013-03-08">
<name>Dezember Zwolf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="465" picture="56019.jpg">Kondou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53852" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-15">
<rating votes="3">2.03</rating>
<name>Februar Zwei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3830" picture="25450.jpg">Terasaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54171" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-22">
<rating votes="3">7.91</rating>
<name>Samejima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55717" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-09">
<name>Elf November</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4032" picture="77662.jpg">Okamoto Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55718" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-09">
<name>Juli</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56722" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-06">
<name>Shodai Rukimedes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3337" picture="211147.jpg">Ogino Seirou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="151539" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 思い悩む.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Broods</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Omoinayamu.</title>
<summary>Alba gets seperated from Rchi-tan and Ros and they get stuck in the dimensional rift. Despite being the hero, Alba somehow ends up in the background and meanwhile in the dimensional rift, Ros and company find someone rather unexpected...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627987</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151540" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 唖然とする.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Is Stunned</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Azen to Suru.</title>
<summary>While in the dimensional rift, Rchi-tan and the others find the original King Rchimedes, however he seems to be asleep with no sign of waking up. Ros suggests that they should leave the dimensional rift as soon as possible since time passes much faster there and then another random fellow shows up...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627989</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151541" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 圧倒される.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Is Overwhelmed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Attou Sareru.</title>
<summary>Outside Turtle Alba is left alone.  A bounty hunter attacks him in disguise.  Who is this assassin with his hidden weapons?
Meanwhile in town, Hime-chan`s repairs are complete.  They try to test the new functionality, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627993</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151542" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 嵌められる.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Is Set Up</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Hamerareru.</title>
<summary>The party arrives at the mechanical city of Turtle to find themselves involved in a murder.
Alba is holding a bloodstained knife. What happened to him? Who is the culprit?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627991</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152230" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 戦慄する.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Is Terrified</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Senritsu Suru.</title>
<summary>With Samejima`s help the battle with Zwei is finally brought to an end.  After the battle Zwei has a change of heart and tells them the truth about the revival of the Demon King.  Just then a new assassin strikes!
Meanwhile Alba has joined the mysterious elf who attacked him, and tries to go into the town.  But he ends up someplace strangely familiar...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627995</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152381" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 絶句する.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Becomes Speechless</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Zekku Suru.</title>
<summary>Alba escapse from prison with the help of Elf`s amazing disguises.  He gives his full name as Elf November and says he hopes they`ll meet again.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627997</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152385" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 帰還する.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Returns</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Kikan Suru.</title>
<summary>Ros faces off with the revived Rchemides, but even with his revived power he is unable to defeat him and has to seal him away again.  Alba tries to stop him before he leaves, but Ros is unwavering.  Just as he reaches his hand out, Ros vanishes with the demon king.  What will Alba do now?  And how will the story end?  The last episode of "Senyu."  Please enjoy the story.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>628011</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152386" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 決意する.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Makes a Choice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Ketsui Suru.</title>
<summary>A shocking event makes everyone freeze.  A stunned Ros resigns himself to an irrevocable truth and at last unleashes his sealed poewr.
But the price of this is great, and the sealed demon king, the first Rchemides, awakens from his long slumber...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>628009</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152387" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 解き放つ.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Unleashed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Tokihanatsu.</title>
<summary>The arrival of Alba`s group makes a mess of everything and December is very mad.
He points his anger at Alba, the center of the group, and attacks.
The next moment the whole group freezes... what has happened to Alba?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>628007</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152388" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 尽きる.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Falls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Tsukiru.</title>
<summary>The heroic deeds of our hero, Alba, save the party from certain doom.  Samejima falls into the depths of despair right after his revival, but Ros goes back to his normal self. Meanwhile, December is angry over having his plan to revive the Demon King interrupted and is about to attack again.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>628005</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152389" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 再会する.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Reunites</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Saikai Suru.</title>
<summary>December reveals Ros`s secret.  The party is shocked and glad to hear it.  But Ros seems unhappy, and December thinks he knows why.  He says that if Ros uses his power it will revive the Demon King, and so he orders Juli to attack again.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>628003</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152390" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 変貌する.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Transforms</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Henbou Suru.</title>
<summary>Janua freezes at Juli`s words, and Juli strikes.  Just when it seemed that Janua might fall as well to his violence, Ros uses his hidden power to save them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>628001</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152391" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者, 沈黙する.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero Falls Silent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha, Chinmoku Suru.</title>
<summary>Samejima`s sacrifice saves the party from Juli`s sneak attack.  His anger at his wounded friend causes Janua to unleash his powerful ninjutsu, but Juli is unphased and speaks to him with a smirk.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>627999</identifier>
<identifier>senyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156665" update="2013-12-12">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">執事長のたび その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitsujichou no Tabi Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156666" update="2013-12-12">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園戦勇.~青春物語~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuen Senyuu.: Seishun Monogatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157018" update="2014-01-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157019" update="2014-01-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157468" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2013-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Season 1 15min. Summary</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157469" update="2014-01-16">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Blu-ray&amp;DVD + Album Selling CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157470" update="2014-01-16">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Season 2 Yokoku 5sec.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157471" update="2014-01-16">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Season 2 Yokoku 15sec.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157472" update="2014-01-16">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Season 2 Yokoku 30sec.</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
