<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9816" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2013-12-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yozakura Quartet: Hana no Uta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hana no uta</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">夜桜四重奏 ~ハナノウタ~</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">夜樱四重奏 花之歌</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9817" type="Sequel">Yozakura Quartet: Tsuki ni Naku</anime>
<anime id="5976" type="Alternative Setting">Yozakura Quartet</anime>
<anime id="7460" type="Side Story">Yozakura Quartet: Hoshi no Umi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10663" approval="16" total="24">Kekkai Sensen</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="179476">It`s a remake of the original series, so you don`t need to watch the original first although it helps somewhat.  While I preferred the original character designs that were more mature, this version really grew on me.

It`s has a nice mix of comedy, romance, and action, and it all blends together to be a really enjoyable result.  Make sure you watch Yozakura Quartet: Hoshi no Umi after episode 8, as that where it fits plot-wise.  Recommended!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="30310">This season is a more pleasant watch than the old show from 2008, but I liked the more mature character designs from back then better. Especially Hime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="558965">this anime is really nice..
character designs are really good...
the story is interesting, but it`s a bit confusing...
if you want to know the full story, read the manga or at least watch the series before this..
while this series, is a remake from the old one, but more complex and more side stories..and cuter character design..tehee
really, the side stories are also nice...
recommended to watch this...and the side stories..</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://yozakura-anime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="13515" type="Series Composition">Ishikawa Manabu</name>
<name id="6889" type="Original Work">Yasuda Suzuhito</name>
<name id="830" type="Animation Work">Tatsunoko Production</name>
<name id="7257" type="Character Design">Ryouchimo</name>
<name id="6889" type="Series Composition">Yasuda Suzuhito</name>
<name id="15726" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takada Akira</name>
<name id="7257" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ryouchimo</name>
<name id="26108" type="Music">Yashikin</name>
<name id="7257" type="Direction">Ryouchimo</name>
</creators>
<description>In a town where humans and demons co-exist, it takes more than a normal police force to maintain the peace. Enter the Hiizumi Life Counseling Office, a fantastic foursome of unique teenagers, each gifted with an amazing super power!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="919">6.26</permanent>
<temporary count="924">7.12</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>140304.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15287</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20987</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>18497</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://yozakura-anime.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Yozakura_Quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>夜桜四重奏_〜ヨザクラカルテット〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3187</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347029</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16487</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1155" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-28">
<name>mermaid</name>
<description>A creature that is half-human (usually the upper body) and half-fish (usually the lower body). A male mermaid is called merman (but they can appear under many different names). Since mermaids are often confused with Sirens in media, they may posses special abilities akin to Sirens such as enchanting voice (on the other hand Sirens are often being portrayed as mermaids). Some mermaids might be able to transform their whole body into human (which is not surprising since mermaids are often associated with the "want to become human" theme) and that should not disqualify them from getting this tag.</description>
<picurl>209970.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1403" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-10">
<name>nun</name>
<description>A nun is a member of a religious community of women, typically one living under vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. She may have decided to dedicate her life to serving all other living beings, or she might be an ascetic who voluntarily chose to leave mainstream society and live her life in prayer and contemplation in a monastery or convent. The term "nun" is applicable to Catholics (eastern and western traditions), Orthodox Christians, Anglicans, Lutherans, Jains, Buddhists, Taoists, Hindus and some other religious traditions.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>165755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2225" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>whipping</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2491" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-09">
<name>nurse</name>
<description>For hentai shows, it`s enough if a http://anidb.net/t884 [nurse costume] is worn without the female character actually working as a nurse.
For ecchi shows, the nurse profession must play a big enough part in the overall setting.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
<picurl>160445.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2868" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-20">
<name>racism</name>
<description>Racism is prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against someone of an ethnically different background based on the pseudo-scientific belief that biological differences between peoples form so-called "races" and that one`s own "race" is superior to another, possibly also holding that members of different "races" should be treated differently. Some definitions include only consciously malignant forms of discrimination, and some views include discriminatory behaviors and beliefs based on cultural, national, ethnic, caste, or religious stereotypes. In works of fiction, this may also include similar actions against other sentient species.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3295" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>world domination</name>
<description>"Gee, Brain, what do you want to do tonight?"
"The same thing we do every night, Pinky: try to take over the world!"
A main objective for one of the characters is absolute control of not just one country, but a whole planet!</description>
<picurl>38878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3435" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>eating of humans</name>
<description>The eating of humans, also called man-eating, is the practice of some species to prey on human beings for nourishment. Examples of possible hunters may include Earth animals, alien species, zombies or other undead, and so forth. Eating of humans is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3815 [human cannibalism]; the former is about other species eating people, while the latter is about humans eating fellow humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3504" parentid="2879" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>sake</name>
<description>Sake, generally referred to as a Japanese rice wine, is an alcoholic beverage made by fermenting rice.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>215208.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3539" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-16">
<name>growing hair</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4703" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-23">
<name>lacrosse</name>
<description>Lacrosse is a team sport of Native American origin played using a small rubber ball and a long-handled stick called a crosse or lacrosse stick, mainly played in the United States and Canada. It is a contact sport which requires padding. The head of the lacrosse stick is strung with loose mesh designed to catch and hold the lacrosse ball. Offensively, the objective of the game is to score by shooting the ball into an opponent`s goal, using the lacrosse stick to catch, carry, and pass the ball to do so. Defensively, the objective is to keep the opposing team from scoring and to dispossess them of the ball through the use of stick checking and body contact or positioning. The sport has four major types: men`s field lacrosse, women`s lacrosse, box lacrosse and intercrosse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4907" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>small town</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5889" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-05">
<name>magic weapons</name>
<description>The characters in this anime wield magic weapons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6068" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-20">
<name>human sacrifice</name>
<description>Human sacrifice is the act of killing one or more human beings as part of a ritual. Throughout the majority of human history, primitive societies have engaged in human sacrifice, generally as a religious act, such as an offering to please or appease deities, spirits, or the deceased. Other uses that have been seen include magic rituals, usually related to black magic or the summoning of demons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6115" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-02">
<name>omimai</name>
<description>Visiting a sick person (as in a hospital or at home).
The protagonist or any other character caught a cold so his friends go visit him. In a school setting this is used as a plot device to allow fellow students to show their concern, and it is also a pertinent excuse to get out of school.</description>
<picurl>160896.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6443" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-02">
<name>wooden horse</name>
<description>A wooden horse is a device used in BDSM play, by having the victim straddle the wooden horse.</description>
<picurl>175282.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6730" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-11">
<name>torture</name>
<description>Torture involves the deliberate act of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or apply coercion to compel action from the victim. Torture, by definition, is a knowing and intentional act; deeds which unknowingly or negligently inflict pain without a specific intent to do so are not typically considered torture.
This is distinct from http://anidb.net/t2905 [erotic torture], which is generally for the purpose of using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3390" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="71">7.52</rating>
<name>Yarizakura Hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yarizakura Hime is a sixteen years old high school girl with supernatural powers because she is the human form of an ancient Dragon. She is a mayor of Sakurashin city which she assumed after her grandmother.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3391" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="24">5.29</rating>
<name>Hiizumi Akina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiizumi Akina is an eighteen years old young man in the employment of the city. He is the director of the Hiizumi Life Counseling Office and the only human who works there. He is able to perform tuning, an ability that can send back youkai to their world and cut off their connection to the human world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3392" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="50">7.27</rating>
<name>Nanami Ao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nanami Ao is a fifteen years old female Satori who helps run the office and is the announcer of the town as well. She has cat ears, which she usually hides with a hat or headphones, and has the ability to read people`s thoughts. She can talk to animals using this ability as well. She has a stronger version called Satellite, which can read the thoughts of everyone in the city at once, though this drains a lot of her energy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3393" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="48">7.46</rating>
<name>Isone Kotoha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isone Kotoha is a sixteen years old high school student who was once a human before she was striked at a very young age. Because of that event she became a Hanyou, half youkai and half human. She is a Language-user (Kotodama Tsukai) who can summon things when she emphasises words. She can conjure up weapons or objects by saying one word, however there are certain objects where she needs to use a lengthy spell in order to conjure it up.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155427.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3394" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="13">7.51</rating>
<name>Kishi Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kishi Kyousuke is an eighteen years old man who is an assistant to http://anidb.net/ch3390 [Yarizakura Hime]. He is an Oni with superhuman strength, but wears a seal that looks like a bracelet around his left wrist. He appears to be harsh towards http://anidb.net/ch3391 [Akina] sometimes because he believes that Akina`s power is not required to protect the town.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3395" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="30">6.61</rating>
<name>Kishi Touka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kishi Touka is a sixteen years old high school student who is http://anidb.net/ch3394 [Kyousuke]`s little sister. She is also an employee of Hiizumi Life Counseling office. Just like her brother, she is an Oni with superhuman strength. She has a crush on http://anidb.net/ch3391 [Akina], which Kyousuke is not pleased with.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3396" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="23">4.76</rating>
<name>Azuma Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azuma Rin is a fifteen years old Jiang Shi (reanimated corpse) who recently moved to the city. Due to being constantly bullied by her human classmates during childhood, she loathed humans until being saved by Akina. She now works in a noodle store. When she was a child she was hunted by humans until she met http://anidb.net/ch20472 [Zakuro] who became her first friend.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1676" picture="144276.jpg">Matayoshi Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3397" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="13">5.00</rating>
<name>Shinatsuhiko Yuuhi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinatsuhiko Yuuhi is a Land God with great power, enough where http://anidb.net/ch3399 [Enjin] and his associates fear him, but it`s his sister http://anidb.net/ch3398 [Yae] who wields the title of Land Goddess of Sakurashin. He appears as a young boy, however he is really much older. He has been watching over Sakurashin for over 200 years and is the District Mayor.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1677" picture="223670.jpg">Matsumoto Sachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3398" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="35">7.13</rating>
<name>Shinatsuhiko Yae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinatsuhiko Yae is http://anidb.net/ch3397 [Yuuhi]`s younger sister. She is the Land Goddess of Sakurashin and is usually shown dressed as a nun who wields two katana swords beside her waist. She appears to be fond of bears and plush toys.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155436.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3399" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="12">4.37</rating>
<name>Hiizumi Enjin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiizumi Enjin is the main antagonist. A youkai who is determined to destroy the city for unknown reasons.
Enjin was a member of the branch family of the Hiizumi household. He was tuned along with his relatives by the main branch centuries before and returns as a non-physical entity possessing the body of Ao`s older brother Gin. To enact revenge at the city, Enjin intends to force the seven pillars to bloom in an attempt to fuse the human and Youkai dimensions. Aside from Gin`s Satori powers, Enjin`s true power is Striking which is the opposite of Akina`s Tuning, summoning objects from the Youkai world instead. Enjin later reveals that he can also perform Tuning as well, but at a much smaller potential than Akina.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20470" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="28">6.58</rating>
<name>V Juri F</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>V Juri F, whole name Victor Juri Frankenstein, is a nurse who runs a clinic in Sakurashin. She has her own TV show called the Juri Channel. She appears to have superhuman strength, however she is really a human. Akina comes by to her clinic to get himself check over because of his tuning ability and can re-tune him.
Juri used to be an assistant for http://anidb.net/ch3390 [Hime] when Hime was a child and had finally become mayor of Sakurashin.
The V and F in her name stands for "Victor Frankenstein", the name of her ancestor and http://anidb.net/ch20471 [Mariabelle]`s father making her Mariabelle`s great-grandniece as Juri is a descendant of Mariabelle brother.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1626" picture="156857.jpg">Ookubo Aiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20471" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-16">
<rating votes="20">4.67</rating>
<name>Mariabelle</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mariabelle is the District Mayor`s assistant, which makes her http://anidb.net/ch3397 [Yuuhi]`s assistant. She is an immortal human.
200 years ago, Mariabelle once died from a deadly disease but her father resurrected her and use her body as a basis to make a cure for the disease to save her brother and her village. Now an immortal and a living dead, she and her father travelled to Sakurashin to have her tuned to prevent other half youkais who seeks her immortality but Yuuhi manage to persuade them not to. As a sign of gratitude for saving her life, Mariabelle became Yuuhi`s assistant.
She is always seen in various cosplay outfit due to Yuuhi.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20472" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="15">6.45</rating>
<name>Kurumaki Zakuro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurumaki Zakuro is http://anidb.net/ch3396 [Rin]`s first friend and the first demon hunter who made an attack on Sakurashin. Zakuro is a necromancer and is capable of controlling anything that was once living, but is now dead, along with other yokai.
After the fight she began working in the same noodle delivery store as Rin.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>155433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20473" type="appears in" update="2014-05-10">
<name>Oyassan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2893" picture="240353.jpg">Yamaguchi Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23494" type="appears in" update="2014-05-10">
<name>Okami-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58064" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="18">5.16</rating>
<name>V Lila F</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>V Lila F is an unknown youkai hunter who appeared in Sakurashin.
She is http://anidb.net/ch20470 [Juri]`s younger sister, and an extremely talented magician.
Just like Zakuro, Lila eventually reforms after reconciling with her sister and becomes her assistant at the hospital.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>142075.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58065" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="2">6.33</rating>
<name>Mizuki Shidou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142072.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58066" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="12">4.93</rating>
<name>Tatebayashi Mina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58067" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="10">4.50</rating>
<name>Tatebayashi Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19679" picture="207991.jpg">Inokuchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61035" type="appears in" update="2013-12-10">
<rating votes="2">6.56</rating>
<name>Lily</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62222" type="appears in" update="2013-12-11">
<name>Shiina Noriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23484" picture="151668.jpg">Keichou Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62223" type="appears in" update="2014-04-27">
<name>Sawaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sawaki is Hime`s classmate.</description>
<picture>154982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9124" picture="186845.jpg">Hayama Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62224" type="appears in" update="2013-12-11">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Mizuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mizuki is Kotoha`s classmate.</description>
<picture>147012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37365" picture="137491.jpg">Takao Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62225" type="appears in" update="2013-12-11">
<name>Morioka Shidare</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62226" type="appears in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="5">5.02</rating>
<name>Amano Midoriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amano Midoriko is Hime`s classmate.</description>
<picture>154983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4616" picture="170439.jpg">Nishi Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62227" type="appears in" update="2013-12-11">
<name>Osanai Akina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Akina.</description>
<picture>147016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62228" type="appears in" update="2013-12-11">
<name>Yarizakura Machi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yarizakura Machi is Hime`s granny.</description>
<picture>147017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19174" picture="50012.jpg">Kubota Tamie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62229" type="appears in" update="2013-12-11">
<name>Hiizumi Makiharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiizumi Makiharu is Akina`s grandfather.</description>
<picture>147018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3093" picture="38195.jpg">Nojima Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62244" type="appears in" update="2013-12-11">
<name>Yotsuya Kiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62245" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-11">
<rating votes="3">4.05</rating>
<name>Sakurano Kohime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakurano Kohime is Hime`s younger cousin.</description>
<picture>147036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62246" type="appears in" update="2013-12-11">
<name>Yaoya no Ojisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Man from vegetable shop.</description>
<picture>147034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33894" picture="151731.jpg">Yamagishi Haruo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62247" type="appears in" update="2013-12-11">
<name>Yaoya no Obasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Woman from vegetable shop.</description>
<picture>147035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38121" picture="223543.jpg">Okada Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62248" type="appears in" update="2013-12-11">
<name>Morino Kazuyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62249" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-11">
<rating votes="3">5.15</rating>
<name>Shinozuka Eiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62250" type="appears in" update="2013-12-13">
<name>Nazo no Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mysterious man.</description>
<picture>147042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62251" type="appears in" update="2013-12-11">
<name>Yotsuya Jinroku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62269" type="appears in" update="2013-12-12">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Yarizakura Hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Hime.</description>
<picture>147050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62270" type="appears in" update="2013-12-12">
<rating votes="1">5.43</rating>
<name>Kishi Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Kyousuke.</description>
<picture>147051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62271" type="appears in" update="2013-12-12">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Kishi Touka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Touka.</description>
<picture>147052.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62405" type="appears in" update="2013-12-18">
<name>Iyo Usuzumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62406" type="appears in" update="2013-12-18">
<name>Kibune Uzu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67012" type="appears in" update="2014-04-24">
<rating votes="4">7.17</rating>
<name>Shinatsuhiko Yae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Yae.</description>
<picture>154897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67013" type="appears in" update="2014-04-24">
<name>Shinatsuhiko Yuuhi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuhi`s taller, older form which he takes when he goes on official rounds. Normaly he keeps the smaller one for Mariabelle`s sake who thinks it`s cute while the older one upsets her.</description>
<picture>154898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1677" picture="223670.jpg">Matsumoto Sachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67014" type="appears in" update="2014-04-24">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>V Juri F</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Juri. When Juri first came to Sakurashin, she had been obsessed with growing up and making people hear what she had to say about her ancestor Doctor Frankenstein.</description>
<picture>154899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1626" picture="156857.jpg">Ookubo Aiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67017" type="appears in" update="2014-04-25">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>V Lila F</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Lila.</description>
<picture>154908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67018" type="appears in" update="2014-04-25">
<name>Hidagyuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="154617" update="2013-10-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソノトキヲ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Moment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Toki o</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154618" update="2013-10-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ススミダス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Set in Motion.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Susumidasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154619" update="2013-10-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハルノカゼ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spring Winds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haru no Kaze</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154620" update="2013-10-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サクラサク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cherry Blossoms Bloom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakurasaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155095" update="2014-07-01">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155096" update="2013-10-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155389" update="2013-10-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イバラミチ.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thorny Path.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ibara Michi.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155390" update="2013-10-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イバラミチ 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thorny Path, Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ibara Michi 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155391" update="2013-10-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イバラミチ 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thorny Path, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ibara Michi 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155392" update="2013-10-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イバラミチ 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thorny Path, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ibara Michi 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156297" update="2013-11-23">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハナノウタ.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Song of Flowers.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hana no Uta.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156298" update="2013-11-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハナノウタ 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Song of Flowers, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hana no Uta 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156299" update="2013-11-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハナノウタ 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Song of Flowers, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hana no Uta 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156300" update="2013-11-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロクノイチ 後</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One of Six, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roku no Ichi: Ato</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156301" update="2013-11-23">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロクノイチ 前</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One of Six, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roku no Ichi: Mae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156680" update="2014-04-24">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よざカル! 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoza-Quar! 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yozaquar! 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156681" update="2014-04-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よざカル! 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoza-Quar! 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yozaquar! 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156682" update="2014-04-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よざカル! 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoza-Quar! 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yozaquar! 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157060" update="2014-07-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2 (ep9)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158294" update="2014-04-24">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よざカル! 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoza-Quar! 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yozaquar! 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159400" update="2014-04-24">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よざカル! 5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoza-Quar! 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yozaquar! 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159871" update="2014-05-15">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よざカル! 6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoza-Quar! 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yozaquar! 6</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
