<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9823" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2013-12-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">White Album 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">White Album II</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">WHITE ALBUM2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">White Album 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">白色相簿2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6026" type="Same Setting">White Album</anime>
<anime id="6970" type="Same Setting">White Album (2009)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10601" approval="12" total="24">Yahari Ore no Seishun LoveCome wa Machigatte Iru. Zoku</anime>
<anime id="896" approval="10" total="15">Kimi ga Nozomu Eien</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="9">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="413789">Powerful drama, the one that leaves you shattered by the end. And yet... makes you eager for more.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="165460">Stays true to it`s predecessor, if you liked the formula so far you wont be disappointed.

Also, one of the most satisfying romance/dramas released in the past year.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="363469">Took a bunch of the good parts of the first series, and improved upon them. The focus of the story never moves away from the three leads, which was a sort of detriment of the first series. The sound direction was pretty good in this series, the characters were all likeable which made the drama more poignant, and the overall story was great. I gave the first series a recommended, and this one was better than the first series, so it gets a Must See from me.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="432445">A poetic story about forlorn feelings between three friends, and the ability of love and guilt to tear friendships apart. This beautiful yet wistful romance poses that ever-present question of its genre: Should tsundere girls get second chances? The music from its predecessor is integrated perfectly into the plot, giving the lyrics fresh meaning. The artwork and scenery are well-executed, and sets the perfect mood together with the delicate and brilliant soundtrack.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="534115">One of the best romance animes I have seen for 2 or 3 years. 2 main heroines are likable and all 2 have very nice char-developments, I can`t choose who wins at the whole series. The story is unique and the music is very great.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="434710">So beautiful yet so sad...</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://whitealbum2.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="21585" type="Direction">Andou Masaomi</name>
<name id="5987" type="Chief Direction">Numata Seiya</name>
<name id="9850" type="Animation Character Design">Fujimoto Satoru</name>
<name id="6584" type="Chief Animation Direction">Mizukami Rondo</name>
<name id="9850" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujimoto Satoru</name>
<name id="1146" type="Music">Aquaplus</name>
<name id="36578" type="Series Composition">Maruto Fumiaki</name>
<name id="1043" type="Animation Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="1146" type="Original Work">Aquaplus</name>
<name id="37596" type="Music">Kobayashi Shuntarou</name>
</creators>
<description>As if to match the guitar I play in the afternoon music classroom, as if to match the piano someone plays in the next room, the pure singing voice from the rooftop connects the three disconnected melodies.
It all started in such a day in late autumn.
At that time, someone fell in love.
Everyone was doing their best. Everyone pushed on. Everyone was intent and honest...
We formed a bond and obtained a precious moment.
That`s why someone fell in love. A love that was too late, a love that shouldn`t have occurred.
And then comes winter. The falling snow covers all sins. And spring eventually comes, melting the snow and imposing all punishments.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1202">7.25</permanent>
<temporary count="1212">7.46</temporary>
<review count="2">6.75</review>
</ratings>
<picture>151348.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15274</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18245</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>28227</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://whitealbum2.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>White_Album_2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>WHITE_ALBUM2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3158</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347014</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16501</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2920</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3758" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-28">
<name>concert</name>
<description>The main characters play one or more live music performances during the show. This mostly happens for anime with the main focus on music.</description>
<picurl>169133.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4606" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>slide show animation</name>
<description>The entire anime or parts of it show sequences of still images. Sometimes used in low budged animations for action scenes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4656" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-06">
<name>infidelity</name>
<description>Infidelity is a violation of a couple`s assumed or stated contract regarding emotional and/or sexual exclusivity, sometimes according to the subjective feeling that one`s partner has violated a set of rules or relationship norms; this violation results in feelings of sexual jealousy and rivalry. What constitutes an act of infidelity is dependent upon the exclusivity expectations within the relationship. In marital relationships, exclusivity expectations are commonly assumed although they are not always met. When they are not met, research has found that psychological damage can occur, including feelings of rage and betrayal, lowering of sexual and personal confidence, and damage to self-image.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>191139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1871" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-02-17">
<rating votes="26">6.30</rating>
<name>Morikawa Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16508.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1872" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-01-04">
<rating votes="47">8.32</rating>
<name>Ogata Rina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16509.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54800" type="main character in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="33">8.23</rating>
<name>Touma Kazusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54801" type="main character in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="22">6.18</rating>
<name>Ogiso Setsuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1961" picture="222838.jpg">Yonezawa Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54802" type="main character in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="11">4.34</rating>
<name>Kitahara Haruki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59607" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-10">
<name>Iizuka Takeya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142785.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59608" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-10">
<rating votes="4">5.27</rating>
<name>Mizusawa Io</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11003" picture="126729.jpg">Nakagami Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59609" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-10">
<name>Hayasaka Chikashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142787.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59610" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-10">
<name>Ogiso Takahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59611" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-10">
<rating votes="3">4.61</rating>
<name>Touma Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1917" picture="151688.jpg">Natsuki Rio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60768" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-25">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Ogiso Akina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="594" picture="156858.jpg">Ono Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60769" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-25">
<rating votes="1">1.81</rating>
<name>Ogiso Susumu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65523" type="appears in" update="2014-03-09">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Yanagihara Tomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39575" picture="168486.jpg">Kashiwagi Miyuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65547" type="appears in" update="2014-03-10">
<name>Miyazaki-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39587" picture="151395.jpg">Miyazaki Tomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65589" type="appears in" update="2014-03-11">
<name>Tsukumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35415" picture="146334.jpg">Chisuga Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65590" type="appears in" update="2014-03-11">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Hazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151458.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23608" picture="65179.jpg">Mochizuki Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65591" type="appears in" update="2014-03-11">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Izumi Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151459.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="65592" type="appears in" update="2014-03-11">
<name>Uehara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151460.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="65618" type="appears in" update="2014-03-13">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Fukaya Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fukaya Aki is a girl representing the student body at 33rd Graduation Ceremony of Houjou Academy.</description>
<picture>151514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29353" picture="186153.jpg">Yamazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="154506" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SOUND OF DESTINY</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sound of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sound of destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sound of Destiny</title>
<summary>The Light Music Club`s members are finally together, and with the School Fair only two weeks away they begin to practice.  With their schedule almost murderously tight, Kazusa proposes a plan to fix their biggest problem, Haruki`s guitar playing.  After a great deal of training, the three finally master their first song, White Album.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645493</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154507" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">軽音楽同好会, 再結成</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Light Music Club, Together Again</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le club de musique pop se reforme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keiongaku Doukoukai, Saikessei</title>
<summary>The "elite student in music room 2" turns out to be Haruki`s delinquent classmate, Kazusa Touma.  With his characteristic pushiness, he tries to get her to join the light music club.  But his pushiness backfires, and only makes her more annoyed.  Setsuna gets irritated... no, involved, and approaches Kazusa secretly.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645491</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154508" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">隣り合わせのピアノとギター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Piano and Guitar, Side by Side</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le piano et la guitare sont bons voisins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tonariawase no Piano to Guitar</title>
<summary>Haruki is entranced by Setsuna`s singing on the rooftop, and plots to get her to join the Light Music Club no matter what.  But she hates standing out, so convincing her is incredibly difficult.  Meanwhile, the club has an even bigger problem.  The elite student from Music Room 2 he was trying to persuade to join his club as the keyboard player isn`t a member of the Music Class, it`s a mysterious person whose class and identity are a total unknown.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645489</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154509" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">WHITE ALBUM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Album</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">White Album</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">White Album</title>
<summary>On a fall day a month before the school fair, Haruki Kitahara`s Light Music Club is about to be disbanded, thanks to trouble caused by their beautiful vocalist, Tomo Yanagihara.  Haruki tries to find a new member, but despite his own problems he`s forced to help with the School Fair Committee too.  There he meets Setsuna Ogiso, winner of the Miss Houjou contest for two years running, who wants to withdraw from this year`s contest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645487</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155115" update="2014-10-20">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155116" update="2014-10-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155765" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">触れあう心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Touching Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cœurs rapprochés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fureau Kokoro</title>
<summary>Setsuna realizes that Haruki has been staying at Kazusa`s house this whole time, and she reveals her true self to him: cowardly, introverted, and pathetic.  But Haruki accepts her as she is.  The boundary between them is broken, and the bonds between the three grow stronger as the school fair draws near.  But Kazusa is skipping sleep and food to work on her "last trick" before the school concert.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645495</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155839" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祭りの前</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Before the Fair</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Avant le festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matsuri no Mae</title>
<summary>Kazusa`s overworking finally catches up to her, and she collapses two days before the school fair.  Haruki cares for her as he continues to practice his guitar.  Kazusa, in a (possibly) fevered state, tells him about her troubled relationship with her mother Youko.  But meanwhile, at the concert rehearsal in the gym, Setsuna is separated from the other two and feels lonely and afraid her first time on stage.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645497</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155946" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪が解け, そして雪が降るまで (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Until the Snow Melts and Then Falls Again... (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La neige fond, puis... tombe la neige (1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki ga Toke, Soshite Yuki ga Furu made (Zenpen)</title>
<summary>Haruki hears about Kazusa`s moving from her mother, who she hadn`t been on good terms with.  He feels betrayed and angrily confronts her.  But his words force open the door to Kazusa`s heart, which she had desperately tried to keep closed so that the three of them could stay together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645505</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155947" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すれ違う心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Hearts Passing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cœurs croisés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surechigau Kokoro</title>
<summary>Ever since the school trip, Kazusa hasn`t come to school. Haruki tells himself that it`s because she`s practicing for the upcoming recital, but part of him is still struggling over what`s happened. And even when he`s with Setsuna that doesn`t go away. He finally invites Ogiso to a birthday party, with just the two of them, to finally come to terms with his feelings. But he doesn`t know that Kazusa is making a big decisions of her own...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645503</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155948" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やがて冬が始まって</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And Winter Finally Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bientôt l’hiver</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yagate Fuyu ga Hajimatte</title>
<summary>After the success of the School Fair concert, Haruki and Ogiso fall in love.  But the two of them still want to include Kazusa just like they have so far.  Kazusa answers by affirming her friendship with Setsuna, and on the surface things continue as before.  And before much time has passed at all, the second semester is over and winter break begins.  Setsuna and Kazusa drag Haruki on a Christmas hot springs vacation, and they enjoy their last big, fun, event.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645501</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155949" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最高の, 最後の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last and Greatest Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le meilleur jour, le dernier jour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikou no, Saigo no Hi</title>
<summary>The day of the festival is here, and the three are getting ready for their performance.  They sing, dance, and play on stage with all their hearts, and have the best time of their live.  But the wonderful fun they had leaves them sad and uncertain about the future.  And that night, Haruki is faced with a sudden and important choice.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645499</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156702" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪が解け, そして雪が降るまで (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Until the Snow Melts and Then Falls Again... (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La neige fond, puis... tombe la neige (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki ga Toke, Soshite Yuki ga Furu made (Kouhen)</title>
<summary>At last Haruki realives Kazuma`s true feelings, but while he`s confused at this sudden turn of events he can`t hide his joy that the girl he loved best likes him too.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645507</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156807" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">卒業</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fin d’études</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sotsugyou</title>
<summary>Haruki collapses after saying goodbye to Kasuza, and Setsuna, who he betrayed, comes to take care of him.  Haruki is too overcome with guilt to move, and Setsuna tries to pretend she knows nothing as she struggles with guilt of her own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645509</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156811" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届かない恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Love That Cannot Be</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un amour à sens unique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todokanai Koi</title>
<summary>At last, Haruki sleeps with Kazusa.  Her wish finally comes true, and she prepares to leave for Europe. Haruki takes Setsuna to the airport, hoping that they can all be together once again.  When the three are reunited, everyone remembers the best moment of their lives: the last song they sang at the school concert.  The title of the song was...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648469</identifier>
<identifier>white-album-2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162869" update="2016-07-21">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama (Setsuna Version)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162870" update="2016-07-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama (Kazusa Version)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162872" update="2014-10-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163644" update="2014-10-20">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163645" update="2014-10-20">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179047" update="2016-07-19">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama Selection Screen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
