<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="984" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>43</episodecount>
<startdate>1987-03-12</startdate>
<enddate>1988-02-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seikimatsu Kyuuseishu Densetsu: Hokuto no Ken 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Ken - Fist of the North Star 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hokuto no Ken 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">FOTNS 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hnk2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">世紀末救世主伝説 北斗の拳2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Fist of the North Star Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ken le survivant 2</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Ken il guerriero 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="983" type="Sequel">Shin Hokuto no Ken</anime>
<anime id="386" type="Prequel">Hokuto no Ken</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="3489" type="Direction">Ashida Toyoo</name>
<name id="4128" type="Original Work">Buronson</name>
<name id="4120" type="Original Work">Hara Tetsuo</name>
<name id="5291" type="Character Design">Suda Masami</name>
<name id="737" type="Work">Toei</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
</creators>
<description>Peace was brought to the land by http://anidb.net/ch7535 [Kenshirou] years ago. But now he is gone; merely a legend. Along with the peace came a distinction in classes, and soon a new era of violence began. A new tyranny arose, the fearsome fighters of the Gento Ko Ken style that fight for their Emperor of Heaven. Rin and Bart have grown up and formed a resistance called the Hokuto Army.
When times are at their worst, Kenshirou returns! Can he stop the Gento terror? And what is the secret of the mysterious Land of Shura?
Source: IMDB</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="534">6.74</permanent>
<temporary count="544">7.36</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>179050.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2199</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1356</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2082</identifier>
<identifier>qimgnd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fist_of_the_North_Star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>北斗の拳_(テレビアニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89213</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1700" parentid="2872" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>pirate</name>
<description>Pirates are people who attack ships on the high seas to rob others of their treasure. Well, at least usually. Other people calling themselves pirates are not unheard of, usually focusing on the freedom and romance involved in the piracy-related tropes and cliches. They may or may not be after the One Piece or a spaceship full of diamonds, too, if that`s what they see as treasure. Real-life pirates were extremely common a few centuries ago, and countries even sponsored their own pirates, called "privateers", to attack ships with flags of other countries. Nowadays, however, very few actual pirates still exist, and they rely more on terrorism and guerrilla warfare than anything else, demanding ransom in exchange for hostages instead of openly attacking the enemies with their swords. Another, more modern meaning for the word refers to people who illegally download copyrighted works they are not entitled to have a copy of. Be whichever it may, there are pirates around here. Arr, avast! Thar be pirates in these dark waters, matey!</description>
<picurl>126791.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3611" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-12-06">
<name>evil empire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4308" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-26">
<name>delayed death</name>
<description>The Final Battle has begun. The two opponents square off, and one of them hits the other with a series of mighty blows that would fell a mountain. But what`s this? Nothing seems to be happening! That`s when your opponent tells you that You Are Already Dead, right before your head explodes, your body separates in two, or you disintegrate into a fine mist. If you`re unlucky, only one of those happens. Sometimes, you may also discover that you were Made of Explodium.
A common trope in martial arts series, this involves some form of Finishing Move that does not take effect immediately. When used with martial arts, it may involve Pressure Point attacks or some form of Ki Attacks. Assassins may use Universal Poison to achieve a similar effect. In video games, Damage Over Time abilities often have this effect.
When used with swords there are a number of common variations, often shown with a Diagonal Cut. In sword duels, the two sides charge each other and attack. There will be a pause as the two pose, then one (or both) will fall down. Another one is for a Master Swordsman to perform a series of lightning-fast slashes, and then slowly and dramatically sheath their sword (with an audible *click*) before their attacks take effect.
This trope is not necessarily limited to martial arts, either. In more modern settings, gunshot wounds can often have this effect, since getting shot typically feels like getting punched hard and it is not uncommon for victims to take some time to realize it. This can be exploited for dramatic effect in war movies, where fatally wounded soldiers wander the battlefield before succumbing.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4387" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>good vs evil</name>
<description>A theme often used to relay lessons of morality. The fight between two entities, with one side representing all that is good and right and the other one all that is evil and wrong.
It’s one of the most conventional themes in literature, and sometimes considered to be a universal part of the human condition.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5821" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>sibling rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7087" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-07-02">
<rating votes="64">8.27</rating>
<name>Rei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rei is the successor of Nanto Suichouken, which is said to be the most elegant of the Nanto Seiken styles, and represents the Star of Justice.</description>
<picture>25347.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7535" type="main character in" update="2020-04-05">
<rating votes="536">8.67</rating>
<name>Kenshirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The 64th successor to the Hokuto Shinken art of combat, after his adopted father, Ryuken. He is considered "one of the greatest" successors in Hokuto Shinken history, due to his knowledge of certain legendary techniques like "Musou Tensei".</description>
<picture>26249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7539" type="appears in" update="2009-05-28">
<rating votes="83">6.96</rating>
<name>Raou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The eldest of the four Hokuto brothers, Raou is a conqueror who takes the mantle of Ken-oh.</description>
<picture>26259.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23" picture="188505.jpg">Utsumi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7543" type="appears in" update="2009-05-28">
<rating votes="20">6.59</rating>
<name>Yuria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26264.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3274" picture="24702.jpg">Yamamoto Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7547" type="appears in" update="2009-05-28">
<rating votes="21">4.05</rating>
<name>Lin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3733" picture="203229.jpg">Suzuki Tomiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7548" type="appears in" update="2009-05-28">
<rating votes="22">6.08</rating>
<name>Bat</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29289" picture="34528.jpg">Suzuki Mie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7549" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-01">
<rating votes="30">8.39</rating>
<name>Toki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27017.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7551" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-28">
<name>Rihaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7938" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-02">
<rating votes="12">8.43</rating>
<name>Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kenshirou`s first major adversary in the series. Shin represents the Star of Martyrdom and is the successor of the Nanto Koshuuken style. Shin was Kenshirou`s rival, who secretly desired Kenshirou`s fiancée Yuria from afar. After his mind was corrupted by Jagi, Shin challenged Kenshirou and defeated him, engraving the seven scars on his chest, subsequently taking off with Yuria by force.
He then forms the King organisation and builds Yuria the city of Southern Cross. However, he is unable to win Yuria`s love and after her failed suicide attempt, Shin entrusts her to the Nanto Goshasei for her protection. Sometime after, he is challenged by Kenshirou in his lair and is defeated. Refusing to die from Kenshirou`s technique, he takes his own life by jumping off the roof of his own palace, while maintaining that Yuria has died.</description>
<picture>27022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10870" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="16">4.66</rating>
<name>Souther</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Souther represents the "Star of Leadership", which rules over the other Nanto stars. His fighting style is Nanto Hou-ouken ("South Star Phoenix Fist), the strongest of the Nanto Seiken, which is a purely offensive style with no defensive stance. Souther was orphaned as an infant and was raised by the previous Hou-ouken successor, Oogai, who trained him during childhood. During his final training lesson, Souther unwillingly killed his master, who intentionally allowed himself to be killed by Souther. Traumatised by the event, Souther disavowed all feelings of love and compassion. After the Nuclear War, he takes on the title of Holy Emperor and enslaves children with his army in order to construct the Holy Cross Mausoleum, a shrine to his deceased master.
Kenshirou challenges Souther, but his Hokuto Shinken techniques proves to be ineffective against him and is brutally defeated and captured. Kenshirou escapes and challenges Souther again. This time, he learns the secret of Souther`s immunity (he has dextrocardia, affecting the locations of his pressure points), and is able to defeat him.</description>
<picture>32398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16038" type="appears in" update="2020-04-06">
<rating votes="5">4.87</rating>
<name>Mamiya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mamiya is a female village leader, who bears a striking resemblance to Kenshiro`s fiancee, Yuria. She recruits Ken and Rei as guardians of her village and later accompanies the two for several story arcs. She has limited martial art skills and fights using weapons such as bladed yo-yos and hidden knives.</description>
<picture>245676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3250" picture="24693.jpg">Fujita Toshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16039" type="appears in" update="2010-03-23">
<rating votes="5">5.82</rating>
<name>Airi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Airi is Rei`s younger sister, who was kidnapped by Jagi on the day of her wedding and then sold to slavery. The Fang Clan managed to get a hold of her after killing her previous captor and used her as leverage against Rei.</description>
<picture>45058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2362" picture="22137.jpg">Andou Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38451" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-07">
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<name>Akashachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30844">Kakuda Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38452" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-07">
<rating votes="2">6.37</rating>
<name>Ein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76818.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3370" picture="74440.jpg">Yamaguchi Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38453" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-07">
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<name>Falco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38454" type="appears in" update="2011-11-07">
<name>Han</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76820.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3220" picture="24200.jpg">Totani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38455" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-07">
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<name>Hyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76821.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="544" picture="238510.jpg">Ogawa Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38456" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-07">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Jakou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38457" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-07">
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<name>Juukei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3059" picture="203228.jpg">Miyauchi Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38458" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-07">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Kaiou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76824.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23" picture="188505.jpg">Utsumi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38459" type="appears in" update="2011-11-07">
<name>Kaiser</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38460" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-07">
<name>Leia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38461" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-07">
<name>Lui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3890" picture="186170.jpg">Takamori Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38462" type="appears in" update="2011-11-07">
<name>Rock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="354" picture="25810.jpg">Hironaka Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38463" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-07">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Shachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38464" type="appears in" update="2011-11-07">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Shouki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38465" type="appears in" update="2011-11-07">
<name>Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69661" type="appears in" update="2014-08-25">
<name>Kokuougou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160124.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70921" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-26">
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<name>Bat</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3282" picture="24710.jpg">Nanba Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70922" type="main character in" update="2014-10-26">
<name>Lin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3940" picture="54324.jpg">Tominaga Miina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70938" type="appears in" update="2014-10-26">
<name>Basque</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70944" type="appears in" update="2014-10-26">
<name>Geira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3310" picture="24332.jpg">Mizutori Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="37553" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時は流れまた時代が動いた...!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Past Is Gone. The Dawn of the New Age!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le temps passe. Une ère nouvelle commence !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">...e la vita continua</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki wa Nagare Mata Jidai ga Ugoita...!!</title>
<summary>Bat is now a brave young man, and Lin has grown into a beautiful woman. Together, they found the North Star Army, to save the people suffering under Jakoh and the Celestial Emperor`s tyranny. But leading an army of greenhorns turns out to be an uphill battle fraught with peril. They continue to await the return of Kenshiro, the savior of legend. Rumors spread far that Ken is dead. Meanwhile, in a poor, squalid village, a "drifter" appears, looking haggard. That drifter is saved by a young boy named Haru, who hasn`t lost his sense of justice or compassion even when living in a poor village.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512504</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37554" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">救世主, 北より来たる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Savior Comes from the North!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sauveur vient du Nord !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La salvezza viene dal nord</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuuseishu, Kita yori Kitaru!!</title>
<summary>Lin and Bat go undercover, but henchmen of the area commander, Bask, capture an innocent boy and girl after mistaking them for Lin and Bat. The callous Bask seeks to execute the girl as an example. Lin and Bat, ready to give up their lives, reveal themselves out in the open. Then, a man suddenly appears... Kenshiro, riding Raoh`s beloved steed Kokuoh!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512508</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37555" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あいつはいつ目覚めるのか...!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When Will He Awaken?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quand va-t-il se réveiller ?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ritorno di fiamma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aitsu wa Itsu Mezameru no ka...!?</title>
<summary>The "Drifter" saved by Haru rests up at a bar where Haru works. Then comes Geld, a Celestial Emperor Army executioner. He took great pleasure in hunting down the remnants of the "Red Dragon Party" that once stood in revolt against the Celestial Emperor. Haru tries to defeat Geld, even if it means suicide for himself, but then the drifter pulls off his cloak, revealing Kenshiro, successor to the Divine Fist of the North Star!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512506</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37556" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の賞金稼ぎアイン! 俺がケンシロウの首をとる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Bounty Hunter, Ein! Kenshiro`s Head Is Mine!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ein, le mystérieux mercenaire : « J`aurai la peau de Kenshiro ! »</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Cacciatori di taglie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Shoukin Kasegi Ein! Ore ga Kenshirou no Kubi o Toru!!</title>
<summary>With Kenshiro finally joining forces with the North Star Army, everyone in the army feels strongly reassured. In the meantime, reports of Kenshiro reach the area commander Geira. Ein, a bounty hunter coming to claim a bounty, hears from Geira that the price on Kenshiro`s head is staggering, boasts loudly that he`ll defeat him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512510</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37557" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">また一つ暗殺拳! その名は元斗皇拳!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Art of Assassination! The Imperial Fist of the Source Star Is the Name!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une autre technique de combat : l`école du « Gento »</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La scuola imperiale di Cento</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mata hitotsu ansatsuken! Sono na wa Gentokouken!!</title>
<summary>Kenshiro`s comrade-in-arms, Rei of the South Star Waterfowl Fist, is buried in a prospering town. But that town, home to Mamiya and Airi, comes under attack by Solia of the Purple Light, a general of the Celestial Emperor Army. At the same time, the North Star Army is in the final stages of an operation to capture another area. Spotting the town in peril, Kenshiro runs to save it!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512512</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37558" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天帝怒る! ファルコ, 北斗を地上より根絶やしにせよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rage of the Celestial Emperor! Falco, Obliterate the North Star from Earth!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`empereur est fou de rage : « Falco, extermine le Hokuto ! »</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`armata di Hokuto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tentei Ikaru! Falco, Hokuto o Chijou Yori Nedayashi ni Seyo!!</title>
<summary>Awaiting the North Star Army is a general of the Celestial Emperor Army, the strongest practitioner of the Imperial Fist of the Source Star, Golden Falco. He singlehandedly routs the entire North Star Army. In exchange for sparing all of their lives, he demands the death of their leader. Bat tries to protect Lin by claiming he is their leader, but Falco sees right through it and identifies Lin as the true leader. What is the tie that binds Falco and Lin!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512514</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37559" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイン危うし! 愛する女に魔の手が伸びた!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ein in Danger! Hands of Evil Reach for His Love!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ein est en danger. Le diable a mis la main sur sa bien-aimée.</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Quando si vuole bene...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ein Ayaushi! Ai Suru Onna ni Ma no Te ga Nobita</title>
<summary>Going on the justification that if Ken spared his life, he couldn`t be that bad of a guy, Bat accepts Ein`s invitation to join forces, and the two capture an area by themselves. But that would lead to tragedy, as the commander of the area they captured, Beron, abducts Ein`s girl, Asuka, in vengeance. Ein`s "lady love" turns out to be a little girl! What is their relation? And what is Ein`s reason for fighting?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512520</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37560" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">南斗の魂燃ゆ! 壮絶ハーン兄弟!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wrath of the South Star! The Illustrious Harn Brothers!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`âme du Nanto brûle. La mort héroïque des frères Harn</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I falchi di Nanto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanto no Tamashii Moyu! Souzetsu HaRn Kyoudai!</title>
<summary>The North Star`s leader must be eliminated... But Lin was once saved a long time ago. Feeling chagrin at this twist of fate, Falco is ready to eliminate Lin regardless. Witnessing this, the criminal Harn brothers urge the boy guarding them to break the concrete holding them imprisoned. They turn out to be successors to one of the 108 styles of the South Star that Falco slaughtered, the South Star Twin Hawk Fist.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512516</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37561" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">元斗の猛将ファルコ! そこにはラオウの影が...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Falco, the Brave General of the Source Star! There Lies the Shadow of Raoh...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Falco, le général du Gento ! L`ombre de Raoul...</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La capitale dell`Impero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gento no Moushou Falco! Soko ni wa Raoh no Kage ga...</title>
<summary>The North Star Army is joined by Ein, now a former bounty hunter, and the seasoned general Rihaku. They set out for the Imperial Capital. Rihaku speaks of Falco`s past. Falco, who held his own against Raoh, once sacrificed his own leg to save a town. Meanwhile, inside the Imperial Capital, General Shoki of the Red Light sparks a revolt against Jakoh.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512518</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37562" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アインの挽歌! 誇りをすてて生きるより熱き死を!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Elegy for Ein! Die Bravely Than Live Without Honor!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`élégie de Ein. Plutôt mourir qu`être esclave !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La signora dei cieli</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ein no Banka! Hokori o Sutete Ikiru Yori Atsuki Shi o!!</title>
<summary>Kenshiro and Falco, both much worse for wear, are put in dire peril by Jakoh`s cowardly schemes. Having already sustained heavy damage all over, both men come under fire from Jakoh`s gigantic spears! Lin`s group desperately seeks to escape from their cave quickly in order to tell Falco and Kenshiro that they have no more reason to fight. Ein hammers into an iron stake with his fist until breaking through to a water vein, and the underground water pressure lets them escape. The punch he stakes his life on finally creates a miracle!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512526</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37563" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ついに天帝の正体が見えた!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Celestial Emperor Is Finally Revealed!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Enfin, l`empereur apparaît !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`imperatore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsui ni Tentei no Shoutai ga Mieta!</title>
<summary>As the battle between Kenshiro and Falco heats up, Lin senses the Celestial Emperor`s voice. The group falls into a trap set by Jakoh and falls deep underground. There, they discover Celestial Emperor Lui. Lin and Lui turn out to be twin sisters. As it turns out, in accordance with the law that there may only be one Celestial Emperor, Falco was ordered by Jakoh to eliminate the infant Lin, but he secretly saved her...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512524</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37564" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帝都にこだます天帝の鳴き声! ファルコはいずこに...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Emperor`s Cries Echoes Through the Imperial Capital! Falco, Where Have You Gone?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les sanglots de l`empereur trahi ! Où est Falco ?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`ultimo ostacolo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teito ni Kodamasu Tentei no Nakigoe! Falco wa Izukoni...</title>
<summary>Jakoh decrees to Falco that if he wants to save the Celestial Emperor, he must strike down Kenshiro. Reasoning that if he lost to Kenshiro, Jakoh would pin all the blame on the Celestial Emperor and make a break for it, Falco hands one of his loyal henchmen and his lover Myu the detonator switch to a bomb in the Imperial Capital, then sets out for battle. Finally, the stage is set for a major confrontation between him and Kenshiro!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512522</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37565" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帝都崩壊! ジャコウ, せめて地獄で夢を見よ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fall of the Imperial Capital! Jakoh, You Can Dream in Hell!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La capitale s`effondre ! Jakou le démon, va en enfer !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Rapimento</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teito Houkai! Jakou, Semete Jigoku de Yume o Miyo!!</title>
<summary>Having lost his trump card, the Celestial Emperor, Jakoh is left naked and alone. Abandoned by his henchmen, he gets obliterated by a furious Falco. The joy of peace returning is short-lived, though. It is found out that Taiga of the Green Light has taken Lin and is trying to cross the Sea of Death. Ein`s life leaves a powerful impression on Kenshiro, and Kenshiro grows determined to pursue Taiga. A new battle is just beginning to unfold...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512528</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37566" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">果てしなき試練! ケンシロウ海を渡る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ordeal Never Ends! Kenshiro Crosses the Ocean!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À l`épreuve de la mort ! Kenshiro traverse la mer !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Pirati</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hateshinaki Shiren! Kenshirou Umi o Wataru!</title>
<summary>Lin is taken to a land beyond the Sea of Dead, "The Land of the Asura." In this land where might determines everything, there exists a style called the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist. Kenshiro, crossing the sea in a pirate ship, learns that the ship`s captain, the one-eyed, one-armed, one-legged Akashachi, once raided the Land of Asura, but was forced to flee and left his son behind. Upon arriving at the Land of the Asura, the first thing he sees is Falco, collapsed and gravely wounded by an Asura.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512530</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37567" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">何が待つ暗黒大陸! そこは伝説の修羅の国!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Awaits on the Continent of Darkness? There Lies the Legendary Land of Asura!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Que réservent les ténèbres ? Le légendaire pays sanglant !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La terra dei demoni</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nani ga Matsu Ankoku Tairiku! Soko wa Densetsu no Shura no Kuni!</title>
<summary>Falco was defeated by a nameless Asura due to losing his artificial leg in the middle of battle. For the sake of his honor, Falco challenges the Asura to a rematch. To deal with the Asura, who burrows underground, Falco uses the Ruinous Freezing Yellow Threat Stance to freeze the surface of the ground, then waits for the Asura to pop up. With Falco throwing himself into the fight fully ready to die, can his Imperial Fist of the Source Star take down the Asura...!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512532</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37573" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弟ケンの危機! やさしきヒョウよ今こそ心を開け!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Brother Ken in Danger! Hyoh, Open Up Your Kind Soul!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ton frère, Ken, est en danger ! Hyo, tu es bon, alors ouvre ton cœur !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Pericolo mortale</title>
<summary>Kenshiro loses badly to Kaioh. Even Ken`s ultimate technique, the Unconcious Transmigration, doesn`t seem to slow Kaioh down. Kaioh declares that the sealed memories which only Hyoh knows are the only key to defeating him in existence. Meanwhile, Jukei struggles to bring back the old, compassionate Hyoh, the one who thought strongly of his younger brother as a child, and stubbornly refused to ever divulge the location of the hidden technique. To do this, he stakes his own life upon hitting a destructive point: Jukei`s ultimate destructive point. This goes beyond his expectations and drastically transfigures Hyoh`s...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512556</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37574" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">問答無用の男達! 遂に荒野の七人がケンを襲う!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Men Beyond Reasons! The Band of Seven Attacks Kenshiro!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ils ne veulent rien savoir ! Les sept cavaliers attaquent Kenshiro !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La leggenda continua</title>
<summary>Seeking to become the third general of Asura, Gammon, Asura of Sasori, takes Rock`s group hostage in order to ambush Kenshiro. Kenshiro sees the suffering in Rock`s eyes, and springs the trap deliberately in order to draw the real culprit, Gammon, out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512548</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37575" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">非情の予言! ケンシロウお前は救世主になれない!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Cruel Prophecy! Kenshiro, You Cannot Be the Savior!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Terrible nouvelle ! Kenshiro, tu ne peux pas être le sauveur !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il liberatore</title>
<summary>Kenshiro is perplexed by Han`s dying words, that he can never become a savior. But the Land of Asura remains unaware of the fact that the news of Raoh`s coming is wrong, and chaos persists. In the midst of this, a villager named Kosem who eagerly awaits Raoh`s coming decides to start an all-out revolt. But the Asuras realize that Raoh will not come, and the villagers are massacred at their hands. Arriving during this, Kenshiro hears someone demanding to know why he is here and not Raoh...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512544</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37576" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロック死の伝達! ケンシロウ友の命を受けとめよ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rock`s Message of Death! Kenshiro, Hang On to Your Friend`s Life!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mort de Rock ! Kenshiro, ils sont morts pour toi !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Lotta impari</title>
<summary>With the death of the third general of Asura, Han, the second general of Asura Hyoh departs in person, at the head of his army, to suppress Kenshiro. Learning of the situation, the master of the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist, Jukei, shockingly claims that Kenshiro cannot win against Hyoh. Kenshiro is Hyoh`s younger brother by blood, and furthermore, Hyoh has a hidden secret...!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512550</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37577" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">善か悪か? 謎の北斗琉拳現わる!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Good or Evil? The Mysterious North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist Appears!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le bien ou le mal ? L`énigme de Hokuto-ryûken !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Killer</title>
<summary>Alph of the Hourglass, an Asura permitted to bear a name, won a battle between Asuras, and in doing so won the right to take Lin. He is charged with eliminating Kenshiro, and uses his poison cape to paralyze Kenshiro and pummel him with attacks. However, the one who lost when two minutes pass turns out to be Alph. Meanwhile, Lin is taken away by Shachi, a wielder of the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512534</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37578" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">馬上の勇士ロック! 俺はケンシロウを信じない!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rock, The Hero on Horseback! I Don`t Believe in Kenshiro!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rock, le cavalier sans peur ! Je ne crois pas en Kenshiro !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I sette cavalieri</title>
<summary>With Raoh`s legend in shambles, tyranny and brutal suppression of revolts has grown worse than ever. Kosem`s son Rock, believing Raoh would come, returned to his village with the intent of joining the uprising, but is horror-stricken upon finding out about the death of his father and the collapse of Raoh`s legend. Rock decides to carry on Raoh`s legend himself, and gathers fellow soldiers to form Raoh`s Army. They boldly dare to challenge the Asuras, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512546</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37579" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の出会いヒョウとケン! いまだ兄は弟を知らず!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Destined Encounter of Hyoh and Ken! Both Are Yet to Know Their Secrets!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les destins se croisent : Hyo rencontre Ken ! Il ne reconnaît pas son petit frère !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Prova di amicizia</title>
<summary>Shachi is determined to protect Kenshiro, whom he believes to be the savior. He continues his journey, disguising himself as a rag and hiding Kenshiro in a coffin. Kaioh is consumed with fear of Kenshiro`s limitless potential, and instructs his henchmen to search for Lin. For her part, after getting swallowed by underground currents, Lin is rescued by Kaioh`s younger sister, Sayaka. Meanwhile, heavily scarred by the killing of Jukei, Hyoh seeks out Sayaka to mend his wounds, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512564</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37580" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新世紀創造主宣言! 俺の名は魔神カイオウ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Announcing the Creator of the New Century! My Name Is Demon Kaioh!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Créateur du nouveau monde ! Mon nom est Kaio le démon !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Maestro e discepolo</title>
<summary>Jukei, master of the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist, awaits Hyoh, who is still in search of Kenshiro. Jukei, believing Kenshiro cannot win against Hyoh, risks his life to try and restore Hyoh`s memories. Meanwhile, Shachi, in pursuit of his own ambition, hands Lin over to the first general, Kaioh. But Kaioh, after taking Lin to his castle, gives off an evil fighting spiritual energy, and declares himself the creator of the new century.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512552</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37581" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴かれたケンシロウの秘密! 修羅の国は母の国!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kenshiro`s Secret Is Revealed! The Land of Asura Is His Motherland!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le terrible secret de Ken. Le pays des démons est sa terre natale.</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Casa, dolce casa</title>
<summary>Due to Shachi`s scheming, Kenshiro`s presence becomes known all across the land as "Raoh`s invasion." The Asuras cower, and the people eagerly await liberation. Relieved to hear this, Jukei tells of his past... He taught the three generals of Asura the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist, and led to the creation of the Land of Asura. Furthermore, this Land of Asura was Raoh and Kenshiro`s birthplace...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512542</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37582" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔の封印! それが北斗宗家ニ千年の悲劇を語る!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seal of the Devil! 2000 Year Tragedy of the North Star Is Revealed!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sceau du démon ! Le Hokuto originel, 2 000 ans de tragédies !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il colpo segreto</title>
<summary>Jukei seeks to restore Hyoh`s sealed-off memories, and draw out the "Key" to destroying the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist, the primary thing Kenshiro would need to win against Kaioh. Kenshiro and Hyoh belong to the main family of the North Star, and Hyoh was the only person to learn the location of the hidden technique. But even after coming to terms with reality, no technique seems to be able to break the seal on his memories. Meanwhile, Kenshiro, in his quest to rescue Lin, sets foot in Kaioh`s castle...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512554</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37583" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カイオウつかの間の勝利宣言! 北斗の幻が彼を襲う!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaioh`s Declaration of Victory! The Phantom of the North Star Attacks!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Victoire éphémère pour Kaio ! L`esprit du Hokuto lui fait face !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il sacrificio dei pirati</title>
<summary>Kenshiro bears heavy damage from his fight with Kaioh. Under the pretext of giving Akashachi a burial at sea, Shachi seeks to withdraw and give Kenshiro a chance to heal. Kaioh returns to prevent that, and as Shachi`s group starts down the waterway, Kaioh once again appears before them! Is this the end of the line!? Shachi is ready to throw in the towel, but suddenly, Kaioh`s evil fighting spiritual energy gets extinguished. Kenshiro, whose pulse should have stopped, stands before them...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512560</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37584" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">処刑台のケンシロウ! 遂に天は海神を走らせた!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kenshiro on the Execution Stand! The Heaven Has Unleashed the God of the Sea!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kenshiro condamné à mort ! Le Ciel envoie le dieu de la mer !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il ritorno del pirata rosso</title>
<summary>Having lost to Kaioh, Kenshiro is cruelly crucified. Shachi watches protectively from the shadows, but then challenges Kaioh, who wields a superior North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist, to a direct confrontation. However, Shachi doesn`t stand a chance against him. Just as Kaioh is about to deliver the finishing blow to Shachi, Akashachi showers him in concentrated sulfuric acid, stalling him long enough to rescue Kenshiro and Shachi. Lin gets swept out of sight in the current... And Akashachi, while trying to finish Kaioh off, meets his end at Kaioh`s hands.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512558</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37585" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">羅将ハン! お前は白き雪も紅に染める男!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The General of Asura, Han! The Man Who Stains White Snow into Crimson!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le démon Han. L`homme qui teint la neige en rouge !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Neve rosso sangue</title>
<summary>Shachi takes Lin to general of Aura Han`s castle, seeking to use Kenshiro to wear down Han for an easy defeat. In the guise of a rag, Shachi offers Lin up to Han as a pretense to get close to him. Han already sees through Shachi`s disguise, and the two quickly resort to battle, though Shachi opts to make a hasty retreat after confirming Han`s strength for himself. Meanwhile, Kenshiro is already inside Han`s castle...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512538</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37586" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">修羅の国に救世主伝説走る! その名はラオウ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legend of the Savior of Asura! His Name Is Raoh!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La légende du sauveur se propage ! Son nom est Raoul !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il ritorno di Raoul</title>
<summary>While watching Kenshiro and Han`s fight from the sidelines, Shachi reflects upon how in this land, one must be strong to survive. After apprenticing himself to an old master of the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist, Shachi decided to become a devil, in direct opposition to his lover Leia, who preached the value of love. He refined his skill under Jukei, who claimed that one day a savior would bring change to this land. But the name of the savior Jukei spoke of turns out to be Raoh!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512540</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37587" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あえて世紀末に愛を説く! その名はレイア!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Is Preached in the Century`s End! Her Name Is Leia!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Elle ose parler de l`amour à la fin du siècle ! Son nom est Leïa !</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Amore rubato</title>
<summary>Shachi is a wielder of the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist. His goal is to overthrow the three generals of Asura who rule the Land of Asura. Meanwhile, Kenshiro meets Shachi`s former lover, Leia, who tells him to kill Shachi, now steeped in evil. Shachi is stopped during his pursuit. In a fight between Kaizel, who can steal a man`s insides without damaging his exterior, and Shachi, what will the outcome be!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512536</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37588" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケンシロウの挑戦状! オレには2度の敗北はない!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kenshiro`s Challenge! Never Be Defeated Twice!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi de Kenshiro ! Cette fois tu ne me battras pas !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Desiderio di vendetta</title>
<summary>Kaioh kills his own younger sister, Sayaka, and spreads word that Kenshiro is the one behind it. Hyoh is consumed by powerful hatred. Kaioh schemes to bring the main family of the North Star to an end. Right in the middle of the funeral for Sayaka being held in Kaioh`s castle, an Asura named Gyoko`s battle train crashes in. Gyoko, rolling in front of Kaioh, bears a message from Kenshiro: I am never defeated twice! Hyoh, believing that Kenshiro killed Sayaka, is consumed in powerful hatred upon hearing that, and takes his first step towards the dark world...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512568</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37589" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カイオウ悪魔の選択! 俺の全身には冷血が脈打つ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaioh`s Evil Decision! Cold Blood Runs Through My Body!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le choix de Kaioh le démon ! Un froid glacial parcourt tout mon corps !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il risveglio di Ken</title>
<summary>Shachi finally brings Kenshiro to a safe haven. Around that time, Commander of Asura Kain, having received instructions to search for Shachi and Kenshiro, sets about his search in hopes of attaining the coveted position of third general. The cabin where Shachi arrived finally gets searched, but due to poor timing, the only one there is the cabin`s elderly caretaker. Asura henchmen intrude inside... Meanwhile, in order to draw Hyoh to the dark world, Kaioh takes his own younger sister by blood, Sayaka.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512566</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37590" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴君ヒョウと悲しき側近! 誰が彼を止めるのか!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tyrant Hyoh and His Sorrowful Aide! Who Will Stop Him Now?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hyo le tyran et les larmes du garde ! Qui pourra l`arrêter ?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La rivelazione</title>
<summary>Having ventured into the dark world, Hyoh`s personality becomes evil and twisted. Upon seeing how he had changed, his adoring, devoted Vice General Nagato is stricken with unbearable grief. Nagato encounters Shachi and Kenshiro, both heavily injured from fighting Kaioh. Despite their positions as enemies, Nagato senses something heart-stirring in Kenshiro`s eyes, and hides the two of them in his house...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512570</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37591" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">北斗存亡の危機! カイオウの魔の手が天帝にのびた!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The North Star on the Brink of Death! Kaioh Reaches Out for the Celestial Emperor!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`école Hokuto est en danger ! Kaio convoite la fille de l`empereur céleste !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Scontro crudele</title>
<summary>In the midst of Kenshiro and Hyoh`s back-and-forth battle, when Kenshiro hits a pressure point, Hyoh uses an evil art to gouge out his own flesh where the pressure point is located. With the battle between Kenshiro and Hyoh, Kaioh is more confident than ever in the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist`s new century. When he has Lin brought before him, Kaioh`s real face surfaces amidst his evil fighting spiritual energy. His face bears an eerie resemblance to Raoh`s... Of course it would - Kaioh is Raoh`s older brother!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512574</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37592" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙の兄弟再会! ケンシロウ, 俺はお前を待っていた!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tearful Reunion of the Brothers! Kenshiro, I`ve Been Waiting for You!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les deux frères se retrouvent ! Kenshiro je t`attendais !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Barlumi di memoria</title>
<summary>Hyoh`s evil fighting spiritual energy has vanished! But his memories haven`t completely returned. His mind clouded with memories of his childhood departure from Kenshiro, Hyoh turns his fist upon Kenshiro once more. Shachi senses danger and finally acts. As Kenshiro catches a glimpse of tears in Hyoh`s eyes, his fist slackens, and to save him, he rushes Hyoh from behind! Then the defeated Hyoh says something unexpected...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512576</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37593" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しき愛の犠牲者! これがカイオウ悪の原点だ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tragic Victim of Love! Kaioh`s Foundation of Evil!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Elle se sacrifie par amour ! Voilà d`où vient la haine de Kaio !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Amore contro odio</title>
<summary>The place Kaioh chooses for a showdown is the Swamp of Demon, a place teeming with evil fighting spiritual energy, and the place where his evil began. Leia gives Kenshiro Shachi`s protector as a memento, and Kenshiro sets foot into the swamp alone. There, the tragic past of Kaioh and Raoh`s mother, and Kenshiro and Hyoh`s mother, is revealed! Then, right before the battle, Kaioh hits a destructive point on Lin! What terrifying effect will it have...!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512582</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37594" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の戦士シャチ死す! 友よ, 愛こそすべてと知れ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fall of Shachi, Warrior of Love! Love Is Everything, My Friends!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mort de Shachi, le guerrier de l`amour ! Sache que sans l`amour, l`homme n`est rien !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La morte di Ork</title>
<summary>Shachi is believed to have already died fighting Kaioh to protect Leia. But the female visages in the Holy Temple of Asura create a mysterious resonance, and with tears in his eyes, Shachi rises again. Even as heavily overwhelmed as he had been, he launches a counterattack so ferocious that it even shocks Kaioh. It all comes from the power of love... Kaioh, now convinced that the main family`s ultimate technique is love, seeks to prove the superiority of the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist that he uses for his evil ultimate art.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512580</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37595" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャチ愛の戦い! カイオウ, それを愚かと笑うのか!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shachi`s Battle for Love! Kaioh Will Ridicule with Laughter!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shachi se bat au nom de l`amour ! Pour Kaio, tout ceci est ridicule !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La statua</title>
<summary>Hyoh regains his memories, and upon hearing of Hyoh`s reconciliation with Kenshiro, Kaioh does a complete about-face. Heavy with anger towards Shachi at having made their reconciliation possible, Kaioh orders the Asuras to hunt Shachi down. Meanwhile, Hyoh has recovered from the worst of his injuries, and tells Kenshiro and Shachi that there is a hidden technique sealed within the Holy Temple of Asura, the sanctum of the main family of the North Star. Leia and Lin`s love opens the way to the hidden technique`s hiding place, and underground, under the watchful gaze of female visages, Kaioh and Shachi do battle...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512578</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37596" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1987-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">骨肉の兄弟対決! もうヒョウの瞳に涙は帰らない!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle of the Blood Brothers! Tears Will Never Return to Hyoh.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le combat des deux frères ! Les yeux de Hyo ne verseront plus jamais de larmes !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Duello fraterno</title>
<summary>Kenshiro`s group hears that Hyoh is exploiting villagers to bring back the birthplace of the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist, the Holy Temple of Asura, from the bottom of a swamp. Kenshiro faces off with Hyoh, who has gone there and turned into a demon. While Kenshiro senses that Hyoh is his elder brother, Hyoh`s memories remain sealed and lost, and Hyoh, seeing Kenshiro only as Sayaka`s murderer, is consumed anew with vengeance. When Kaioh hears reports of the fighting, he lets out resounding laughter at how smoothly things are going for him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512572</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37597" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最終話 序章! リンの運命を握る第3の男が現れた!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prologue to the Final Episode! A Third Man Appears to Determine Lin`s Fate!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Avant-dernier épisode ! L`apparition d`un troisième homme va influencer le destin de Lynn !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il ritorno di Bart</title>
<summary>Kaioh`s fist no longer has any effect on Kenshiro. In contrast to the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist, whose style has already been perfected and has no further progress, the Divine Fist of the North Star is a style which continues to constantly evolve on the battlefield. Thus, by using the hidden technique Kenshiro acquired, the art to deflect the North Star Lapis Lazuli Fist, it is rendered completely ineffective. Seeing his chances of winning slipping away, Kaioh casts off the armor he wears to contain his evil fighting spiritual energy, and goes all-out in a last ditch battle! Meanwhile, Black Yaksha meets his end protecting Lin, and Hyoh is in dire peril once more! But then, some unexpected backup arrives...!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512590</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37598" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばケンシロウ!! さらば北斗神拳!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Episode: Farewell, Kenshiro!! Farewell, the Divine Fist of the North Star!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu, Kenshiro !! Adieu, Hokuto-shinken !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Addio, Ken</title>
<summary>After saving Lin and Hyoh, the North Star Army rushes towards the place where the ferocious battle between Kenshiro and Kaioh is unfolding. Kaioh has cast off his armor and fights desperately using his evil fighting spiritual energy, while Kenshiro shows that he has the advantage by far. But Kaioh, who can`t even hurt him with his evil fighting spiritual energy now, borrows his mother`s strength for one final blow! Kaioh gets sent flying into the sky by a geyser erupting from beneath the grave, and when he swoops down upon Kenshiro, Kenshiro`s fist slams into him! Can the history of fate that has laste since the era of the main family of the North Star be put to rest, at long last!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512588</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37599" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最終章 残り3回! これが北斗宗家2000年の血の歴史!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Chapter: The Last Three Episodes! Here Is the 2,000 Year-Old History of the Main Family of the North Star!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Plus que trois épisodes ! L`histoire sanglante du Hokuto dure depuis plus de 2 000 ans !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I due cugini</title>
<summary>Kenshiro and Kaioh`s deadly struggle continues. But Kenshiro is put in dire peril when his body becomes paralyzed by gas in a cave beneath the Swamp of Demon. Meanwhile, learning of the destructive point hit on Lin, the Asuras go after her. Danger draws closer and closer to Lin as she begins to regain consciousness. Will Hyoh make it in time!? In the midst of battle, Kenshiro learns that Kaioh also bears the blood of the main family of the North Star. There is a story behind that, a tragic tale about the main family of the North Star from before the Divine Fist of the North Star was founded...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512586</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="37600" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カイオウ屈辱の歴史! 天はリンの運命もぬりかえる!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaioh`s Disgraceful Past! The Heaven Recreate`s Lin`s Destiny!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kaio a été humilié dans sa jeunesse ! Le Ciel s`émeut du destin de Lynn !!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`anello della morte</title>
<summary>Because of the destructive point that Kaioh hit, when Lin wakes up, she may very well fall in love with the first person she sees, regardless of whom it may be. Kenshiro, shaking with rage, fights with Kaioh. Realizing Lin`s peril, Hyoh once more overstrains his heavily injured body to save Lin... What is the disgrace Hyoh speaks of, that twisted Kaioh as a child!? And what of the feelings Raoh told Kenshiro that he had towards Kaioh!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>512584</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-north-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="46873" update="2006-02-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">9.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46874" update="2007-07-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">2.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139745" update="2012-05-20">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2012-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">英語版総集編 北斗の拳 第6部 カイオウ編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fist of the North Star: The Kaio Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eigoban Soushuuhen Hokuto no Ken Dai 6 Bu Kaiou-hen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
