<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9842" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1986-02-21</startdate>
<enddate>1986-02-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Soukou Kihei Votoms: Woodo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Armored Trooper Votoms - Uoodo Recap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Soukou Kihei Votoms: Uoodo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Soukou Kihei Votoms: Udo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">装甲騎兵ボトムズ ウド</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9843" type="Sequel">Soukou Kihei Votoms: Kummen</anime>
<anime id="1698" type="Full Story">Soukou Kihei Votoms</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.sunrise-anime.jp/sunrise-inc/works/detail.php?cid=218</url>
<creators>
<name id="661" type="Character Design">Shioyama Norio</name>
<name id="1694" type="Chief Direction">Takizawa Toshifumi</name>
<name id="660" type="Original Work">Takahashi Ryousuke</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Plan">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="660" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Ryousuke</name>
<name id="660" type="Direction">Takahashi Ryousuke</name>
<name id="5283" type="Music">Inui Hiroki</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="23">6.89</permanent>
<temporary count="23">6.32</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>157362.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12337</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=218</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>800</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>162300</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15209" type="appears in" update="2018-09-22">
<rating votes="30">4.09</rating>
<name>Coconna Batora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3732" picture="25105.jpg">Kawanami Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15211" type="appears in" update="2018-09-22">
<rating votes="22">3.85</rating>
<name>Vanilla Batora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15212" type="appears in" update="2017-06-05">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Bouleuse Gouto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3301" picture="24327.jpg">Tomita Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15676" type="appears in" update="2018-12-04">
<rating votes="168">8.80</rating>
<name>Chirico Cuvie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As the central character around which Votoms revolves, Chirico Cuvie is haunted by two pasts—one he cannot remember and another he cannot forget. He has no memory of his life prior to his 10th year, in which he lived on the planet Sunsa with adoptive parents who found him in a refugee center and were studying his unusual healing abilities—until they were killed in the first of many enemy invasions. Chirico witnessed their deaths, and survived burns that would have killed an ordinary human. But over the subsequent years, he proved himself to be far from ordinary.
Enlisting in the Melkian army as an Armored Trooper pilot, Chirico distinguished himself in many battles against the http://anidb.net/ch90340 [Balarant] and was transferred at age 16 to the elite http://anidb.net/ch90343 [Red Shoulder Battalion]. There, he was scrutinized by the commanding officer, Colonel Yoran Peruzen. Peruzen had been watching Chirico for many years, and had become convinced that Chirico`s miraculous recuperative powers made him immortal; a supreme survivor. After nearly ending Peruzen`s life, Chirico was thrown into the final battle of Sunsa. He wasn`t supposed to survive it, but he did. This was the battle that brought the Hundred Years War to an end, and the Red Shoulder Battalion was disbanded soon after.
In the last ditch effort to rid himself of Chirico, Peruzen transferred him to General http://anidb.net/ch89503 [Albert Killy]`s rogue unit for the raid on Lido. Killy`s men were instructed to kill Chirico during the operation, but Chirico`s unusual abilities made him more difficult to eliminate than anyone could guess. Caught up in events completely beyond his control, however, Chirico became a renegade - haunted both by Killy`s agents and the Melkian army.
Waiting only to uncover the lies and conspiracies that surround him, Chirico makes his way across the galaxy to find his destiny. His incredible stamina and resourcefulness are the result of his unknown heritage. When this truth is uncovered, nothing will ever be the same again.
Source: Geocities</description>
<picture>227433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40573" type="appears in" update="2018-12-04">
<rating votes="43">4.00</rating>
<name>Fyana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Beautiful and mysterious, she is at the center of the conspiracy that nearly cost http://anidb.net/ch15676 [Chirico his] life on Lido. She is many things to many people, and her evolution through various identities changes her from a living weapon to a human being. As Proto One, she is the deadly killing machine she was designed to be as the first Melkian http://anidb.net/t2047 [Perfect Soldier]. As the Phantom Lady, she is a figure of mystery on the streets of Uoodo City. Chirico later gives her the name Fyana, and from that point she begins to develop as a person with genuine emotions.
Genetically engineered by the Melkian army, her enhanced fighting abilities make her as deadly as she is captivating. What no one could have foreseen, however, was that when she first awoke in Lido and saw Chirico, her destiny would be forever linked with his. From Lido, she is abducted by the http://anidb.net/ch90342 [Secret Society] and later sent against Chirico in battle. When she meets him face to face for the second time, she feels a strong attractions to him which eventually inspires her to defect from the Secret Society and join him on the run.
Her dependency on the radiation of jijirium for re-energization leads to dangerous conditions when she cannot find appropriate regenerative facilities, but when in top from she is an excellent, refined soldier, highly skilled in many forms of combat.
Source: MAL</description>
<picture>227435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21545" picture="55611.jpg">Yanaga Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="149767" update="2013-04-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>1986-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
