<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9881" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>75</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2015-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dia no Ace</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ace of Diamond</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Диамантеният ас</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Diamond no Ace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Daiya no Ace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Daiya no A</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ダイヤのA[エース]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ace of the Diamond</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ace of Diamond</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Ace of the Diamond</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">钻石王牌</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Ace of the Diamond</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11115" type="Sequel">Dia no Ace: Second Season</anime>
<anime id="10739" type="Other">Dia no Ace (2014)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3423" approval="29" total="32">Major (2005)</anime>
<anime id="6139" approval="5" total="11">One Outs</anime>
<anime id="7291" approval="4" total="10">Ookiku Furikabutte: Natsu no Taikai Hen</anime>
<anime id="6424" approval="4" total="9">Cross Game</anime>
<anime id="241" approval="2" total="6">Touch</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="308191">If you like Major or any other of the hundreds of baseball anime out there, this one is for you. This is one of the better baseball anime out there actually and for once the main isn`t some super awesome fastball throwing god like usual.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://diaace.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="9742" type="Character Design">Ueta Minoru</name>
<name id="7839" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tasaki Satoshi</name>
<name id="8625" type="Series Composition">Konuta Kenji</name>
<name id="7995" type="Direction">Masuhara Mitsuyuki</name>
<name id="10818" type="Original Work">Terajima Yuuji</name>
<name id="721" type="Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="731" type="Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="38550" type="Music">Flyingpan</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr10818 [Terajima Yuuji], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr17160 [Weekly Shounen Magazine].
http://anidb.net/ch58411 [Sawamura Eijun], who is a pitcher from a country high school, gets teamed up with a catcher from a school with an elite baseball team. He decides to quit his school to attend the school that this catcher plays.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="909">6.98</permanent>
<temporary count="914">7.47</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>142315.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15337</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18689</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/ace-of-diamond/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/diaace/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://diaace.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ace_of_Diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ダイヤのA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3186</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347019</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16485</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>diaace_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2378" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>hard-working</name>
<description>Describes someone, who is constantly, regularly, or habitually active or occupied.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2671" parentid="2869" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>school dormitory</name>
<description>A school dormitory or residence hall is the student living quarters at an elite academy, boarding school, or military school. The main characters may live or work at the dormitory, and it often becomes the backdrop for a reoccurring part of the story.</description>
<picurl>223167.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2978" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-28">
<name>aim for the top</name>
<description>This can be a positive or negative plot device. A character may strive to become the best in an altruistic way (e.g. best healer, most widely learned master), or it can be quite banal and primitive (e.g. challenged delinquents wanting to be the strongest fighters).
Alas in fighting anime the latter usually prevails.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="58408" type="main character in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="25">9.01</rating>
<name>Miyuki Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A brilliant second-year catcher with an easy going personality and a sharp eye.</description>
<picture>142298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58409" type="main character in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="10">7.34</rating>
<name>Kominato Haruichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A first-year second baseman of the team, Haruichi is a naturally talented, all-rounder baseball player. Despite his small stature and frail appearance, he has pinpoint precision while batting the ball, able to hit it as wide and as far as he pleases, and control where the ball lands. He also is extremely talented at defense, able to catch a ball in the air and throw it while still floating. He is often noted to have amazing baseball sense, able to decide in a split second where to hit the ball, what to watch for, and when to steal. His ability in baseball exceeds his older brother`s, Ryousuke Kominato, who is first-string player and also a second baseman. The only thing lacking is his stamina, which he works hard on improving. Born in the Kanagawa Prefecture, he is a very calm and quiet person, often acting as tsukkomi to Sawamura Eijun`s boke. He has a habit of saying things bluntly and often praises either Furuya or Eijun, causing them to compete against each other frequently. He plays reserve in the first-string team and occasionally feels envious of Eijun and Furuya for being able to play in a match. He is very small compared to other boys and it has been noted that he looks a bit like a girl. He is easily embarrassed, especially when praised. His relationship with his brother is slightly strained because they play the same position, but he still admires him to no end. Though reserved, he is highly ambitious and aims to take his brother`s position. When he was a child, their relationship was closer, with Ryousuke often protecting him from bullies.</description>
<picture>142297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58410" type="main character in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="19">3.13</rating>
<name>Furuya Satoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eijun`s rival, Furuya is a right-handed pitcher with extremely strong fastballs and forkballs. Furuya`s pitches are so strong that no catcher in Hokkaido was able to receive them. As a result, he became alienated from his middle-school team because he was far above them in ability. After hearing about the genius catcher, Miyuki Kazuya, he applied to go to Seidou high school to play baseball with him, and immediately took respect when Miyuki easily caught his pitch. During the game of first years versus second years, Furuya jumped from the second team to the first team after only one pitch. After playing his first official game against Yokohama, Furuya became a living legend within the high school baseball world and is often described as a monster rookie. Furuya`s strong points are his incredible pitching, outfield defense, and batting. His weaknesses are stamina and infield defense. Also, Furuya`s pitches are so powerful that they cause damage to his fingertips and nails, so he cannot pitch for very long. He is stoic and unsociable with a cool demeanor and often has an expressionless face. However, his aura completely changes while pitching, once being described as "a wild wolf who wants to pitch some balls". He dislikes all other aspects of baseball besides pitching. However, he is surprisingly humble, once mentioning that he never thought himself better than Eijun. He respects Eijun to a certain point and often accompanies Eijun to do extra practice at night. Because he was an outcast in his middle school, he is happy about but unused to the Seidou upperclassmen`s friendly but bossy treatment towards him, being content when he was ordered to fetch them drinks and uncomfortable when they excessively praise him. He also likes taking advice. He gets bored easily, disliking it when he cannot play in a match, and often falls asleep when he isn`t playing, or when he wants to ignore somebody.</description>
<picture>142296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58411" type="main character in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="26">5.73</rating>
<name>Sawamura Eijun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character. Eijun is a left-handed pitcher who has extremely erratic throwing motions. His body is naturally flexible with supple joints, allowing him to immediately change the pitch`s direction. Because Eijun has been playing baseball without proper instruction, his pitches normally change direction right before the batter hits the ball. However, this makes catching the ball difficult, as most catchers cannot predict where the ball will end up. He was initially unaware of this quirk in his throws. His knowledge about baseball is mediocre at best, but he strives to improve his skills and become Seidou`s ace player. Eijun comes from Nagano where he played baseball in his middle school. His team was below average, often making mistakes during critical moments and losing almost all matches. However, Eijun has an extremely strong spirit which, no matter how hopeless the situation got, inspired his teammates to continue playing their best. His childhood friend, Wakana, was the baseball team manager. Initially, after Eijun had been scouted by Seidou, he had planned to refuse because he wanted to keep playing with his friends in the same high school. However, his friends encouraged Eijun to go to Seidou despite their reluctant feelings because they felt as if they were holding Eijun back. Eijun eventually goes to Seidou and boldly declares that he will become the team ace. Eijun`s strong points are his infallible spirit, bunting, infield defense, and his idiosyncratic pitches. His weaknesses are control, outfield defense, and batting. His personality is hotheaded and loudmouthed, often causing his teammates exasperation because of his stupidity. He has a rivalry/friendship with Furuya Satoru, a fellow first-year pitcher. Because his middle school team was so weak, he is extremely level-headed in critical times.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>142295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59281" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="6">8.64</rating>
<name>Yuuki Tetsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59282" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="8">8.02</rating>
<name>Kuramochi Youichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59283" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="9">8.16</rating>
<name>Isashiki Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59284" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="14">8.35</rating>
<name>Takigawa Chris Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59285" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Tanba Kouichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59286" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="8">6.88</rating>
<name>Kominato Ryousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59287" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="6">5.22</rating>
<name>Masuko Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59385" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="9">3.43</rating>
<name>Kawakami Norifumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59386" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="4">5.54</rating>
<name>Azuma Kiyokuni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59387" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="14">8.62</rating>
<name>Kataoka Tesshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59388" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="4">4.14</rating>
<name>Kanemaru Shinji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59389" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="8">7.90</rating>
<name>Takashima Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60249" type="appears in" update="2013-10-06">
<name>Sano-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60250" type="appears in" update="2013-10-06">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Eijun no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35883" picture="132002.jpg">Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60251" type="appears in" update="2013-10-06">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Eijun no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33784" picture="93013.jpg">Takeuchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60252" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>Sawamura Eitoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3125" picture="24097.jpg">Mitsuo Senda</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60253" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="4">6.07</rating>
<name>Aotsuki Wakana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38582" picture="143925.jpg">Kaji Ayano</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60401" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<name>Nobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22360" picture="223532.jpg">Shimozuma Yoshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60656" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Manaka Kaname</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60871" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="4">6.75</rating>
<name>Yoshikawa Haruno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36511" picture="134700.jpg">Endou Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60872" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="2">7.39</rating>
<name>Natsukawa Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36509" picture="134698.jpg">Takahashi Karin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60873" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Oowada Akiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35883" picture="132002.jpg">Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60874" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Oota Kazuyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33784" picture="93013.jpg">Takeuchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60875" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="2">2.32</rating>
<name>Umemoto Sachiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38634" picture="144425.jpg">Hanamori Yumiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60876" type="appears in" update="2013-10-28">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Tahara Toshihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19591" picture="50874.jpg">Katou Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60877" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Takako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29400" picture="157186.jpg">Yamaguchi Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60878" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Mine Fujio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61064" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Maezono Kenta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23246" picture="61476.jpg">Tajiri Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61065" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Miyauchi Keisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146177.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23534" picture="74510.jpg">Murata Taishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61066" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Toujou Hideaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32515" picture="196887.jpg">Sudou Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61067" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Makihara Masumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28671" picture="62527.jpg">Miyake Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61068" type="appears in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Kaneda Tadahiro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="38699" picture="145180.jpg">Umoto Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61715" type="appears in" update="2013-11-21">
<name>Yamazaki Kunio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36678" picture="158322.jpg">Kawaguchi Shou</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="32515" picture="196887.jpg">Sudou Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61716" type="appears in" update="2013-11-21">
<name>Hayashi Shin`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61717" type="appears in" update="2013-11-21">
<name>Mori Shouhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23246" picture="61476.jpg">Tajiri Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61718" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Kadota Masaaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11275" picture="65394.jpg">Suzuki Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61719" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Tanaka Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33784" picture="93013.jpg">Takeuchi Eiji</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="25068" picture="70119.jpg">Kajikawa Shouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61788" type="appears in" update="2013-12-01">
<name>J Animal M</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="36733.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61942" type="appears in" update="2013-12-01">
<name>Nakata Ataru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29947" picture="223488.jpg">Terashima Junta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61943" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Ono Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146572.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11275" picture="65394.jpg">Suzuki Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61944" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Zaizen Naoyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62195" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Saitou Hiromi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25068" picture="70119.jpg">Kajikawa Shouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62196" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Kuwata Masaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32515" picture="196887.jpg">Sudou Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62197" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Seki Naomichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36678" picture="158322.jpg">Kawaguchi Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63325" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Harada Masatoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63326" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="3">4.45</rating>
<name>Narumiya Mei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68494" type="appears in" update="2014-07-07">
<rating votes="1">8.72</rating>
<name>Seidou Koukou Yakyuubu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>142315.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68737" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Yang Shunchen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68738" type="appears in" update="2014-07-20">
<name>Hirai Tsubasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68739" type="appears in" update="2014-07-20">
<rating votes="7">7.99</rating>
<name>Todoroki Raichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68740" type="appears in" update="2014-07-20">
<rating votes="4">5.87</rating>
<name>Sanada Shunpei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68741" type="appears in" update="2014-07-20">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Mishima Yuuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68742" type="appears in" update="2014-07-20">
<name>Akiba Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32333" picture="131863.jpg">Kanemoto Ryousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68743" type="appears in" update="2014-07-20">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Kamiya Carlos Toshiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="367" picture="17213.jpg">Kenn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68744" type="appears in" update="2014-07-20">
<name>Shirakawa Katsuyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68745" type="appears in" update="2014-07-20">
<name>Yoshizawa Hideaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68746" type="appears in" update="2014-07-20">
<name>Yamaoka Riku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36678" picture="158322.jpg">Kawaguchi Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68747" type="appears in" update="2014-07-20">
<name>Maki Yousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68781" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Sekiguchi Junzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6639" picture="41436.jpg">Tenjin Hidetaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68786" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Shirasu Kenjirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22360" picture="223532.jpg">Shimozuma Yoshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68787" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Murata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22360" picture="223532.jpg">Shimozuma Yoshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68788" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Tachi Hiromi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68789" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Nakai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23534" picture="74510.jpg">Murata Taishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68790" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Matsumoto Takahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23246" picture="61476.jpg">Tajiri Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68791" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Kunitomo Hiroshige</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="415" picture="241624.jpg">Nakano Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68792" type="appears in" update="2014-07-22">
<name>Higasa Shouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36678" picture="158322.jpg">Kawaguchi Shou</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="29947" picture="223488.jpg">Terashima Junta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68796" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Maimon Nishikou Buchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23246" picture="61476.jpg">Tajiri Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68797" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Minamidaira Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158471.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32515" picture="196887.jpg">Sudou Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68798" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Oomae Takahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68801" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Chiba Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68802" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Kikunaga Masaaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158470.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23534" picture="74510.jpg">Murata Taishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68803" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Miyata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28671" picture="62527.jpg">Miyake Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68804" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Ninomiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22360" picture="223532.jpg">Shimozuma Yoshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68805" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Kunimi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37069" picture="157013.jpg">Tomita Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68806" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Oonishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38341" picture="141125.jpg">Morita Shuujirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68807" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Ogata Kazunari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23246" picture="61476.jpg">Tajiri Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68808" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Shiratori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33784" picture="93013.jpg">Takeuchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68809" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Hashimoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158478.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68810" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Tsushima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158479.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68811" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<name>Takada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158481.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68812" type="appears in" update="2014-07-23">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Sakai Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33784" picture="93013.jpg">Takeuchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71402" type="appears in" update="2014-11-16">
<name>Tadano Itsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36495" picture="176250.jpg">Yamaya Yoshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71403" type="appears in" update="2014-11-16">
<rating votes="2">6.38</rating>
<name>Nagao Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76205" type="appears in" update="2015-07-05">
<rating votes="4">9.24</rating>
<name>Todoroki Raizou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="292" picture="68967.jpg">Nishi Rintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76206" type="appears in" update="2015-07-05">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Yakushi Koukou Yakyuubu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="76227" type="appears in" update="2015-07-05">
<name>Fukui Kento</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="76233" type="appears in" update="2015-07-05">
<name>Inashiro Jitsugyou Yakyuubu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="154786" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真っ向勝負!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Head to Head!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Affrontement !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makkou Shoubu!</title>
<summary>The scrim continues. Sawamura has finally based. It was thanks to the advice from Haruichi Kominato. As he steps into the batter`s box, he declares to score a run. His batting turns out to be amazing. To answer the call, Sawamura sprints and makes it back to the plate. The first-year team gains momentum, but the Head Coach is ending the game mid way. However, he will let the game continue if the entire first-year team wants to keep playing. How will they respond?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644919</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154787" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Clash</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Choc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu</title>
<summary>A game between the first-years and the second and third-years is being held. While Sawamura worries about whether or not he can play, he chances upon the Head Coach in the bath. "I don`t want to see anyone but me standing on the mound." The Head Coach gives Sawamura one more chance in response to his statement. On the day of the game, the second and third-years are playing with everything they have. The first-year team looks pale, but Sawamura is pumped for his first game. Sawamura seems to be full of energy, but perhaps it isn`t being put to good use...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644917</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154788" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">同じタイプ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Are You Like Me?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Du même genre ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onaji Type?</title>
<summary>Seidou High School faces off against Ichidai Third High School, the school that beat them last year. While their top-level offense rakes in runs, the ace Tanba isn`t doing too hot. The game turns into a batting game. On the other hand, Sawamura is back at school, training by himself. During his training, Furuya, another first-year pitcher approaches him. Showing sympathy to Sawamura`s peculiar training method, Furuya offers to play catch with him. Sawamura is in a cheery mood with Furuya`s kindness, but the speed of Furuya`s throws far exceeds his expectations.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644915</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154789" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">投手失格?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Not Qualified to Be a Pitcher?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pas l’étoffe d’un lanceur ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toushu Shikkaku?</title>
<summary>Sawamura is nervous being roomed with his older baseball teammates. However, their unexpectedly warm welcome makes him feel right at home. Next day, he feels too much at home, and ends up sleeping in for his first practice! There, he reunites with Miyuki who also overslept. Unfortunately, Miyuki`s advice on resolving the situation only makes it worse. The head coach himself tells Sawamura that using him as a player is out of the question. However, recalling the messages from his teammates back home, he declares to the coach, "I came here to become the ace of this team!" So the head coach gives him a challenge.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644913</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154790" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">相棒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Partner</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Partenaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aibou</title>
<summary>Sawamura gets himself into a baseball match against the 12th grade batter, Kiyokuni Azuma. Sawamura forms a battery with Kazuya Miyuki, the catcher carrying high hopes for Seidou. Sawamura loses confidence against Azuma, an opponent he`s never faced, but Miyuki`s lead slowly pulls out Sawamura`s full potential. And then he throws his last pitch. After returning from Tokyo, Sawamaura is lost about his future, unable to forget his pitching with Miyuki. He wants to test his strength in Tokyo, but he can`t betray his junior high teammates and leave them behind. Bewildered, his teammates approach him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644911</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154791" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の一球</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One Pitch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La balle du destin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Ikkyuu</title>
<summary>Game set. Eijun Sawamura, the pitcher of a novice junior high baseball team, meets with a bitter walk-off loss. For Sawamura, that became his last game in junior high, so he sets a new goal of going to the nationals in high school with his teammates. As he begins his hard quest on studying, a guest arrives unannounced. Her name is Rei Takashima, and she is the assistant director of the prestigious Seidou High School Baseball Team. Takashima invites Sawamura to Seidou after seeing his potential, but Sawamura`s reply was far from what she had expected.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644909</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154834" update="2015-01-12">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154835" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155941" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたりのバッテリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Two Batteries</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les deux batteries</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Battery</title>
<summary>Sawamura and Furuya are called to the bench. They are to incorporate the pitchers` training menu into their practice. Sawamura is excited by this addition, but unfortunately, Miyuki is partnered up with Furuya. While Sawamura is showing discontent that he isn`t Miyuki`s partner, a suspicious looking man there stands with a cold look. He is the other catcher, Chris. "Nice to meet you, poor pitcher," mutters Chris with a gloomy voice. Sawamura senses something eerie.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644921</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156310" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスの真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Truth About Chris</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vérité sur Chris</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chris no Shinjitsu</title>
<summary>"You won`t ever be the ace." Sawamura receives a grim statement from Chris after seeing Furuya`s performance in a game. Chris leaves Sawamura with a difficult training menu and leaves before anyone else. All Sawamura sees in him is a man who has given up. However, the moment he makes that comment out loud, Miyuki loses his cool. What ticked him off? What is Chris hiding?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644923</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156311" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悔しさ, 胸に刻んで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With Chagrin in His Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La frustration gravée dans le cœur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuyashisa, Mune ni Kizande</title>
<summary>After learning the truth about Chris, Sawamura follows him around to get him to teach Sawamura baseball. Chris finally gives in to Sawamura`s persistence and decides catch his pitches. The pitch Sawamura decides to throw is the fastest pitch he can. But in response, Chris asks, "What is your specialty?" Sawamura can`t throw breaking balls or amazing fastballs. What kind of pitch should he throw? He asks around his teammates for help, and he arrives at an answer.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644925</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156432" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">磨け, クセ球</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hone Your Moving Fastball</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Perfectionner mes balles changeantes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Migake, Kusedama</title>
<summary>Chris tells Sawamura to improve on his specialty. While Sawamura started this relationship being an arrogant prick, Chris has been a catcher to him from the start; the training menu Chris gave him was a menu specifically for him. Sawamura puts in the effort to improve because he wants Chris to see his growth before Chris graduates from the team. At the first-string try-out game, Sawamura asks Chris for a favor. What will Chris say?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644927</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156613" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリス出陣!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chris to the Field!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chris entre en jeu !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chris Shutsujin!</title>
<summary>What Sawamura throws from the mound is an amazing moving fastball. However, his control`s going haywire. When it looks like he might be getting replaced, the man who comes in is Chris. What is the "plan" that Chris takes when it appears all is lost?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644929</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156713" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ターゲット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Target</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La cible</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Target</title>
<summary>Chris`s father Animal comes to watch the game. He tries to stop his son from pushing himself to play. However, watching Chris make dangerous plays sends him back to the days he was a pro, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644931</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156808" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一軍昇格</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`re in the First-String</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Promotion en équipe première</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichigun Shoukaku</title>
<summary>Sawamura`s opponent batter Zaizen makes an unexpected play. However, Sawamura fixes his pitching and avoids the worst. Being on a roll, Sawamura throws his final pitch. What of the ball that Sawamura throws with everything he wants to tell Chris?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644933</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156916" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">合宿スタート!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Training Camp Begins!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Début du camp d’entraînement !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gasshuku Start!</title>
<summary>Sawamura keeps training hard. However, it was obvious to everyone that he was overworking himself. Chris calls Sawamura over to give him a warning—the best thing Chris could do out of concern for Sawamura`s body. As the training camp of hell begins, Sawamura...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644937</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157279" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレーで引っぱれ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lead with Your Plays!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tire l’équipe vers le haut !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Play de Hippare!</title>
<summary>The training camp continues. The first-years can barely keep up with the harsh training. As Sawamura improves little by little, he is called to Miyuki`s room for some reason. There, he found his upperclassmen waiting, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649577</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157308" update="2015-01-12">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157507" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">試練</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épreuve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiren</title>
<summary>With fatigue from the camp, no one is playing well in the practice game against Osaka Kiryu. Even Furuya gives up 11 runs in just four innings. And finally, he calls for a time out. When everyone assumes he`s raising the white flag, he makes a statement expressing his fortitude.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649579</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157656" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">試合は楽しい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Games Are Fun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les matchs, c’est fun !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiai wa Tanoshii</title>
<summary>Seido and Kiryu begin playing neck and neck, and then Sawamura is called to the mound with Miyuki as his batterymate. "Let`s have fun," says Miyuki, but Sawamura doesn`t know what this game means for him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649581</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157833" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ムカつくけど</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Hate It, But...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Il me fout les boules !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukatsuku kedo</title>
<summary>"At least pitch to the inside." Miyuki tries to motivate Sawamura, who goes out with just his moving fastball and little experience. But Sawamura is unable to throw well. So Miyuki gives Sawamura another word of advice. This time to believe the fielders and throw with spirit. Is Miyuki trying to encourage him or put pressure on him? But it reminds Sawamura why he came to Seido. And the pitch he throws next...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649583</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157930" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">因縁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fate</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Destin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Innen</title>
<summary>Seido, Inashiro Vocational, and Shuhoku are having a three-way round-robin. Game two of the round-robin is Inashiro vs Shuhoku, and the ace of Inashiro, Mei Narumiya, is pitching this game. He`s the one who shut out Seido`s batters at the last summer tournament semi-final. To make matters worse, Narumiya shows off a new weapon he didn`t have last year. The pitch lights a fire under Seido`s ace, Tanba. He too has a new weapon he`s been working on.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649585</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158056" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">緊急事態</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emergency</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">État d’urgence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinkyuu Jitai</title>
<summary>Miyuki and Tanba`s opinions clash mid-game. However, Tanba claims that what he wants to do is necessary for him to become a true ace. As Tanba gets closer and closer to becoming a true ace, something terrible happens.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649587</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158251" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の舞台へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Dream Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vers le théâtre de nos rêves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Butai e</title>
<summary>Many rivals gather at the opening ceremony of the Tokyo Qualifiers, and only two schools can make national. Seido`s summer to bring glory back to their name begins with a game against Maimon West High School. Seido`s starting pitcher is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649589</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158336" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アピールタイム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Calling for Attention</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Plein les yeux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Appeal Time</title>
<summary>Maimon West High School`s starting pitcher isn`t who Seido were expecting. The Seido team struggle against a player with no data and finish their first attack without scoring. However, Furuya isn`t doing any less as the starting pitcher.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649591</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158384" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">公式戦デビュー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Official Game Debut</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Premier match officiel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koushikisen Debut</title>
<summary>With the first game done, each player focuses on cleaning up his techniques. Chris teaches Sawamura how to hold the ball for a four-seam fastball. It should be a powerful weapon for Sawamura down the line.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649593</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158481" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">精密機械</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clockwork</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Machine de précision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seimitsu Kikai</title>
<summary>The opponent in the fourth round is Akikawa Academy. Their pitcher, Shunshin Yeung, has been called "clockwork" due to his impeccable pitch control. "This won`t be like the previous games." The Seido team shift their gears.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649595</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158552" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">降谷攻略</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anti-Furuya Strategy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À la conquête de Furuya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Furuya Kouryaku</title>
<summary>Furuya starts in the Akikawa game, and he hammers them with his fastballs. However, it was Akikawa`s plan to tire him out by increasing his pitch count from his lack of control. Miyuki realizes their plan and makes a comeback move.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652021</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158706" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミラクル明川</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Miracle Akikawa</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le miracle Akikawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miracle Akikawa</title>
<summary>Top of the first, Shunshin Yeung stands in the batter`s box. His overflowing determination forces Furuya to throw a meatball and takes a long hit into the left, giving Akikawa the first two runs of the game. Akikawa takes up the reins of the game, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652023</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158941" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逃げねえぞ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Not Running</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je fuirai pas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nigenee zo</title>
<summary>Furuya grows weak under the hot weather, but Akikawa makes the move to exhaust him even more using bunts. In order to avoid telling the world about Furuya`s weakness before the Ichidai game, Coach Kataoka decides to use Sawamura. What does the coach see in him?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653471</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158968" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝者と敗者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Winner and Loser</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vainqueur et vaincu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shousha to Haisha</title>
<summary>Coach Kataoka uses Haruichi as a pinch hitter. Haruichi answers with a beautiful hit. Sawamura and Kuramochi follow up. Then Ryosuke steps up to the plate. In this huge chance to score, he makes a squeeze play!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653477</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158969" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">拮抗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Neck and Neck</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des forces comparables</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikkou</title>
<summary>Sawamura finally comes out to play, and he magnificently takes out the Akikawa batters. To reciprocate, the Seido batters commence their counterattack. As Miyuki stands at bat, he thinks, "If I were calling plays for this pitcher..." Will he get it right?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653475</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158970" recap="true" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">軌跡 沢村栄純 熱闘のマウンドへ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Path, Eijun Sawamura to the Scorching Mound</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Parcours. La route d’Eijun Sawamura vers le combat intense</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki: Sawamura Eijun - Nettou no Mound e</title>
<summary>An unexpected guest showed up before Sawamura fter he lost his final game in junior high. She was a scout from the prestigious Seido High School. From their life-changing meeting to the summer tournament, his story thus far is told once more.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653473</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158971" update="2015-01-12">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158972" update="2014-04-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159706" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダークホース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dark Horse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Outsider</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dark Horse</title>
<summary>Seido stays to watch Ichidai`s game to prepare for the upcoming quarterfinal. Ichidai`s opponent is Yakushi, a nameless school. Yakushi`s clean-ups were completely different from their previous games and were played by first-years. Ichidai scores in the first inning making it look like an easy win, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653479</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159831" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの夏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des étés bien différents</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Natsu</title>
<summary>Manaka, the ace of Ichidai, is back in top shape on the mound. However, Raichi, the cleanup of Yakushi hits the ball right into Manaka, which forces him to step down. Even without the ace, Ichidai put up a good fight but are unable to secure a win. Seido are shocked by the outcome of the game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653481</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159974" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金のなる木</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Money Tree</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Devenir riche par la batte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kane no Naru Ki</title>
<summary>In preparation for the Yakushi game, Coach Kataoka speaks to the pitchers. Sawamura, Furuya, and Kawakami are told that Tanba won`t be pitching, but Tanba is told to be ready to go. The coach wants to play with everyone as a team. The quarter-final begins, and Yakushi`s lineup is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653483</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160177" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">頼れる先輩達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reliable Teammates</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des coéquipiers sur qui on peut compter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tayoreru Senpai-tachi</title>
<summary>Raichi takes the fight between him and Furuya in the first inning. On that note, Yakushi scores the leading run. However, Miyuki`s throw to second and encouragement of, "you have many reliable teammates behind you" takes some pressure off Furuya. On top of that, Furuya...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653485</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160333" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ポテンシャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Potential</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Potentiel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Potential</title>
<summary>Furuya wants to keep pitching, but Coach Kataoka switches him out. Sawamura is up next and he faces off against Raichi. Raichi gets excited about Sawamura`s moving fastball seeing how much potential it has. What`s the outcome of this fight?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653487</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160396" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エース登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ace Walks On</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le numéro 1 entre en scène</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ace Toujou</title>
<summary>Yakushi finally brings out their ace, Sanada. Miyuki falls prey to Sanada`s cutter. Sawamura pitches aggressively to match Sanada`s pitching, but Yakushi aren`t going to sit by and watch.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653489</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160495" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バースト!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burst!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rafale !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Burst!</title>
<summary>Sawamura and Raichi face off for the second time. Sawamura is fired up with Coach Kataoka`s encouraging words. However, the hit he thought he jammed turns into a homerun and devastates Sawamura. Then, he gets switched out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653493</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160871" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの役割</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Roles</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chacun son rôle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Yakuwari</title>
<summary>In the top of the eighth, Kawakami relieves Sawamura from the mound and faces Raichi. Kawakami and Miyuki choose to walk him. At a glance, Seido apear to be cornered, but Kawakami regains his confidence from giving Raichi the walk.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653495</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161060" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">期待を背負って</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Expectations of an Ace</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Leurs espoirs sur ses épaules</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitai o Seotte</title>
<summary>It`s the top of the eighth with two outs and runners on first and third, and Tanba takes the mound. Following the efforts of Furuya, Sawamura, and Kawakami, Tanba takes the ball. His first batter is Sanada, the ace of Yakushi. Coach Todoroki`s orders are to hit Tanba`s first pitch and shut him down.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653497</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161144" update="2015-01-12">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161276" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウィニングショット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Winning Shot</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le coup gagnant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Winning Shot</title>
<summary>The top of the ninth is Yakushi`s last chance to score. Raichi comes up to bat at two outs and a runner on first. Yakushi`s dugout is cheering loudly for Raichi. "I don`t want to let my team down." Raichi makes his resolve. Tanba`s third pitch goes in a little soft and Seido lose all their hope.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653499</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161409" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いざ, 準決勝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s the Semifinal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Maintenant, la demi-finale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iza, Junkesshou</title>
<summary>For the semifinal, Seido High School go up against Sensen Academy`s Maki, the giant. As the veteran of the match up, Coach Ukai tells the reporters that Seido`s weakness is Coach Kataoka`s lack of experience. At Seido High School, Sawamura is still blue from being taken off the mound in the Yakushi game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653501</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161579" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そびえる大巨人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Giant Looks Down</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’imposant géant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sobieru Daikyojin</title>
<summary>Under Coach Ukai`s definitive command, Maki throws his huge curveballs. Tanba begins to show signs of fatigue. Will Sawamura be called to the mound? Eijun`s junior high friends came all the way out to cheer. Some members of Inashiro are also watching from the stands.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653503</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161734" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リベンジ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Revanche</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Revenge</title>
<summary>Haruichi comes onto the field as a pinch hitter for Tanba. Maki pitches emotionally against Haruichi. After two strikes, Haruichi gently meets Maki`s curveball and hits it to the outfield. At the bottom of the sixth, Sawamura walks on.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653505</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161920" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決め球</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Best Pitch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lancer de prédilection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimedama</title>
<summary>Maki hits powerful fouls off Sawamura. As Maki stands with intensity in the batter`s box, Coach Ukai tells him to smash the wall of the top three schools with his bat. Sawamura throws a crossfire pitch under Wakana`s and his fellow teammates` watch.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653507</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162096" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fantasy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rêve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume Monogatari</title>
<summary>After defeating Sensen Academy, Sawamura enjoys his time with his junior high friends. The second game of the semifinals is between the tournament favorite, Inashiro Vocational High, and a dark horse, Sakurazawa High. Coach Kikukawa exclaims, "It`s time to make history!" And the game sets off to an unexpected start.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653509</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162361" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望を呼ぶ投球</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pitching of Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des lancers qui font désespérer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zetsubou o Yobu Toukyuu</title>
<summary>As Nagao takes on Inashiro with his knuckle ball, Sakurazawa wait for their chance to score. However, Sakurazawa slowly lose their cool experiencing Narumiya`s untouchable fastball. Their calm defense evaporates and errors inevitably follow. Unfortunately, Inashiro`s next batter is their cleanup, Harada.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653511</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162477" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">...あの夏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cet été-là...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">... Ano Natsu</title>
<summary>After the game, Narumiya bumps into Miyuki. "Remember the last time all of us got together?" Carlos asks, as everyone Narumiya invited to Inashiro was present. That is of course, Miyuki included.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653513</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162561" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寮にて....</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At the Dorm...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dans les internats...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryou nite...</title>
<summary>As Seido finish reviewing Narumiya`s pitching, Yuki talks about the confidence he has toward the final. His words were backed by the hard work everyone has put in. At Inashiro, they are also carefully preparing for the Seido game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653515</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162631" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懐かしい顔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Nostalgic Face</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un visage du passé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsukashii Kao</title>
<summary>The day before the final, Sawamura says he wants to learn a breaking ball to overcome his weakness. Azuma, an alumnus of the team stops by with great timing to show his support. Sawamura begins to practice the cutter with Azuma in the batter`s box.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653517</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162738" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日への足跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Footsteps to Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les pas vers l’avenir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asu e no Ashiato</title>
<summary>The current third-years were called "the hopeless year" when they joined. Their upperclassmen had lost all hope for them, but they diligently practiced, continuously encouraging each other. Their hard work changed their rivalry for each other into trust.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653519</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162934" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦開始!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle Begins!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Début de la bataille finale !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentou Kaishi!</title>
<summary>Sakai is shocked from being taken off the starting roster for the final, and Coach Kataoka gives him some words of encouragement. Being one victory away from going to nationals, everyone at Seido can`t seem to hold down their excitement. Coach Kataoka is no exception, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662015</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163100" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">負けたくない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Don`t Want to Lose</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je veux pas perdre !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maketakunai</title>
<summary>Narumiya strikes out Yuki, and Seido is reminded of Narumiya`s strength. Furuya takes the mound in the bottom and starts off with three consecutive strikeouts. Narumiya matches Furuya`s performance with three strikeouts as well. It`s going to be a pitching game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662017</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163360" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギアチェンジ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Change Gears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Passage à la vitesse supérieure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gear Change</title>
<summary>After three innings, it`s still a close final. Next up is the cleanup, Yuki, and Narumiya changes his gears. Baiting with the changeup, he strikes out Yuki with a fastball, creating momentum for Inashiro. Seido then realizes Narumiya is only going all out for Yuki and the team takes a mental blow.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662019</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163584" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">託す信頼, 応える勇気</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Entrusted Faith and the Courage to Perform</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La confiance donnée, le courage d’y répondre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takusu Shinrai, Kotaeru Yuuki</title>
<summary>In the top of the fifth, Furuya gets a hit off Narumiya. It`s the perfect chance to tie the game, and Shirasu, batting ninth, hits Narumiya`s fastball. Will Shirasu make first base? And in the bottom of the fifth, the ace, Tanba, takes the mound.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662021</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163765" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強い男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strong Men</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un homme solide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuyoi Otoko</title>
<summary>When Inashiro has two outs with the bases loaded, Tanba pulls through to get Seido going. However, Narumiya and Harada change their pitching pattern to keep Seido away from the bases. As the innings change and the Seido players walk out to the field, Kuramochi stops Ryosuke.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662023</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163881" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決断</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Détermination</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketsudan</title>
<summary>Seido`s loss seems imminent against the mighty Inashiro. To make things worse, Tanba`s leg cramps at the bottom of the seventh. Coach Kataoka decides to switch him out and puts Sawamura on the mound. The next batter is Narumiya!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662025</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163992" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">頼もしい後輩達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reliable Underclassmen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des jeunes pleins d’avenir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanomoshii Kouhai-tachi</title>
<summary>Sawamura strikes out Narumiya with three pitches. Miyuki`s bold strategy and Sawamura`s strong heart lift the tension in the air. Seido High School is back in their usual offensive attitude. Furuya is up to bat, and Narumiya throws a powerful crossfire pitch!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662027</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164369" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">前を打つ男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Three-Hole</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’homme qui frappe devant lui</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mae o Utsu Otoko</title>
<summary>Seido scores a run. Haruichi stands in the batter`s box in place of Ryosuke as a pinch hitter. Seido has high expectations for the lucky kid. On the other hand, Inashiro can`t give anything up. Narumiya grows furiuos seeing Haruichi`s wooden bat. Can Haruichi connect to the next batter?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662029</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164587" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怖いもの知らず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fearless</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Intrépide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kowai Mono Shirazu</title>
<summary>It`s Yuki versus Narumiya. Yuki hits Narumiya`s changeup with his unparalleled concentration, and Seido turns the game around! Tanba finds himself tearing up at Yuki`s hit, while Narumiya can`t keep his cool. Going into the bottom of the eighth, Sawamura continues to pitch.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662031</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164664" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤独な太陽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lonely Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un soleil solitaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodoku na Taiyou</title>
<summary>At the top of the ninth, Inashiro is behind by a run. "I can`t picture us losing," says Narumiya as he reflects on the loss at nationals and the hardships he`s overcome. The Inashiro team goes back to fielding, entrusting everything to their perfectionist ace.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662033</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164742" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">執念</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Determined</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ténacité</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuunen</title>
<summary>The unique experience of pitching in the last inning of a tournament final pressures Sawamura like never before. Carlos stands crouched over the plate, trying to get hit by a pitch. Can Sawamura resist his overwhelming determination to win?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662035</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164804" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天王山</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Victory or Defeat</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Apogée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tennouzan</title>
<summary>With a runner in a scoring position, Inashiro`s cleanup, Harada, stands at bat. Victory is one step away, but the challenge of a lifetime stands in its way. Using the last available time out, the ace goes to the field to relay a message. Can they defend the run and make nationals? The game finally comes to a close.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662037</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164805" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">残響</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lingering Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Échos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zankyou</title>
<summary>An unbelievable turn of events happens at the bottom of the ninth. Inashiro`s ace, Narumiya, turns the game around with his bat. Seido players fall to their knees. They were one step short of making nationals. Alas, their summer comes to an end.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>666673</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164928" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リスタート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Restart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nouveau départ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Restart</title>
<summary>After losing the final, things are looking grim at Seido. Haruichi has locked himself in his room. "Somewhere in my heart, I was waiting for this day." Maezono tells him how he feels. After Maezono`s eye-opening remark, Haruichi rises and grabs a bat.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662041</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165353" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">日の当たる場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un lieu ensoleillé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hi no Ataru Basho</title>
<summary>As the new captain, Miyuki tells the team his will, "I want to be greedy about winning." The second-years who were overshadowed before by the third-years show their potentials for the new team. However, Kawakami is still stuck in the past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662043</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165383" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エースの座</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ace Title</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le fauteuil de nº 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ace no Za</title>
<summary>To everyone`s surprise, the game against Yakushi is a pitcher`s game. Furuya takes Raichi out going three for three that inning, and the Seido team sees Furuya`s growth. In the bullpen, Sawamura feels threatened as Furuya`s growth shines on the mound.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662049</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165384" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">発奮材料</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Kick</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Stimulant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Happun Zairyou</title>
<summary>The new team at Seido isn`t meshing well just yet. The result of the practice games has been 8 wins and 4 losses with no explosiveness from the batters. Coach Kataoka accepts the practice game Yakushi requested in hopes of raising the team`s morale. Sawamura is fired up, but Miyuki isn`t happy with his lack of control.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662047</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165385" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よそ者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Outsider</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`intrus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yosomono</title>
<summary>The night before the national final, Narumiya lowers his head to his teammates and surprises everyone. Next day, Narumiya walks on to the Koshien mound, motivating Sawamura to practice harder as he watches it on TV. Later, an unfamiliar man comes to observe Seido`s practice.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662045</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165405" update="2015-01-12">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165406" update="2015-01-12">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165407" update="2015-01-12">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165795" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">負けらんねぇ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Can`t Lose!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je peux pas perdre !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makerannee!</title>
<summary>Furuya closes six innings without conceding any runs, and the crowd is excited to see the making of a true ace at Seido. Yakushi brings out their ace, Sanada, to the mound, and his presence overwhelms Seido. After seeing them both pitch, Sawamura can`t hold himself back.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662051</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166468" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Next Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Next Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Next Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Next Stage</title>
<summary>After conceding three runs without getting any outs, Sawamura is switched out of the game. "If I walk off here, I`ll never..." Memories of the summer final resurface. Contrary to Furuya putting on a show on the mound, Sawamura sits in the dugout like a corpse.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662053</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166683" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">71</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">9月の空の下</title>
<title xml:lang="en">September Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sous le ciel de septembre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kugatsu no Sora no Shita</title>
<summary>Sawamura isn`t himself anymore with the yips, but everyone still has faith in him that he`ll be back. While the team is worried for him, he continues his running exercises on his own, and slowly but surely, he`s regaining his zeal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662055</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166804" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">72</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の教え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Lesson</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Derniers enseignements</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Oshie</title>
<summary>Coach Ochiai and Coach Kataoka have conflicting opinions, but the fall tournament is going well for the team. While Sawamura continues to struggle with the yips, Chris shows up like a knight in shining armor. "Practice the low and away." Sawamura`s motivation is renewed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662057</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166891" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">73</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">継承</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inheritance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Succession</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keishou</title>
<summary>The third years are left speechless hearing about the resignation of the coach. Coach Kataoka puts the current team through the off-season training menu, and Maezono gives words of wisdom to the players who are slacking. Miyuki is impressed with how dependable Maezono has become and wonders why Coach Kataoka seems to be keeping a secret.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662059</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166949" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">74</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">道しるべ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guiding Light</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jalon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michishiribue</title>
<summary>The first and second-years find out about Coach Kataoka`s resignation, and they are flustered. Isashiki doesn`t feel any pressure from their plays, so he gives them a piece of his mind.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662061</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167212" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">75</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その場所を目指して―</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Pursuit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Visons ce fameux stade !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Basho o Mezashite -</title>
<summary>Maezono hits a home run at the top of the ninth, evening out the game at 3-3, and at the bottom of the ninth, Sawamura finally gets his chance on the mound. From the third-year team, Chris walks out as a pinch hitter to face Sawamura. Can Sawamura show his mentor the pitching of his life?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662063</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182126" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645075</identifier>
<identifier>ace-of-the-diamond</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
