<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9892" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-04-11</startdate>
<enddate>2014-06-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sidonia no Kishi</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">I cavalieri di Sidonia</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">시도니아의 기사</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Sidonia`nın Pilotları</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Рицарите на Сидония</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Лицарі Сідонії</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">シドニアの騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Knights of Sidonia</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Рицарите на "Сидония"</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">希德尼娅的骑士</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Knights of Sidonia</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10713" type="Sequel">Sidonia no Kishi: Daikyuu Wakusei Sen`eki</anime>
<anime id="10939" type="Summary">Gekijouban Sidonia no Kishi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11782" approval="22" total="25">Blame! (2017)</anime>
<anime id="416" approval="21" total="23">Blue Gender</anime>
<anime id="9556" approval="20" total="25">Suisei no Gargantia</anime>
<anime id="8549" approval="19" total="33">Muv-Luv Alternative: Total Eclipse</anime>
<anime id="5415" approval="11" total="18">Macross Frontier</anime>
<anime id="1806" approval="11" total="14">Soukyuu no Fafner: Dead Aggressor</anime>
<anime id="5911" approval="3" total="10">Koukaku no Regios</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="14">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="481642">Have long since forgotten most of the plot but the opening is one of the best earworms there is. Enjoy :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="252269">Surely nice visuals and the story we will see where it goes but i think there is some potential. Lets hope for a nice run...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="78044">I just started watching it because it was available on Netflix. i`m very restricted with mecha titles, and Sidonia has it`s perks. It succeeds on giving a BSG atmosphere, where they seem lost in space, and thats great. But aside from that, all other elements are pretty standard. The always saving the day hero, shallow side characters. And the animation style is not the best to my taste.
At last, this season build the whole plot and accomplished nothing. Which is very frustrating. Leaving everything to the next season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="382591">Excellent mix of multiple genres, unusual CG and music.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="449787">Ok, the story, characters and plot is so-so, but... when u watch the way of battle makes me can`t say a word, because it`s so stunningly awesome! Just remind me of Total Eclipse, but in different view of points.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="728642">I leave very few recommendations but I have to say this. An absolute must see for sci-fi fans, though I would go as far as to say that this could be enjoyed by fans of action and mecha. The animation, pacing and character development are perfect (I mean perfect for the plot). Every episode ends on a cliffhanger; leaving you wanting more! One slight fault is that I couldn`t understand where the unwavering determination of the protagonist comes from. He seems really quite uncomplicated for someone brought up as he has. Also, the obvious political aspects are alluded to but not developed. Aside from that...quite perfect. I wonder of season 2 can match it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="631534">Different visuals to the run of the mill. Gripping storyline, great characters and concept.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="241634">Space anime are ok in my book but this one is a MUST SEE. I have never personally seen an anime that tries to stick to "reality" as much as possible. The world tries to stick to logic, while usually such anime enjoy bending and ignoring totally reality. 

I did not feel attracted to the 3D design of the anime a lot, especially because I feel a lot of times the lipsync feel kind of off. 

The storyline is amazing to me. I have watched only the first episode on a random watch and after watching 4 anime, which account to 125 episodes, I still were thinking of this one. I finally decided to watch the second episode and from there it was all the way to the end. It still felt awkward at times due to the 3D but it was worth every second of watching this.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.knightsofsidonia.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7425" type="Original Work">Nihei Tsutomu</name>
<name id="14495" type="Direction">Shizuno Koubun</name>
<name id="30744" type="Animation Work">Polygon Pictures</name>
<name id="2315" type="Series Composition">Murai Sadayuki</name>
<name id="6883" type="Music">Asakura Noriyuki</name>
<name id="39801" type="Character Design">Moriyama Yuuki</name>
</creators>
<description>It has been a thousand years since the Gauna, a strange alien race with no known method of communication, destroyed the solar system. A portion of humanity managed to escape using enormous seed ships like the Sidonia, which have allowed them to maintain the population while drifting through space. http://anidb.net/ch61369 [Tanikaze Nagate] is a young man who has been raised deep in the bowels of the ship. When he goes into training to pilot the huge robotic weapons known as Gardes, Nagate is entrusted with piloting the legendary unit known as Tsugumori. Nagate and his fellow pilots put their lives on the line against the Gauna, in the desperate battle for the survival of humanity...
Source: Polygon Pictures</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2654">6.96</permanent>
<temporary count="2671">7.50</temporary>
<review count="3">5.60</review>
</ratings>
<picture>145720.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15496</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19775</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ppi.co.jp/works/sidonia/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.knightsofsidonia.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://starchild.fm/anime/knightsofsidonia/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Knights_of_Sidonia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>シドニアの騎士</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3363</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>346433</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16995</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2968" parentid="4831" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-05">
<name>faceless alien invasion</name>
<description>Uncommunicative, faceless aliens suddenly invade Earth from outer space or a parallel world thus causing a war with humans.
If the humans are lucky, the invasion may go off without a war that would cause untold destruction and death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3075" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-27">
<name>nervous breakdown</name>
<description>A character sees his entire world being destroyed around him, and his brain can`t take it anymore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3375" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-10">
<name>cel-shaded animation</name>
<description>Cel shading (often misspelled as `cell shading`) or toon shading is a type of non-photorealistic rendering designed to make 3-D computer graphics appear to be flat. Cel-shading is often used to mimic the style of a comic book or cartoon. It is somewhat recent, appearing from around the beginning of the twenty-first century. The name comes from cels (short for celluloid), the clear sheets of acetate which are painted on for use in traditional 2D animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3435" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>eating of humans</name>
<description>The eating of humans, also called man-eating, is the practice of some species to prey on human beings for nourishment. Examples of possible hunters may include Earth animals, alien species, zombies or other undead, and so forth. Eating of humans is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3815 [human cannibalism]; the former is about other species eating people, while the latter is about humans eating fellow humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3580" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-01-05">
<name>cliffhanger ending</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4004" parentid="2638" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>organic mecha</name>
<description>An organic mecha is a mecha that has organic tissue in its composition. The most prominent historical example is http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion].</description>
<picurl>224892.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4342" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-06">
<name>large-scale war</name>
<description>When the whole world, or, at least, a big part of it, partakes in the hell that is war.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4404" parentid="2274" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-28">
<name>real robot</name>
<description>A smaller form of mecha with no special abilities. They are mostly used by deploying them in battle just like modern tanks. They can be mass produced and their pilots (usually military officers or soldiers) are (mostly) interchangeable. Tanks are often a threat to them and they are more easily destroyed than their bigger counterparts.</description>
<picurl>42787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4809" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>superstition</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4860" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>lost love</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5150" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-11">
<name>asymmetric warfare</name>
<description>Asymmetric warfare is war between conflicting groups whose relative military power differs, or whose strategy or tactics differ significantly.
Asymmetric warfare can describe a conflict in which the resources of two groups differ in essence, and in the struggle, they interact and attempt to exploit each other`s weaknesses.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6614" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-12">
<name>Animeism</name>
<description>Animeism is a late-night Japanese programming block established in April 2012. It is devoted to anime and broadcast each Thursday night on MBS, in a fashion similar to Fuji TV`s http://anidb.net/t3865 [noitaminA] that also airs on Thursdays. Just like noitaminA, the block airs two series back to back. From April 2015 onwards, the block was moved to Friday nights.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>63625.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6849" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-19">
<name>organism cloning</name>
<description>Organism cloning, also called reproductive cloning, is the creation of an organism that is genetically identical to another. While this is a natural phenomenon in many species, this tag is specifically about artificial organism cloning, as in Dolly the sheep. Cloning of multicellular organisms, and especially of human beings, remains both a scientific frontier and a highly controversial subject, especially in regards to its ethics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="61355" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-31">
<rating votes="47">5.79</rating>
<name>Samari Ittan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female pilot appointed as leader during their deployment. Her skill and popularity are unmatched, and she`s very popular with the male pilots. More than a few of them want to photosynthesize with Samari, but she doesn`t let it bother her.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>150912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61356" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-31">
<rating votes="32">7.38</rating>
<name>Hiyama Lalah</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dorm mother of the pilot dorms. She`s a bear-type dorm mother in charge of running the dorm for pilots and cadets. She`s usually very nice, but she gets mad when people call her by her first name, Lalah, and her wild instincts are let loose.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>150916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61357" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-24">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Tanba Shinsuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161572.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="416" picture="23206.jpg">Saka Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61358" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-14">
<rating votes="40">6.21</rating>
<name>Sasaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61359" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-31">
<rating votes="16">7.02</rating>
<name>Seii Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Commands the Guardian squads under Captain Kobayashi.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>150913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1441" picture="18827.jpg">Tsuboi Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61360" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-28">
<rating votes="54">8.17</rating>
<name>Kobayashi Kanchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The mysterious young female captain of the Sidonia spaceship who commands the Guardians into attacking the enemy Gauna aliens. Known to most just as The 28th Generation Captain, her face appears concealed behind a Japanese Kabuki mask most of the time.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>150914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61361" type="appears in" update="2014-03-31">
<rating votes="6">6.25</rating>
<name>Yamano Eiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guardian Pilot Cadet, 628th generation. A studious young woman, who achieved her position as a cadet through hard work, so she holds some antagonism towards Nagate and Izana who got their assignments under special conditions.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>150911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38753" picture="145652.jpg">Mori Nanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61362" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-05">
<rating votes="45">1.37</rating>
<name>Kunato Norio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guardian Pilot Cadet, 628th generation. Cadet Training Unit ID# TS 岐(Ku) - 001.
His skills are extremely fine, and he prides himself as one of the top cadets. He`s also to become the 8th generation heir to Kunato Developments, and is extremely proud. He discriminates against Nagate and Izana, considering them sub-humans, and doesn`t think too well of the fact that Nagate is the one piloting the hero`s Guardian, Tsugumori.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>150908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61363" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-17">
<rating votes="21">3.52</rating>
<name>Kunato Mozuku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61364" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-26">
<rating votes="13">4.26</rating>
<name>Tsuruuchi Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61365" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-28">
<rating votes="58">8.21</rating>
<name>Hoshijiro Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61366" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-28">
<rating votes="71">7.19</rating>
<name>Shinatose Izana</name>
<gender>intersexual</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61367" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-13">
<rating votes="43">5.94</rating>
<name>Midorikawa Yuhata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Midorikawa Yuhata suddenly transfers into the Guardian Pilot Training Academy`s 628th generation. Her older brother is a member of Sidonia`s most distinguished and strongest Guardian unit, the Akai squad. Her hobby is building plastic models of Guardians.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>150910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61368" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-31">
<rating votes="26">6.55</rating>
<name>Ochiai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain`s Assistant. Aide to Captain Kobayashi and the young man responsible for Nagate`s care.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>150915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61369" type="main character in" update="2015-12-13">
<rating votes="68">5.89</rating>
<name>Tanikaze Nagate</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The series main protagonist who was created by his grandfather deep inside Sidonia, thus he did not underwent the special genetic treatment to develop the ability to perform photosintesis and must eat on a daily basis like a regular human for nutrition. Despite having a hard time adapting to Sidonia`s way of life and getting in trouble constantly while being rejected by the other humans due to not being aware of the laws and attributes of the new culture, he eventually becomes the spaceship`s ace pilot after saving the day on several missions.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>150905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61370" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-28">
<rating votes="26">6.28</rating>
<name>Honoka Ren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the eleven Honoka sisters who are all Guardian pilots. They are long haired albino females who appear identical due to being human clones.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>150909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61371" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-28">
<rating votes="29">6.09</rating>
<name>Honoka En</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the eleven Honoka sisters who are all Guardian pilots. They are long haired albino females who appear identical due to being human clones.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>150909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61372" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-28">
<rating votes="14">6.69</rating>
<name>Honoka Hou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the eleven Honoka sisters who are all Guardian pilots. They are long haired albino females who appear identical due to being human clones.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>150909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66228" type="appears in" update="2014-05-23">
<rating votes="3">6.80</rating>
<name>Saitou Hiroki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67336" type="appears in" update="2014-05-09">
<rating votes="3">6.37</rating>
<name>Akai Mochikuni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67337" type="appears in" update="2014-05-09">
<rating votes="3">3.11</rating>
<name>Momose Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67338" type="appears in" update="2014-05-09">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Aoki Kashiwade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67339" type="appears in" update="2014-05-09">
<rating votes="3">4.25</rating>
<name>Midorikawa Izumo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11275" picture="65394.jpg">Suzuki Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67688" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<rating votes="2">2.51</rating>
<name>Kangoshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67689" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Roujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="599" picture="226547.jpg">Naya Rokurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67690" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Josei Announcer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67692" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<name>Koukouchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="249" picture="46910.jpg">Miyagawa Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67693" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Imada</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="16828" picture="171539.jpg">Anzai Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67694" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-31">
<rating votes="23">5.19</rating>
<name>Shinatose Yure</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67695" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<rating votes="2">2.57</rating>
<name>Tanikaze Nagate</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156089.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67696" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<name>Sidonia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>156092.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67697" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<name>Tsugumori</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>156093.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67698" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<name>Ichihachishiki Moribito</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>156094.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67699" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<name>Ga487</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156100.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67700" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<name>Ga488</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156102.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67701" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<name>Benisuzume</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156103.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67702" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Ga491</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156104.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67703" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<name>Ga489</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156105.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67704" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<rating votes="4">9.43</rating>
<name>Beni Hoshijiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67705" type="appears in" update="2014-05-31">
<rating votes="16">8.10</rating>
<name>Ena Hoshijiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67828" type="appears in" update="2015-06-14">
<name>Nakazono</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="37111" picture="136419.jpg">Kubo Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67829" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-30">
<rating votes="14">5.16</rating>
<name>Tahiro Numi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67936" type="appears in" update="2014-06-13">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Ga541</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156629.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68045" type="appears in" update="2014-06-20">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Ga542</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156915.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68050" type="appears in" update="2014-06-20">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Samari Han Soujuushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68439" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Takahashi Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="68440" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<name>Houraichou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12783" picture="225340.jpg">Fujii Yukiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74394" type="appears in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="4">4.60</rating>
<name>Honoka Shimai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75927" type="appears in" update="2015-06-14">
<name>Toua Juukou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>174645.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="75928" type="appears in" update="2015-06-14">
<name>Kunato Kaihatsu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>174646.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="75929" type="appears in" update="2015-06-14">
<name>Fushi no Sen`in-kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Immortal Ship Committee is a group of individuals aboard the Sidonia who are deemed essential to the ship`s mission and are kept alive indefinitely with biotechnology.
Starting about 600 years before the beginning of the story, the core members of the Immortal Ship Committee - Kobayashi, Hiyama, Saitou, and Ochiai - began taking drugs that made them immune to aging and disease. As time went on, more members were added to the Committee until, one hundred years before the storyline, there were 25 members of the Immortal Ship Committee. They were led by Kobayashi, and had the ultimate goal of delivering Sidonia to a safe and habitable star system.
While some members of the Immortal Ship Committee live in the flesh, most of them live inside mechanical shells that protect their bodies from the diseases of aging. These members are unnamed, but appear to be the actual committee (also called the Assembly) members that make decisions for Sidonia. Their real names are not given and they are referred to by numbers. The only visible portion of their body are their faces, which are covered by skeletal masks and hide their youthful appearance. Physically, the members of the Immortal Ship Committee look as if they were in their late twenties.
Fearing for the survival of Sidonia, they try to remove Captain Kobayashi from her position, with Member #5 presenting himself as the next captain. However, shortly after he does so, the clone Ochiai kills him and every other member of the committee present.
After the murder of the committee members, only six immortals remain on Sidonia.
Source: wikia</description>
<picture>174647.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="151624" update="2013-07-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-07-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158757" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="20">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選択</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Choice</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Fedakârlıklar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158758" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">栄光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Glory</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Zafer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eikou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158759" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="18">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Starry Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Unutuluş</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshizora</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158760" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="20">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初陣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Unutuluş</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uijin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159467" update="2014-04-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不死</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Undead</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ölümsüzlük</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159468" update="2014-04-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="18">4.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚悟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resolve</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Çözümleme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakugo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159469" update="2014-04-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敬礼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Salute</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Selamlamalar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keirei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159470" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">漂流</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adrift</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sürüklenme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyouryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159471" update="2014-04-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159472" update="2014-04-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160156" update="2014-05-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="16">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰艦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Returning to the Ship</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yuva</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160157" update="2014-05-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝突</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Collision</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Çarpışma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoutotsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160158" update="2014-05-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Determination</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kararlar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketsui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160159" update="2014-05-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">眼差</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gaze</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Empati</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manazashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169822" update="2015-07-15">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
