<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9893" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-10-09</startdate>
<enddate>2013-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">BlazBlue: Alter Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">BLAZBLUE ALTER MEMORY</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">BlazBlue: Alter Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Blazblue Alter Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">苍翼默示录 Alter Memory</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="30352">For fans only. Waste ur time at ur own liking</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="89628">For fans only.

It gives a vibe that it`s going to become better in a moment but it never does.
Shallow.

My vote: 5.0
*** Check up my profile for my voting system and genre preferences ***</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="382591">Valuable source of informations about characters and story if you played BlazBlue game.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="727010">As a fan of the actual games I can say if you actually play the games then you`ll want to watch this too. It covers a few things not covered in Continuum Shift (which this show actually is a adaptation of). If you aren`t a fan of the game series however this show might be hard for you to get a grasp on due to the nature of things that occur within it such as time travel and the powers. To fans this would be perfectly natural and they would understand the names given to things such as the weapons which they don`t explain in the show.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://blazblue-am.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="11225" type="Animation Work">Hoods Entertainment</name>
<name id="2932" type="Character Design">Shitaya Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="4556" type="Series Composition">Akao Deko</name>
<name id="1794" type="Direction">Tachibana Hideki</name>
<name id="2932" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shitaya Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="37230" type="Animation Work">TeamKG</name>
<name id="38590" type="Music">Arte Refact</name>
</creators>
<description>The story is set in December of 2199, when the streets are full of anticipation for the end of the year and the start of the new one. Amid the celebrations, word spreads that Ragna the Bloodedge, an SS-class rebel with the highest ever bounty on his head, has appeared in the 13th Hierarchical City of Kagutsuchi. The apparent aim of Ragna or the "Grim Reaper" is the destruction of the system controlling the world. To collect the bounty, a motley array of unrivaled fighters converge on Kagutsuchi.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="759">2.41</permanent>
<temporary count="771">5.32</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>136806.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15344</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18767</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>32502</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://blazblue-am.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>BlazBlue_Alter_Memory</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>BLAZBLUE#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3169</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>346825</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16518</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00OVDXJ82</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="201" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>bounty hunter</name>
<description>A bounty hunter is one who hunts and captures targets (be it people, animals, etc.) for monetary gain, preferably without killing/destroying their target. Despite being illegal in most of the world today, it is a legal profession in the United States and Philippines (a former commonwealth of the US), who are known as "bail enforcement agents".
If they are only and constantly hired to kill, they are likely an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1869" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>familiar spirit</name>
<description>A familiar spirit is a spirit, typically animal-shaped, which is summoned by a magic-user usually to perform various menial tasks. In witchcraft a typical familiar spirit takes the form of a black cat, hence the superstition that a black cat is bad luck.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2461" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>domestic cat</name>
<description>The cat (Felis catus or Felis silvestris catus), also known as the domestic cat to distinguish it from other felines and felids, is a small, usually furry, domesticated, and carnivorous mammal. Cats are valued by humans for companionship and their ability to hunt vermin and household pests, and are often kept as indoor pets, in which case they are also called housecats; they have been associated with humans for at least 9,500 years and are currently the most popular pet in the world, being found almost everywhere on Earth.
Cats are similar in anatomy to the other felids, with light, strong and flexible bodies, excellent hearing, sense of smell, and near darkness eyesight, quick reflexes, sharp retractable claws, and teeth adapted to killing small prey. They are skilled predators and hunt over 1,000 species for food. Despite being solitary hunters, cats are a social species, with communication means that include pheromones, body language and a variety of vocalizations, such as meowing, purring, trilling, hissing, growling and grunting.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>41283.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2802" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-14">
<name>action game</name>
<description>Any game where reflexes are the key to the gameplay, violence is optional.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3592" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-30">
<name>only makes sense with original work knowledge</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3826" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-26">
<name>evil laugh</name>
<description>The thing all great evil villains do after saying/doing something evil.
Some notable examples of great evil villains with evil laughs: Dr. Evil, Dr. Horrible, The Joker, Lelouche, Light, and Mickey Mouse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5874" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>guns are useless</name>
<description>Guns are about as effective as throwing tissue while only manly things like swords, spears, and bare fists are any use at all.
If the weapon shoots a projectile faster than human eyes can track, it is useless. Most guns only serve as a filler for the protagonist to dodge all their shots so they can kill them with a "real" weapon.
The sniper rifle is an occasional exception to this rule. This is because it can be used to quickly and efficiently reduce the amount of character development the animators have to worry about.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6055" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-15">
<name>time loop</name>
<description>A time loop is a common plot device in science fiction (especially in universes where time travel is commonplace). Events in the story repeat themselves a number of times with or without some variation with each pass. Most characters either do not realise this is occurring or are attempting to break the cycle in some way. 
One well-known example of this is in the 1993 film Groundhog Day, in which the main character is the only one aware of the time loop, although time loops had appeared in many fictional works prior to that. Stories with time loops commonly center on correcting past mistakes or on getting a character to recognise some key truth; escape from the loop may then follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="55913" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-07">
<rating votes="1">7.36</rating>
<name>Iron Tager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Originally the leader of an Ikaruga unit, Tager suffered a mortal wound during the Ikaruga Civil War and was forced to withdraw. He was revived as Iron Tager, an enormous cyborg, by Kokonoe whom he pledged loyalty to afterward. After his revival, he bears a similar resemblance to a demon, which resulted in him dubbed as the "Red Devil of Sector Seven". He is feared by many, but in truth he is very calm and calculated, only engaging in violence when necessary. He has resumed his duties since his revival as a cyborg and is currently not only pursuing Hakumen, but also Ragna as a secondary target. In the true ending of Continuum Shift, he and Makoto travel with Noel to Ikaruga after Noel has been saved by Ragna.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>145545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55914" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-16">
<rating votes="4">6.56</rating>
<name>Kokonoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kokonoe is Tager`s superior at Sector Seven, Lotte (who became Arakune) and Litchi`s former employer and Jubei and Nine`s daughter. She is a half-beastkin, two of the Six Heroes, though she shows unexplained disdain for this fact, supposedly "staying angry for weeks" when Jubei is mentioned. Kokonoe is a rather serious and cynical woman with no regard for emotions, and always strives for Tager to complete his missions without fail; however, she can on rare occasions be quite personable, mostly around her creations. She`s displayed and perceived as cranky most of the time. She has a deep hatred for Terumi, because he killed her mother, Nine. She and Taokaka possess a few similar personality traits, something that most note as `more in common than they realize`, due to their impatient nature and short attention span. She is also the host of the `Help Me, Professor Kokonoe!` comedy segments.</description>
<picture>144317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4983" picture="171535.jpg">Matsuura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55915" type="main character in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<name>Jin Kisaragi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jin Kisaragi is a former Major in the NOL and one of its elite commanding officers as well as the rival to Ragna. He is always cool and calm, but is also jealous, ambitious, and possessive with little care for others, treating them like they are mere obstacles. He displayed formidable actions to gain his rank during the Ikaruga Civil War. When he heard that Ragna the Bloodedge had arrived on the scene, he quickly abandoned his post to hunt him down by himself. The truth, however, is that Ragna is Jin`s biological brother, and Jin`s early feelings of rivalry were furthered by his visions of the future and his Nox Nyctores` amplification of his emotions. Terumi caused Jin`s mind to hack off Ragna`s arm (later nearly dying without the intervention of Rachel) and supposedly kill Saya, and Jin often says that he`s looking forward to killing Ragna again. After the incident, he was adopted into the Kisaragi house, a highly powerful and respected family within the NOL. He possesses a notable psychosis, said to be caused by his sword, the Nox Nyctores Mucro Algesco: Yukianesa.
Source: Wikipedia </description>
<picture>143409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55916" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-09">
<rating votes="10">7.37</rating>
<name>Taokaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taokaka, or Tao for short, is a catgirl who is a member of the Kaka tribe, wearing a large coat that obscures her true face, only exposing beady red eyes and a row of teeth. She wants to get back the sky above her village, which was sealed off by humans building cities above her village, was recently sent by the Elder to retrieve the bounty on Ragna`s head, becoming a vigilante in the process. Despite this resolve, she is considerably food-obsessed and forgetful, often falling asleep on a whim, becoming hungry moments after a meal, or forgetting details moments after hearing them. She is good friends with Litchi, affectionately referring to her as "Boobie Lady".
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>143991.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55917" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-23">
<rating votes="4">4.18</rating>
<name>Tsubaki Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsubaki Yayoi is Jin`s childhood friend/relative and Noel`s former roommate from the Military Academy and a member of the NOL`s 0 Division. She is described as a straight-A student, and has a rather no-nonsense personality. She`s very serious and reserved, and is a member of the dignified Yayoi family. In the true ending of Calamity Trigger, where she appears as a sub-character, she is assigned by Hazama to kill Noel and Jin.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55918" type="main character in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="13">5.41</rating>
<name>Noel Vermillion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noel Vermillion is a young girl who was found amidst the burning fields of Ikaruga where she was rescued, and then adopted by the family of Vermillion and is the main heroine of the series. It was because of her outstanding combat activity that she became a high-ranking member of the NOL using the Nox Nyctores revolver Arcus Diabolus: Bolverk, which apparently does not fire actual bullets but rather inflicts damage by creating distortions in dimensional space. Noel also seems to be extremely reliant psychologically on her guns, to the point where she breaks down crying if they are taken away from her. She was made Jin`s subordinate by the NOL, although Jin treated her poorly due to her resemblance of Saya. When Jin rushed off to hunt down Ragna without permission from the NOL, Noel was assigned to stop him and bring him back to his post at the Library.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>143408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30757" picture="82468.jpg">Kondou Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55919" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="4">3.95</rating>
<name>Hazama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuki Terumi is the main antagonist of the BlazBlue series. He is a ghost who has taken the alias Hazama, a captain of the NOL`s Intelligence Division. At first, he appears to be supervising Noel`s actions to keep her in line, but he has a sinister hidden agenda. He is also the creator of the BlazBlue and the mastermind responsible for cutting off Ragna`s arm, hacking off Jin`s mind, presumably killing Saya, and most likely causing the space-time distortions. Most who are aware of his presence regard him with contempt and perhaps even fear, as Rachel defiantly stands up to him in one path, but does not attack him in many of the events of BlazBlue: Calamity Trigger. Against Rachel`s warnings, Noel says the words "Dark Susano`o" upon looking at Terumi. Jubei and Hakumen mention that the seal holding him may have been broken and Takamagahara may have been reactivated, and Jubei notifies Hakumen of his return. He seems to be at odds with the other remaining members of the Six Heroes. Kokonoe has a murderous attitude toward him because he killed her mother, Nine, and in Terumi`s own words Rachel is the only being currently capable of "keeping up" with him. At the end of Story Mode, he issues confidential verbal orders to Tsubaki to kill Noel and Jin.</description>
<picture>143411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55920" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-23">
<rating votes="5">3.87</rating>
<name>Makoto Nanaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makoto Nanaya is another classmate of Noel`s and Jin`s from the Military Academy, much like Tsubaki. She is a beastkin with squirrel-like features, and is considerably hyperactive with a short attention span. She is outgoing, adventurous, and has inhuman reflexes. She has a few complexes about her race but nonetheless proudly acknowledges who she is. She seems to be working under the NOL`s Intelligence Division, but is actually an informant for Sector Seven. In the true ending, she transfers to Sector Seven in order to protect Noel. In battle, she fights using her specially-made cross tonfas.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144708.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10361" picture="38073.jpg">Isomura Tomomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55921" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-01">
<rating votes="6">4.85</rating>
<name>Litchi Faye Ling</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Litchi Faye-Ling is a renowned doctor living in Orient Town, located in Kagutsuchi. She owns a clinic there and is helped by her assistant Linhua. She had worked with Tager and Kokonoe in Sector Seven until the incident where Lotte Carmine, one of her colleagues, became Arakune. She defends the local townspeople from Arakune and seeks to restore him to his former self through any means necessary, even through death. She also seems to respect Bang Shishigami, even apologizing to him if she defeats him in a match, although she remains unaware of the true extent of his feelings for her. She is often subject to adoration for her noticeably large bust, particularly from Taokaka who likes to grope them. She is well-known and trusted by the Kaka clan living beneath Kagutsuchi, often bringing them food or teaching their members. At some point she took an object from the Boundary, her panda hairpiece named Lao Jiu. It acts as an amplifier of Seithr, and seems to allow her control over her staff. She is also the main character in the supplemental "Teach Me, Miss Litchi!" episodes, where she attempts to teach Taokaka the intricacies of the BlazBlue world.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55922" type="main character in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="7">8.81</rating>
<name>Ragna the Bloodedge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ragna the Bloodedge is the main protagonist of the BlazBlue series. Also known as the Grim Reaper, he is feared by the NOL for being the most powerful individual to have ever rebel against them since the Ikaruga Civil War. His actions, which included destroying countless number of their branches, has labeled him the most wanted criminal to received the largest bounty ever in the history of the NOL. He possesses a powerful form of ars magus called the Azure Grimoire, or simply referred to as the titular BlazBlue, which is often either the secondary or primary target of those after him and his bounty. His ultimate goal is to destroy the NOL, for he blames them for destroying his family. He is Jin Kisaragi`s biological brother, whose rivalry with him stems from an incident that happened when their sister Saya was presumably killed. His right arm is mechanical because his real one was cut off by Terumi, who had taken control of Jin`s mind. He was resurrected by Rachel as a Dhampir, causing one of his green eyes to turn red and his once-blond hair to white. The BlazBlue he possesses is only a fragment of an imitation; the true Grimoire is actually destined to be wielded by Noel Vermillion.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>143407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55923" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="12">7.75</rating>
<name>Rachel Alucard</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rachel Alucard is a vampire and the current head of the noble Alucard family. Rachel slipped out of her castle in search of fun because she hates to be bored. Due to her hair ties, many characters call her rabbit, a name that irritates her to no end, though Ragna seems to be the only one who can get away with calling her an idiot. Despite her status however, she deeply loathes her vampiric impulses. She seems to be watching Ragna, as she is the one who accidentally turned him into a half-vampire by giving him her powers (this is also the reason behind his heterochromia and healing ability). Due to this, he is one of the only characters who is aware of her. She also watches and toys with the other characters as part of her amusement.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>143410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60282" type="appears in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<name>Kemono Hyoue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Juubei, also known as Mitsuyoshi, is one of the Six Heroes and Ragna`s master who battled the Black Beast alongside Hakumen. As revealed in Phase 0, he was originally named Mitsuyoshi, and did not take up the name Juubei until after the Dark War. He is a beast-man and is the father of Kokonoe. It is also revealed that Taokaka and her clan were genetically engineered from his DNA. Despite his appearance (he is considerably short and does not come off as threatening, resembling a cat more than either of his descendants), he is a powerful warrior, with numerous characters referring to him as the most powerful being on the planet. He is armed with the Nox Nyctores Mucro Somino: Musashi, a pair of kodachi, one stored in each end of the sheath. Supposedly, its power is to cut "what cannot normally be cut", implied that it is able to destroy a magical field or barrier. He works to safeguard his friends in their times of need. An interesting fact to note is that Juubei is actually the one to finish the enemy in Taokaka`s Astral Heat. His former and current names are derived from the famous samurai Yagyuu Juubei Mitsuyoshi.</description>
<picture>143986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60283" type="appears in" update="2013-10-09">
<name>Ragna (Shounenki)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60284" type="appears in" update="2013-11-12">
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<name>Gii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gii is Rachel`s stout bat familiar. He is often burdened by Rachel`s orders during teatime, or by her fits whereinshe has the penchant of either using him as a footrest or pinching his cheek.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>145775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10391" picture="38277.jpg">Zougou Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60285" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="4">6.22</rating>
<name>Nu-No.13-</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nu-13 is a Murakumo Unit who was forged in Kagutsuchi`s Gates of Sheol. She was programmed to terminate anyone she deems as hostile subjects that come near the Gate. Nu is also shown to have a split personality, split between an emotionless girl when around others and a clingy young girl when around Ragna. Nu wants to absorb Ragna and have him join her in destroying the world, because she, too, possesses a piece of the Azure Grimoire (although neither she nor Ragna realized the pieces they possess are actually imitations). When Ragna refuses to join her and breaks her heart, she decides to take him by force. She also knows Hakumen, recognizing him as a "Sankishin Unit". She, as with Noel, was made as a replica of Saya, Ragna and Jin`s sister who is presumed to be dead. They seem to share some of Saya`s memories, though nothing congruous.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>143989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30757" picture="82468.jpg">Kondou Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60286" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="1">5.42</rating>
<name>Hakumen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the Six Heroes, Hakumen is a samurai-like "Susano`o unit" wielding a sword as tall as he is and wearing a mask that completely hides his face. He led mankind to defeat the Black Beast, then when attempting to warn the people that they needed to "repent for their sins" lest the Black Beast return, they trapped him in a space known as the "Edge", where he drifted for nearly a hundred years until Kokonoe discovered him. Kokonoe helped him return to the world, hoping to use him to defeat Terumi, but he set out to achieve his own agendas before being completely salvaged from the Edge. During his journey, he has also shown tremendous respect towards Bang and his unyielding spirit, something truly out-of-character for Hakumen. Hakumen often says that his sword will purify the world of sin and vanquish that which is evil. In truth, Hakumen is Jin`s future self, whose soul was bound to the Susano`o unit after falling into the Gates of Sheol and saved by Rachel. He now possesses the ability to generate seemingly indefinite amounts of energy at will, and his sword, the Nox Nyctores Interfectum is apparently capable of killing characters that otherwise could not be killed or would simply regenerate (i.e. Ragna, Nu, and Arakune). In Continuum Shift, he was taken and imprisoned by Kokonoe, but eventually freed by Rachel, agreeing to help her find Terumi.</description>
<picture>143990.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60720" type="appears in" update="2013-10-23">
<name>Relius Clover</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Relius Clover is one of the main antagonists of the series and is also Carl and Ada`s father, and Ignis` husband. He`s a genius alchemist known as the Puppeteer. His experiments include the creation of Nox Nyctores named Deus Machina: Nirvana, which he harvested his daughter`s body to create. He completed this project with help from Kokonoe of Sector Seven. His own puppet, the Fluctus Redactum: Ignis, was created from the body of his wife, Ignis, who is similar in appearance to Nirvana. He was also involved with the creation of Murakumo Units. Relius is seen alongside Phantom and the Imperator of the Novus Orbis Librarium. He is also working with Hazama to achieve his goals, which at this point are unknown.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60721" type="appears in" update="2013-10-23">
<name>Carl Clover</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Carl Clover is a young boy who, like Noel and Jin, was a student at the Military Academy, but dropped out without warning while Noel and Jin graduated. He is currently after Ragna`s bounty and the Azure Grimoire, leading him to become a vigilante. He travels with a maid-like puppet called Nirvana, whom he believes to be his sister Ada.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144709.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60786" type="appears in" update="2013-10-26">
<name>Linhua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Linhua is a young girl who works as Litchi`s assistant in her clinic in Orient Town.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144811.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38683" picture="145169.jpg">Katou Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60787" type="appears in" update="2013-10-26">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Yuuki Terumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60931" type="appears in" update="2013-12-29">
<name>Nago</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nago is Rachel`s black transmogrifying cat that speaks and acts just as snobbishly as her. He is often seen in umbrella form but he could also morph into and be used as either a Lobelia (bat lance) cannon or a comfy chair.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>147826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17213" picture="46559.jpg">Suzuki Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61233" type="appears in" update="2013-11-07">
<rating votes="3">5.76</rating>
<name>Lambda-No.11-</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lambda-11 is an imitation Murakumo Unit created by Kokonoe by combining the body of the 11th experimental replica of Saya with the soul of Nu, which was recovered after falling into the Gates of Sheol during the conclusion of Calamity Trigger`s Story Mode. Kokonoe completely erased her memory and as a result, Lambda is only interested in carrying out Kokonoe`s orders, although some fragment of her original self manages to resurface when she confronts Ragna.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>145548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30757" picture="82468.jpg">Kondou Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61234" type="appears in" update="2013-11-07">
<name>Valkenhayn R. Hellsing</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Valkenhayn R. Hellsing is one of the Six Heroes and Rachel`s elderly butler and trusted advisor who has served the Alucard family line for generations. He possesses a sharp wit and is concerned for Rachel`s well-being. Valkenhayn seems to be worried about Rachel associating with things below her class (particularly Ragna, although others might apply), but he always acts in a sophisticated and gentlemanly manner. Judging from comments frequently dropped by Rachel, he seems to have once been a vigilante himself. He seems to know Terumi well enough to recognize him on sight, even though Terumi can change shape.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>145547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61235" type="appears in" update="2013-11-07">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Platinum the Trinity</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Platinum the Trinity is a young girl with three personalities named Luna, Sena, and Trinity Glassfield. Luna is a rude young girl; Sena is a polite young boy; and Trinity is the spirit of one of the Six Heroes. Trinity`s personality is locked within her Nox Nyctores, and she is only able to come to the surface for brief periods of time. This Nox Nyctores` full name is Arma Reboare: Muchourin, a bell which has the power to incarnate matter. Platinum normally prefers to avoid violence and lives in the ruins of Ibukido, but came to Kagutsuchi on Jubei`s request in order awaken Bang`s Nox Nyctores. Platinum is very fond of Jubei; however she harbors a deep hate towards Ragna, apparently because of jealously towards his friendly relationship with Jubei.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>145546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61689" type="appears in" update="2013-11-20">
<name>Shishigami Bang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shishigami Bang is a ninja from Ikaruga village. He lost his home in the Ikaruga Civil War and his master Tenjou at the hands of Jin Kisaragi, and he and his followers began living in Kagutsuchi waiting for the right moment to strike back at Jin and the NOL. There, he declares himself a hero of love and justice, and dedicates himself to exterminating evil and overturning injustice wherever he goes. He is quite overexuberant, prone to speeches and tangents as well as making dramatic entrances.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>146150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61690" type="appears in" update="2013-11-20">
<name>Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23867" picture="157190.jpg">Nanase Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61691" type="appears in" update="2013-11-20">
<name>Kodomo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30202" picture="166938.jpg">Sugiyama Shigemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61692" type="appears in" update="2013-11-20">
<name>Rotenshou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61897" type="appears in" update="2013-11-30">
<name>Arakune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arakune is a black blob-like creature with a white mask who formerly worked alongside Tager and Litchi in Sector Seven. After an attempt to study the Boundary, he became what he is today, now housing innumerable insects with his now-blobby body and thriving on knowledge. His horrible condition has rendered him virtually insane and lacking any reliable memory, as well as distorting his speech to near incoherency.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>146491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3154" picture="24136.jpg">Hikida Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62103" type="appears in" update="2013-12-05">
<rating votes="3">5.65</rating>
<name>Mikado</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62648" type="appears in" update="2013-12-29">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Mu-No.12-</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mu-12 is a Murakumo Unit and Noel Vermillion`s true form after fusing with the True Azure.</description>
<picture>147825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30757" picture="82468.jpg">Kondou Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="154522" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">確率事象</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Probabilistic Events</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Continuum Shift</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakuritsu Jishou</title>
<summary>As Ragna recovers from his wounds, Rachel meets with three mysterious beings and Noel runs into an old friend and classmate from the Military Academy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="154523" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傍観の眼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Observing Eye</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le regard de l`Observateur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boukan no Me</title>
<summary>Rachel has her showdown with Takemikazuchi, Hazama shows his true colors, and Ragna faces a fight with yet another bounty hunter.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="154524" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼の継承者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Azure Successor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`Héritière de l`Azure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ao no Keishousha</title>
<summary>Rachel and Hazama watch over Ragna, hoping against hope that their expectations will be betrayed, in spite of the fact that all has gone as it always has.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="154525" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤き反逆者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Rebel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le renégat écarlate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akaki Hangyakusha</title>
<summary>Ragna is on a one-man rampage against the ruling body, the Novus Orbis Librarium. And a mysterious woman named Rachel directs him to go to the 13th Hierarchical City of Kagutsuchi next.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="154860" update="2016-05-06">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154861" update="2016-05-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155231" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">機械仕掛けの魂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mechanical Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une âme mécanique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikaijikake no Tamashii</title>
<summary>Hazama throws an obstacle in Ragna`s way to buy himself some time. This encounter leads Ragna to have an entirely different sort of experience with Lambda.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="155232" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">審判の羽根</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wings of Judgment</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les ailes du jugement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinpan no Hane</title>
<summary>Tager continues to slowly track Noel. Noel finds Tsubaki, which results in a complicated showdown. And Rachel leads Ragna to where he needs to be and to confront what he already knows.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="155233" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">偽りの世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">False World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un monde de mensonges</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuwari no Sekai</title>
<summary>Kokonoe`s little gambit with Ragna plays out. In the meantime, Jin is still searching for Ragna, but instead, ends up being found by Bang Shishigami, who wants revenge against Jin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="155234" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">1.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白き双銃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pair of White Guns</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les pistolets d`Albâtre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroki Soujuu</title>
<summary>Rachel conducts her own mysterious business as usual, porting from place to place. Kokonoe has her own agenda and sends Tager to carry out a mission. And Ragna works towards a full recovery with the help of some friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="156137" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来への代償</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Price for the Future</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le prix de l`avenir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai e no Daishou</title>
<summary>Kokonoe and Rachel believe that Noel`s transformation into Mu is irreversible, but Ragna refuses to give up on Noel.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="156138" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">叢雲覚醒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Murakumo Awakens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`éveil de la Murakumo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Murakumo Kakusei</title>
<summary>Terumi`s designs for Noel come to fruition and he crows about what he has achieved to Ragna, even as Ragna fights a losing battle against him to save Noel.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="156139" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神殺しの繭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The God-Killer`s Cocoon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cocon du tueur de dieux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamigoroshi no Mayu</title>
<summary>Makoto and Noel face off against Hazama as he explains to Noel what her true place is in this world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="156140" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秩序の力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Power of Order</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pouvoir de l`Ordre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chitsujo no Chikara</title>
<summary>As Makoto works to get Noel to safety, she explains her faith in Kokonoe and her doubts about Hazama. And Tsubaki finally finds Jin again, who is still struggling to deal with his recalcitrant weapon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="177083" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2014-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぶるらじ風 キャラクターコメンタリー #6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BlueRadio Character Commentary #6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BlueRadi Kaze Character Commentary #6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177084" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2014-04-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぶるらじ風 キャラクターコメンタリー #5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BlueRadio Character Commentary #5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BlueRadi Kaze Character Commentary #5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177085" update="2016-05-06">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2014-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぶるらじ風 キャラクターコメンタリー #4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BlueRadio Character Commentary #4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BlueRadi Kaze Character Commentary #4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177086" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2014-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぶるらじ風 キャラクターコメンタリー #3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BlueRadio Character Commentary #3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BlueRadi Kaze Character Commentary #3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177087" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2014-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぶるらじ風 キャラクターコメンタリー #2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BlueRadio Character Commentary #2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BlueRadi Kaze Character Commentary #2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177088" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぶるらじ風 キャラクターコメンタリー #1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BlueRadio Character Commentary #1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BlueRadi Kaze Character Commentary #1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177465" update="2016-05-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177466" update="2016-05-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177467" update="2018-12-10">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending of Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="185119" update="2017-02-27">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
