<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9895" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-03-27</startdate>
<enddate>2013-05-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Puchimas! Petit Idolmaster: Takatsuki Gold Densetsu Special!! Haruka-san Matsuri</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ぷちます! プチ・アイドルマスター: 高槻ゴールド伝説すぺしゃる!! はるかさん祭り</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Puchim@s! Petit Idolm@ster OVA</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9445" type="Parent Story">Puchimas! Petit Idolmaster</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="3512" type="Original Work">Bandai Namco Games</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the http://anidb.net/t2805 [4-koma] spin-off manga by http://anidb.net/cr34095 [Akane], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr28845 [Dengeki Maou] since 2011.
While searching a remote island, Producer finds a shrine resembling Haruka-san and proposes a trip to investigate its artifacts. The gang splits up into groups to investigate a few different sites on the island. What will they find on this adventure?
— written by CDB-Man
Note: Episode 1 was bundled with the limited edition of the [i]Puchimas! manga, volume 5. Episodes 2-4 are included in volumes 1-3 respectively of the BD/DVD for http://anidb.net/a9445 [Puchimas! Petit Idolmaster].[/i]</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="118">4.25</permanent>
<temporary count="120">6.15</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>136841.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19886</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18781</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://puchimas.com/1st/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Puchimas!_Petit_Idolmaster</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ぷちます!_-PETIT_IDOLM@STER-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>351863</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3934" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-10">
<name>non-linear</name>
<description>The story is told achronologically.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4117" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-01">
<name>rolling boulder trap</name>
<description>Nothing beats the rolling boulder trap in case you want to smash those tomb raiders to a blood pool to teach them a lesson. Its simplicity and versatility is matched only by its destructiveness and the sheer terror it evokes.</description>
<picurl>192783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4151" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>German suplex</name>
<description>A wrestling move commonly used in a slapstick manner by one of the more unique characters in a series. The move typically signals a strong and coordinated individual (who may or may not actually be a wrestler). Often the move will be deployed on the same person over and over again as part of a running gag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6293" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="100">5.66</rating>
<name>Amami Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4712" picture="27521.jpg">Nakamura Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6294" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-08">
<rating votes="89">4.83</rating>
<name>Futami Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6295" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-08">
<rating votes="92">6.12</rating>
<name>Futami Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78207.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6296" type="main character in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="101">6.39</rating>
<name>Kikuchi Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3006" picture="226210.jpg">Hirata Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6297" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-10">
<rating votes="86">7.15</rating>
<name>Miura Azusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6298" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="77">5.78</rating>
<name>Hagiwara Yukiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1876" picture="66007.jpg">Asakura Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6299" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-10">
<rating votes="138">7.71</rating>
<name>Minase Iori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75114.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6300" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-10">
<rating votes="132">6.52</rating>
<name>Takatsuki Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4714" picture="171986.jpg">Nigo Mayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6301" type="main character in" update="2011-07-10">
<rating votes="51">6.20</rating>
<name>Akizuki Ritsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2039" picture="41388.jpg">Wakabayashi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6302" type="main character in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="187">8.37</rating>
<name>Hoshii Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4713" picture="186249.jpg">Hasegawa Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6303" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="162">7.76</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Chihaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28763" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-17">
<rating votes="105">8.19</rating>
<name>Shijou Takane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28764" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-17">
<rating votes="87">8.35</rating>
<name>Ganaha Hibiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33053" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="47">5.89</rating>
<name>Otonashi Kotori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6958" picture="31903.jpg">Takita Juri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49238" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="6">6.14</rating>
<name>Afuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4713" picture="186249.jpg">Hasegawa Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49239" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="6">4.86</rating>
<name>Io</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>95001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49240" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="7">5.35</rating>
<name>Koami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>95002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49241" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="7">5.35</rating>
<name>Komami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>95003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49242" type="main character in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="17">8.05</rating>
<name>Takanya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>95007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49243" type="main character in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="7">6.30</rating>
<name>Chicchan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2039" picture="41388.jpg">Wakabayashi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49244" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="7">5.92</rating>
<name>Chihyaa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>95000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49245" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="6">5.55</rating>
<name>Chibiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49246" type="main character in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="8">7.14</rating>
<name>Haruka-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4712" picture="27521.jpg">Nakamura Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49247" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="5">6.95</rating>
<name>Piyopiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>95006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6958" picture="31903.jpg">Takita Juri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49248" type="main character in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="6">5.93</rating>
<name>Makochii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>95004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3006" picture="226210.jpg">Hirata Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49249" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="8">7.31</rating>
<name>Miura-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>95005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49250" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="8">6.46</rating>
<name>Yayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>95008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4714" picture="171986.jpg">Nigo Mayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49251" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-02">
<rating votes="11">6.70</rating>
<name>Yukipo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>95009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1876" picture="66007.jpg">Asakura Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50890" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-31">
<rating votes="3">8.71</rating>
<name>Producer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128688.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57254" type="appears in" update="2013-06-16">
<name>Supepapupu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57255" type="appears in" update="2013-06-16">
<name>Rideikudon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57256" type="appears in" update="2013-06-16">
<name>Orochi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146422" update="2016-06-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わぁるど2-3 いふうどうどう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">World 2-3: Majestic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">World 2-3: Ifuudoudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146423" update="2016-06-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わぁるど2-2 あっついなぁ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">World 2-2: It`s So Hot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">World 2-2: Attsuinaa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151185" update="2016-06-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わるど1 わんだふるでいず / わるど2-1 きみょうなほこら / わるど3 いつもいっしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">World 1: Wonderful Days / World 2-1: An Odd Shrine / World 3: Always Together</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">World 1: Wonderful Days / World 2-1: Kimyou na Hokora / World 3: Itsumo Issho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162563" update="2016-06-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わぁるど2-4 あいどるだもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">World 2-4: We`re Idols, After All</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">World 2-4: Idol Da Mono</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
