<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="992" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-07-08</startdate>
<enddate>2000-07-08</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Pocket Monsters: Kesshoutou no Teiou Entei</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon: Movie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon 3: Lord of the Unknown Tower</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Pokémon 3: Im Bann des Unbekannten</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Покемон: Повелитель кристальной башни</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Покемон: чары Анноуна</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Pokemon 3: Zaklęcie Unown</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="synonym">Pokémon 3: Unownien loitsu</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="synonym">Pokémon 3</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="synonym">Pokémon 3: Kristallitorni</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 ポケットモンスター 結晶塔の帝王 ENTEI</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Pokemon 3: The Movie - Spell of the Unown</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Pokémon 3: Im Bann der Icognito</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Pokémon 3 : Le sort des Zarbis</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Pokémon 3: Zaklęcie Unown</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Pokémon 3: Unowns Förtrollning</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Pokémon 3: O Feitiço dos Unown</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Pokémon 3: Entei - O Feitiço dos Unown</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Pokémon 3</title>
<title xml:lang="da" type="official">Pokémon 3</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Pokémon 3: Entei</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">Unown פוקימון 3: ההרפתקה של</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Pokémon: Az Öntudatlan betűi</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Pokemonai 3</title>
<title xml:lang="sk" type="official">Pokémon 3</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="230" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters</anime>
<anime id="6798" type="Other">Pichu to Pikachu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.pokemon.co.jp/anime/movie/2000/</url>
<creators>
<name id="734" type="Work">Shogakukan Productions</name>
<name id="4464" type="Character Design">Ichiishi Sayuri</name>
<name id="4235" type="Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
<name id="5780" type="Original Plan">Tajiri Satoshi</name>
<name id="5660" type="Music">Miyazaki Shinji</name>
<name id="6897" type="Music">Tanaka Hirokazu</name>
<name id="5573" type="Character Design">Matsubara Norihiro</name>
<name id="2803" type="Character Design">Kagawa Hisashi</name>
<name id="2803" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kagawa Hisashi</name>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
</creators>
<description>The Pokemon master Ash must rescue his mother from the encasement of a crystal tower.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1385">3.88</permanent>
<temporary count="1401">6.13</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221881.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>831</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1118</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2357</identifier>
<identifier>etsacr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pokemon.co.jp/anime/movie/2000/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Pokémon_3:_The_Movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版ポケットモンスター_結晶塔の帝王_ENTEI</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>187</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>162552</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7208</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="533" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="8">5.52</rating>
<name>Chicorita</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chikorita is the Grass-type Starter Pokémon in Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal. One may also get this Pokémon in Pokémon Emerald by completing the Hoenn Dex (not including Jirachi and Deoxys). It is reptilian in appearance, but it has a large leaf sprouting from its head, a collar of crystalline seeds around its neck, and a short tail. Chikorita, by nature, are docile Pokémon that love to soak up the sun`s rays. The leaf serves multiple purposes; in its natural environment, its leaf detects the density of humidity and temperature in the atmosphere to help it seek warm places. The pleasant aroma that wafts from the leaf can be used by Chikorita in battle by waving it around to becalm the foe and keep it at bay. In the Pokémon anime, Ash Ketchum caught a Chikorita early on its adventure through Johto, after saving it from a sudden snowstorm. Chikorita is very affectionate, stubborn, and powerful, often sees Pikachu as a rival for Ash`s affections, and apparently has a crush on Ash. In the episode "Current Events", Chikorita evolves into a Bayleef when Ash was almost in mortal peril.</description>
<picture>243038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="536" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="6">10.00</rating>
<name>Hinoarashi</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cyndaquil is the Fire-type Starter Pokémon in Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal. In Pokémon Emerald you may get Cyndaquil after completing the Hoenn Dex. Cyndaquil are covered with a flame-resistant, dull-yellow fur with a rich streak of blue running from the tip of its snout over its head and spreading out to cover the majority of its back. There are also four spots of red fur on the back. When Cyndaquil is frightened or angry, it can focus its internal energy to produce blazing "spines" of flame from the spots. While it is a quadruped, Cyndaquil is more than capable of maneuvering on two legs. They are based on an echidna.
Cyndaquil are generally timid and not naturally aggressive, and are often seen curled into a ball for protection. This action leaves its back and special flame-emitting vent fur exposed. When predators and enemies stalk too close, Cyndaquil unleashes a furious flame from the vents as a deterrent. If provoked further, Cyndaquil will intensify its flames, creating a smokescreen that will buy it some time to escape.
Cyndaquil has made numerous appearances in the Pokémon anime, mostly under the control of Ash. His Cyndaquil often seemed to be very shy and relaxed, often sleeping. At first, it needed time to warm up and use flamethrower, but with some training from Ash, it is now able to use its flamethrower whenever it wants. It also possesses prodigious dodging capabilities, able to wear opponents down by simply evading long series of attacks over an extended period of time. Cyndaquil is currently at Professor Oak`s lab since Ash decided to make a fresh start when going to Hoenn, and therefore, left all of its Pokémon, except Pikachu, with Professor Oak.</description>
<picture>243041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="539" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="6">4.01</rating>
<name>Waninoko</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Totodile is the Water-type Starter Pokémon in Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal. It resembles a small crocodile and has a short blue body with a yellow band on its chest. On its back and tail are four red spikes. Totodile has a big and prominent jaw, filled with many sharp teeth; it is strong enough to cut down a tree. It`s very energetic, cheerful and rowdy, and occasionally can be seen running through swampy areas, biting and chomping at everything that moves.
In the anime, Ash acquires a Totodile after a duel with Misty to determine its rightful owner. Ash`s Totodile is rather carefree, fun loving, and loves to dance. It is shown to be friendly towards other Pokémon, and is a fast swimmer, as shown in Pokémon Heroes. Ash used Totodile in many battles throughout Johto, including the Johto League. A Totodile seen in the very first episode of the Johto series was very attached to Jessie from Team Rocket, or rather, her long hair (which Totodile loved to bite) that runs down her back. Ash`s Totodile is currently at Professor Oak`s lab since Ash decided to make a fresh start when going to Hoenn, and therefore, left all of his Pokémon except Pikachu with Professor Oak.</description>
<picture>243044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="546" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="8">7.25</rating>
<name>Yorunozuku</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noctowl is the second owl Pokémon, being the evolution of Hoothoot. It is a large bird whose plumage is colored in various shades of brown. Its round head has two piercing, red eyes and two large "eyebrows". These eyebrows help balance Noctowl while it is flying to increase its aerodynamics. When hunting, Noctowl puts its prodigious eyesight to good use to hunt down prey without fail. It is also very good at sneaking up to its victims unnoticed thanks to its supple, soft-feathered wings that allow it to fly without making any noise. When a Noctowl needs to ponder especially deep thoughts, it can rotate its head 180 degrees, which serves to increase its intellectual faculties.
In the anime, a shiny Noctowl has been part of Ash`s team during his travels in Johto. Ash frequently used his Noctowl to explore an area from the sky, or to puncture Team Rocket`s hot-air balloon. Ash used it in many battles throughout Johto, but it is currently living in Professor Oak`s lab since Ash decided to make a fresh start and leave all of his Pokémon except for Pikachu when he left for Hoenn.</description>
<picture>243050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="558" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="4">7.27</rating>
<name>Togepii</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Togepi is a baby Pokémon that hatches from an egg. The Pokédex says that this Pokémon`s "shell is filled with joy" and that it will bring happiness to its trainer as it travels along with him/her. In the Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal games, Togepi first appears as a mystery egg given to the player by a minor character called "Mr. Pokémon", which he/she has to take back to Professor Elm. In FireRed and LeafGreen a character living in the Sevii Islands will give you a Togepi egg, but this event happens only after obtaining the National Pokédex. Like all infant Pokémon, on the day a Togepi hatches, it develops a parental relationship with the first person it sees. (for example, the Togepi would think of the first female it sees as its mother)
In the Pokémon anime, Togepi is the second second-generation Pokémon to be introduced as a character before the release of Pokémon Gold and Silver (Ho-oh was the first). Ash Ketchum discovers an egg in the ancient ruins at Grandfather Canyon. He carries this egg around until the episode "Who Gets to Keep Togepi?". The egg hatches, and after a long dispute it is decided that Misty will keep the newly-hatched Pokémon. Since then, she grows inseparable to it and carries it around everywhere, going frantic whenever it gets lost. She usually keeps it in her backpack when she thinks that it needs protection. The only attacks that it is shown to use are Charm, and more notably, Metronome (which it learned by trying it after witnessing another Pokémon using it), which usually saves Ash and his friends from mortal peril; in one instance, it teleported them out of danger, another, it created a huge explosion, and in another used Reflect.
In a later episode in season six within the Advanced Generation, Misty travels to Hoenn to meet up with Ash, Brock, May, and Max. Due to one of Team Rocket`s plans going wrong, they end up in "Mirage Kingdom", a place where people praise Togepi for they believe it will be their savior. Togepi ends up going into a mirage, followed by Ash and his crew, to discover a Togepi Paradise in ruins. To defend it, it evolves into a Togetic, a Pokémon that makes its first Anime appearance and defeats the villain of "Mirage Kingdom". It then makes the difficult decision of staying in the Togepi Paradise to protect it instead of continuing with Misty. In the end, Misty released Togetic so it can defend Mirage Kingdom and returned to her duties as the Cerulean City gym leader.
The English DVD release of Mewtwo Strikes Back incorrectly refers to Togepi as Pokémon #152.</description>
<picture>243060.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="844" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="20">8.61</rating>
<name>Entei</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Entei is one of the three "Legendary Beasts" that are featured in Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal. According to legend, the Legendary Beasts were reincarnated by Ho-Oh from the spirits of three Pokémon which died in the fire that gave Burnt Tower its name. They are awakened in this tower in their first video game appearance. Other myths maintains that it is born during the eruption of a volcano, and that a new one is born along with each volcano.
Entei is an embodiment of magma, being able to launch powerfully searing, fire that is hotter than magma from its mouth. This fire consumes everything that it touches. When it roars, volcanos around it are apparently triggered to erupt. Due to being unable to fully control its own power, it constantly sprints around the world.
Entei is the main Pokémon in the movie Pokémon the Movie 3: Spell of the Unown, in which the Unown create it from Molly`s imagination.</description>
<picture>243122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4038" picture="25985.jpg">Takenaka Naoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1925" type="appears in" update="2011-03-03">
<rating votes="43">7.00</rating>
<name>Rocket-dan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Team Rocket is a highly organized criminal syndicate "in pursuit of evil" headed by Giovanni (called "The Boss" by his underlings) and based in Kanto. Its main focus is in stealing or capturing, then selling, rare and/or strong Pokemon, but it also conducts cruel experimental research on Pokemon. According to the Generation II games, the Team Rocket Oath says: "Steal Pokemon for profit. Exploit Pokemon for profit. All Pokemon exist for the glory of Team Rocket." Team Rocket`s final goal is to take over the world using Pokemon.
In the anime, Team Rocket is based in Kanto, with many smaller branches reaching out in Kanto and Johto. Giovanni is the Gym Leader of Viridian City during the early part of Ash`s journey. There is also an underground school for training aspiring Team Rocket members. In addition, Team Rocket had its headquarters near Pallet Town and Viridian City, but this was destroyed by Mewtwo in its rage; it is unknown where the headquarters are now. All that is known is that the headquarters are now in a large building built at the end of a canyon and guarded by many grunts, seen when Jessie, James, and Meowth returned from the Hoenn region to report back to Giovanni.</description>
<picture>25950.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1937" type="main character in" update="2011-03-03">
<rating votes="479">5.97</rating>
<name>Musashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jessie is one half of of the Team Rocket duo that follows around Ash Ketchum and friends in the Pokemon anime, usually trying to steal Ash`s Pikachu, but always failing.
Jessie`s mother, Miyamoto, was a high-ranking Team Rocket agent. When Jessie was around the age of three, Miyamoto left on a mission to the Andes Mountains to record the voice of the elusive Pokemon Mew. However, Miyamoto disappeared, and Jessie was put into a foster home which had very little money. There were times when she had no choice but to eat snow because of a lack of more nourishing food.
When she was old enough, she left home to become a Pokemon nurse in Jouto. However, the school she was enrolled in was literally for Pokemon nurses (i.e. Chansey), so she failed to graduate and left, leaving behind a Chansey she had befriended there. It is assumed that she then traveled back to Kanto, where she enrolled in Pokemon Tech, a trainer`s school, met James, and subsequently failed and dropped out. After this, Jessie and James joined a bicycle gang in Sunny Town, where Jessie was known for swinging a chain above her head as she rode her bike (nicknamed "Chainer Jess").
Due to conflicts in canon between Kanto and Johto episodes and the special episode "Training Daze", what happened between Jessie and James after the bike gang is unknown. What is known, as shown in the special episode, is that they joined Team Rocket separately and were on initially unfriendly terms after being grouped with Meowth. However, they quickly made up and the rest is history.
Sometime before joining Team Rocket, and it is not known when, Jessie obtained a Contest Pass in the Hoenn region. Also during the years before Team Rocket, she had several boyfriends, all of whom left her and/or treated her badly. In "Xatu the Future", she revealed that she had once worked at a T.V. station as the Weathergirl. In "From Cradle to Save" is also revealed that she once was a ninja.
She has a long-standing bitter rivalry with Cassidy, another member of Team Rocket. Another member, Wendy, held a grudge against Jessie for failing to pay for a drink (making Wendy pay), but got her revenge when she added the charge to Jessie`s overall Team Rocket bill.
In the episode "Ignorance is Blissey", Jessie was reunited with her friend Chansey from the Pokemon nurse school; Chansey had since evolved into a Blissey.
Starting in Hoenn, Jessie has become a Pokemon Coordinator, entering every contest that she could. She frequently makes it to the battle round, but usually loses there. However, in "Borrowing on Bad Faith", she finally succeeded in winning an (unofficial) contest by using Ash`s Aipom, which she had saved earlier in the episode. And, in "Team Shocker!", she finally wins an official contest with her Dustox in at Solaceon City. Later she also won a ribbon with help of her Yanmega. She has Contest Passes to compete in the Hoenn, Kanto, and Sinnoh regions.
While Jessie`s role in the Pokemon anime has not yet ended, in Toshihiro Ono`s manga, "The Electric Tale of Pikachu", she ended up married to James and with child.
Jessie seems to have a special preference for snake-like Pokemon, owning both an Arbok and a Seviper. In "The Ninja Poke Showdown", she expressed a preference for Poison-type Pokemon in general.
For unknown reasons, she, James and Meowth mostly use hot air balloons instead of faster ways of transportation.
In the Kanto contests, Jessie disguises herself as Jessebella (which is similar to James former fiancee Jessiebelle) wearing a red dress and glasses. Eventually, Ash, Brock, Max and May finds out her true identity at the last contest.
During the Kanto Grand Festival, Jessie dresses up as Jessadia (Japanese: キャンディ・ムサリーナ Candy Musalina). and wears glasses, long white socks, a yellow and orange dress, and has her hair in pigtails. She works there as an announcer and Lilian Meridian`s assistant; Lilian herself says she may not really like "Jessadia"`s style, but recognizes her talent. In the Latin American dub, she enters Super Contests under the name Jessiebella (referencing Jessiebelle again). Jessie currently still continues to use the Jessalina disguise while participating in Super Contests.
In "Pruning a Passel of Pals!" and "Strategy With a Smile!" she once again used her Jessadia disguise to report on the Wallace Cup.
Although Jessie had entered mostly every contest in Hoenn &amp; Kanto, she lost in every single one, whether it was the first match of the Battle Rounds or the finals. But in the Sinnoh Region, she has so far won 2 ribbons using her Dustox and Yanmega.</description>
<picture>2338.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1938" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="420">5.46</rating>
<name>Nyarth (Rocket-dan)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meowth is a very unique Pokémon as it has many of the characteristics of a human. It walks on two feet, talks and is as smart as any human. Meowth is currently a member of Team Rocket and he travels around with Jessie and James trying to capture Pikachu and other rare Pokémon for Giovanni.
Meowth generally finishes his sentences with "Nyaa (ニャー)" which is the equivalent of "meow" in English. This helps people remember that despite his ability to talk like a human, he still has cat character traits.
Meowth is also known for coming up with his many schemes to try to capture Pikachu. While Jessie and James always agree with Meowth and think his plans are brilliant, they are generally foiled by Ash and his friends.
Long Con to Access Raimon City Pokémon Center
Meowth schemed with Jessie, James and Doctor Zager to figure out a way for them to infiltrate the Raimon City Pokémon Center where high-leveled Pokémon are stored in a vault that is protected by a security machine scan system that would only open if Nurse Joy (Isshu) or Nurse Joy`s Audino were scanned. Meowth pretended to be no longer part of Team Rocket making up a story that his made an error while executing a certain operation and when headquarters hear of his mistake, they told him he was fired.
Ash, Iris and Cilan believed him and allowed Meowth to travel with him. Pikachu though didn`t trust Meowth even though Meowth proved on numerous occasion that it should be trusted. Meowth`s plan was put into action when they arrived at the Raimon City Pokémon Center and as soon as Nurse Joy`s Audino was scanned to open the door, Meowth turned on Pikachu and the other and captured all the Pokémon in the vault. The long con had been a success and Meowth met up with Jessie and James below the Pokémon Center. Unfortunately, they weren`t able to get away as Ash and his friends realized that Meowth had just been conning them and they were able to stop Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>56344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6900" picture="34079.jpg">Inuyama Inuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2611" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="370">7.66</rating>
<name>Kojirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>James is one part of of the Team Rocket trio that follows around Ash Ketchum and friends in the Pokémon anime, usually trying to steal Ash`s Pikachu, but always failing.
James is mostly a comedic parody of bishounen characters; the English dub in particular tends to give him a melodramatic and even campy tone. He is somewhat famous for carrying a rose, though in more recent episodes he does not display it often. Mostly, his rose is displayed in the Team Rocket motto.
The only child of millionaires, James was forced to endure formal society. At a young age, he was forcefully engaged to a girl of whom he was terrified, Jessiebelle, all because his parents wanted to have a wealthy daughter-in-law. Thus, he ran away from home, leaving behind his beloved pet Growlie. He attempted to enroll in Pokémon Tech, a trainer`s school, but, along with his new friend Jessie, flunked out. Then, with Jessie, he joined the Sunny Town bicycle gang, where he was popular for being the only gang member to have to use training wheels (nicknamed "Trainer Jim"). Eventually James, Jessie, and the bike gang went their separate ways.
Due to conflicts in canon between Kanto and Johto episodes and the special episode "Training Daze", what happened between James and Jessie after the bike gang is unknown. What is known, as shown in the special episode, is that they joined Team Rocket separately and were on initially unfriendly terms after being grouped with Meowth. However, they quickly made up and the rest is history.
Since he is proficient in several activities, including Pokémon haiku and PokéRinger, it is possible that he developed his skills during his temporary separation from Jessie, but this is not known for sure.
In the episode "Holy Matrimony!", James returned to his home as a result of a trap by his parents, who pretended to be dead. He was reunited with his old pet Growlie and managed to avoid marrying Jessiebelle. Growlie stayed behind when James returned to Jessie and Meowth.
James has a tendency to be swindled by a Magikarp Salesman, who has on many occasions tricked him into buying a Magikarp or other useless Pokémon and items for large sums of money.
James also has a tendency to cross-dress, but has not done it since "Pros and Con Artists". He does, however, dress up like famous celebrities as well, such as Professor Oak, Juan, and Norman.
James loves rare bottle caps and has an impressive collection of them. In the episode "All That Glitters!" it is revealed that he has "drunk enough soda pop to float an aircraft carrier".
For unknown reasons, he, Jessie and Meowth mostly use hot air balloons instead of faster ways of transportation. However in newer episodes the balloon is shown with `jets` attached to explain how they get from one place to another faster than walking.</description>
<picture>2423.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6693" type="main character in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="911">2.49</rating>
<name>Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
Ash is the main character of the Pokémon anime. Raised in Pallet Town, he started his journey to become a Pokémon Master at the age of 10. On the day that he started his journey, Ash carelessly woke up late despite being told by his mother, Delia Ketchum to get to bed. He rushed to Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory only to find out that the beginner Pokémon - Bulbasaur, Squirtle, and Charmander - had already been given out to trainers who arrived on time. However, Professor Samual Oak mentioned that there was one more Pokémon available - Pikachu. Despite constantly hitting Ash with Electric-type attacks and refusing to return to its PokéBall, Ash decided to take Pikachu along with him on his journey to become a Pokémon Master. Pikachu is cold towards Ash at first and laughs at his failures; however, when Ash saves Pikachu from a flock of wild Spearow, he begins to warm up to his new trainer and the two finally become friends. After the battle with the flock of Spearow, a Ho-Oh is seen flying towards a rainbow in the sky. The PokéDex reveals that the Ho-Oh is an unidentified Pokémon. Thus, the journey of Ash and Pikachu begins.
Captures in Viridian Forest
While making his way towards Pewter City and his first Kanto League Gym Battle, Ash came upon a wild Caterpie deep within Viridian Forest. Instead of using Pikachu to battle against the wild Pokémon, Ash took his chances and threw a PokéBall without weakining the Caterpie first. Luckily, he was able to catch the Pokémon without any trouble. The capture of Ash`s Caterpie marked Ash`s first capture as a Pokémon Trainer, making Ash`s Caterpie the second Pokémon to join his team.
The next day, while continuing the trek through the Viridian Forest, Ash came up on a wild Pidgeotto. He tried to just throw a PokéBall like he did with Ash`s Caterpie, but Pidgeotto swatted the PokéBall away. Misty informed that he must weaken the Pokémon first before attempting to capture it. He called out Ash`s Caterpie to battle against, but Misty quickly informed him that Bug-type Pokémon are weak against Flying-type Pokémon like Pidgeotto. After Pidgeotto dealt significant damage to Ash`s Caterpie, Ash recalled it and sent out Pikachu. Pikachu was able to use its Thundershock to weaken Pidgeotto and allow Ash to capture it with a PokéBall. Thus, this capture marked Ash`s second capture as a Pokémon Trainer, making Ash`s Pidgeotto the third Pokémon to join his team.
Later on, while still in the Viridian Forest, Ash was approached by Team Rocket, who attempted to steal his Pokémon. After defeating Meowth, James`s Koffing, and Jessie`s Ekans, Ash`s Caterpie evolved into Ash`s Metapod.
Some of Ash`s greatest accomplishments have been at the various Pokémon Leagues. He was the victor at the Orange League and the Battle Frontier. He also competed in the Indigo League and the Johto Silver Conference where he placed admirably in both those competitions as well.
Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup
Ash participated in the Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup at the Kagome Town stadium. In the first round he was in the fifth match and faced off against Marris. The match was quickly showcased and Ash won the battle and advanced to the second round while Marris was eliminated from the tournament.
The Isshu League
Ash participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where he was matched up against Trip. Trip`s Serperior was sent out to battle Pikachu and Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior`s speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter Trip`s Serperior speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round. The two met in the Pokémon Center after the battle, and Trip vowed that the next time they met that he would win. The two shook hands and parted ways.
In the first main round, Ash`s opponent was shown on the match up electronic board but not much else is known about the battle. Ash`s Scraggy participated in the second main round of the Isshu League tournament where it faced off against a Darumakka. It was able to defeat it so that moved on to the next round.
In the third round, Stephan was matched up against Ash. Cilan noted that the two of them have a very direct taste and that it would be a good battle. It was only a 3 on 3 battle but the both of them gave it their all. The first two battles of the third round setup the final match up of Stephan`s Sawk vs Ash`s Krookodile, both of which were very injured from the previous battles. Both of them did their best to muster up their reserve strength but in the end a surprise move of Aerial Ace by Ash`s Krookodile was super effective against Stephan`s Sawk and it knocked it out to give Ash the victory while eliminating Stephan from the tournament. Stephan realized after the battle that the reason that Ash withdrew Waruvial after the first battle was because Ash knew that Stephan would definitely send out Dageki, so he didn`t reveal that it knew Aerial Ace and saved until the end.</description>
<picture>6210.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8091" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-30">
<rating votes="989">3.91</rating>
<name>Pikachu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
On the morning that Ash was to start his Pokémon journey, he woke up late and by the time he reached Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory, all of the beginner Pokémon were already taken. However, Professor Samual Oak did have one Pokémon left, a wild Pikachu. At first, Pikachu did not like Ash and would refuse to enter his PokéBall. He would often laugh at Ash`s failures and refused to listen to him. However, after Ash proved his loyalty to Pikachu by protecting him from a flock of Spearow, and thus began to earn Pikachu`s trust and respect. The two have since become best friends and Pikachu never leaves Ash`s side.
Since the day Team Rocket first encountered Pikachu, it has been their sole goal to capture it. Day after day, their plan to capture Pikachu has been thwarted mainly due to Pikachu`s amazingly powerful Thunderbolt that keeps on blasting them off.
On numerous occasions, Pikachu has made it evident that he is happy being a Pikachu and has no desire to evolve into a more powerful Raichu. It has proven time and time again that it is a powerful and worthy opponent to any Pokémon that dares to battle it.
Gym Battle against Burgh`s Leavanny
Pikachu was then sent out to battle Burgh`s Leavanny. Burgh`s Leavanny managed to tie up Pikachu with String Shot but unlike Ash`s Swadloon who was able to break free, Pikachu ended up getting hit with a couple of Leaf Storm attacks and a Hyper Beam before it rolled into another of Burgh`s Leavanny`s Leaf Storm attacks to break the string off its body so it could attack. Freed from the String Shot, Burgh`s Leavanny tried to tie it up again but Pikachu managed to avoid it with its speed and then knocked Burgh`s Leavanny out with a combination of Iron Tail and Electro Ball.
Gym Battle against Elesa
Elesa`s Emolga knocked out Ash`s Snivy and was then matched up with Pikachu. Pikachu made quick work of Elesa`s Emolga and knocked it out with one attack, its Iron Tail.
Elesa`s Tynamo was the last Pokémon that she used in her gym battle against Ash. It was matched up against Pikachu who had just defeated her Emonga. Pikachu had a hard time defending against the fast Tackle attack that Elesa`s Tynamo kept hitting it with but Pikachu used its Thunderbolt to create a large dust cloud leaving only a small corridor for Pikachu to focus on it and so Elesa`s Tynamo couldn`t maneuver out of the way. Pikachu one hit K.O`d Elesa`s Tynamo with a Iron Tail. The loss gave Ash the overall victory.
Battle against Alder`s Bouffalant
Ash challenged Alder to a battle and he accepted though he had been walking all night and was actually quite tired. Alder sent out his Buffron to battle Pikachu but just as the battle started, Alder fell asleep standing up and didn`t give any orders to his Buffron. Alder`s Bouffalant stood still as Pikachu began hitting it with attack after attack until it Alder`s Bouffalant finally got mad at Alder and charged at him and set him flying into a tree. After that, Alder`s Bouffalant no longer wished to battle and Alder conceded the battle.
Gym Battle against Skyla
In Skyla air battle simulation, Ash`s Tranquill was matched up against Skyla`s Unfezant and since her Pokémon was the highest evolved form, she determined that her Pokémon would be the winner in that match-up. In the actual gym battle, Ash`s Tranquill was up against Skyla`s Unfezant which was the match-up just after Ash`s Tranquill had defeated Skyla`s Swoobat. Skyla`s Unfezant proved to be stronger and faster than Ash`s Tranquill, so Ash recalled it and set out Pikachu. Pikachu had a definite advantage over Skyla`s Unfezant with its electric attacks and it quickly knocked it out with its Electro Ball attack.
Ash Just after Pikachu ended up knocking out Skyla`s Unfezant, Skyla`s Swanna was sent out to battle against it. Skyla had been watching her grandpa`s battle videos and noticed that he used the move Aqua Ring to defend against Electric attacks. She used that same defense against Pikachu which nullified its Electric attacks. It`s Iron Tail also couldn`t hit it so high in the air. Ash then noticed the rings in the air and Pikachu jumped up on them and managed to hit Skyla`s Swanna but not directly. Pikachu was now up in the air though and Skyla`s Swanna had the advantage there and it quickly knocked Pikachu out with a powerful Brave Bird attack.
Battle Against Trip`s Serperior at the Isshu League
Pikachu participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where it is was matched up against Trip`s Serperior. Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter its speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round.</description>
<picture>88041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8135" type="appears in" update="2011-01-12">
<rating votes="73">8.01</rating>
<name>Sonans (Musashi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While Wobbuffet is technically Jessie`s Pokémon, it has been around so long that it has become a main character, appearing in almost every episode of the series since it debut.
Wobbuffet was first seen walking around with Benny, his previous trainer. Jessie traded her Lickitung for Wobbuffet and it has been with her ever since that day.
Wobbuffet rarely battles but when he does, his Counter and Mirror Coat moves have proved to be very effective. Unfortunately, Jessie`s tactics aren`t always sufficient to master Wobbuffet`s superior defensive skills.
Wobbuffet also randomly comes out of his Pokeball, especially during the Team Rocket motto. He is also seen blasting off with Jessie regardless if he was actually part of the action.</description>
<picture>56350.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12558" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="50">5.85</rating>
<name>Ookido Yukinari-hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a Pokémon researcher that was once a competitive Trainer, and is generally considered the best in his field. As such, his role in the Pokémon games and anime is that of a mentor to young Pokémon Trainers, a source of information and an occasional plot device. Amongst other things, he is credited with inventing the Pokédex. He also hands out a Bulbasaur, Squirtle, or Charmander to beginning trainers (depending on which Pokémon the trainer chooses) to start their adventure in the Kanto Region. Although he is an expert on all matters relating to Pokémon, Professor Oak specializes in Pokémon behavioural science. He appears in Pokémon 4Ever as a child who was pulled into the future by Celebi. Additionally, it is apparent after Pokémon 3: The Movie that he knew Delia Ketchum since she was a child; this most likely is the reason he occasionally exhibits parental-type concern (mainly in the form of scolding Ash as he is doing something that is dangerous). He also creates poems centred around Pokémon and is known as the rhyming professor by Dawn.</description>
<picture>37802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16389" type="main character in" update="2018-10-29">
<rating votes="377">7.39</rating>
<name>Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misty is the Gym Leader of Cerulean City Gym. Ash first met her when she pulled him out of the lake while fishing. He took her bike and head off towards the nearest Pokemon Center to help Pikachu. Pikachu later fried her bike and she got mad and wanted Ash to replace it.
Misty has always had a bit of a crush on Ash and it was one of the reasons she decided to travel with him. After traveling with Ash through Kanto, the Orange Islands and the Johto regions, Misty returned to her position as the Cerulean City Gym Leader while her sisters went on a trip around the world.
Misty is a devote Water Pokémon trainer and she specializes in Water-type Pokémon. On the other hand, Misty completely despises Bug-type Pokémon and avoids them whenever possible.</description>
<picture>56342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2138" picture="21613.jpg">Iizuka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16390" type="main character in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="288">5.09</rating>
<name>Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brock was the Gym Leader of the Pewter Gym but during his travels abroad, his family has taken over the gym in his absence. Brock goal is to become a Pokémon Breeder and learn as much about Pokémon as he possibly can.
Brock was impressed with Ash during their first encounter when Ash challenged him to a Gym Battle. Brock decided to journey with Ash and together they have explored many regions.
Brock is also known for his obsession with girls. Almost every girl Brock sees, he immediately falls in love with. Misty, Max and most recently his Pokémon Croagunk have always been there to keep him in check before scaring off the girls with his overbearing introductions. He is also an expert on Nurse Joy and Officer Jenny as he recognizes all the differences in their personalities and features where as other people cannot tell the difference.</description>
<picture>56341.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16470" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="53">5.52</rating>
<name>Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tracey is a Pokémon Watcher that traveled with Ash during the Orange Islands. He is currently staying and studying with Professor Oak in Pallet Town. He also takes care of Ash`s Pokémon that are residing at the Professors laboratory.
Tracey is a very good artist and enjoys drawing. His artistic skills have been a benefit to him as a Pokémon Watcher as he is able to quickly sketch a scene with great detail.
While journeying with Ash and Misty, Tracey replaced Brock in their group as Brock stayed with Professor Ivy for awhile. Tracey proved that he was quite knowledgeable about the many various aspects of Pokémon which greatly benefited Ash and Misty.</description>
<picture>56346.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22303" type="main character in" update="2010-10-12">
<rating votes="52">5.13</rating>
<name>Hanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Delia is the mother of Ash Ketchum and she resides in Pallet town with a Mr. Mime she befriended.</description>
<picture>56458.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4962" picture="60945.jpg">Toyoshima Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22368" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="10">9.08</rating>
<name>Lizardon (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Charizard evolves from Charmeleon during a battle with Aerodactyl but still remains disobient to Ash.
Kanto Pokémon League:
Fifth Round - Vs Ritchie.
Ash gambled on using a disobient Charizard and he was trailing in the battle and his other Pokémon were tired.
Charizard originally appeared like it was not going to do anything but after Ritchie`s Charmander narrowly missed with a flamethrower, Charizard decided to fight back with a flamethrower of its own with panicked Charmander and forced Ritchie to recall it.
Pikachu was Ritchie`s third and final Pokémon in the battle and was against Ash`s Charizard which had just forced Charmander to be switched. Charizard trembled the ground with a couple of stomps making Pikachu lose its balance and then blew Pikachu away using a gust from its wings. Seemingly thinking Pikachu was not a worthy opponent, Charizard took a nap in the middle of a battle and despite Ash pleaded with it to battle, it was eliminated. This gave Sparky the victory over Charizard and put Ritchie into round six.
Ash angrily recalled Charizard into its ball.
Orange Islands.
Ash called upon Charizard to battle Tad`s Poliwrath which had a reputation of being a very strong Pokémon. Charizard refused to listen to Ash`s orders and Poliwrath shoots a water gun on Charizards tail making the flame much smaller, then a subsuquent Ice Beam hits Charizard and freezes it. The battle left Charizard very injured and Ash had to keep its tail flame alive much like he did when he first found it as a Charmander.
Despite an intial struggle, Charizard saw how much Ash cared for him and once it reached full health in the morning Charizard became friendly with Ash and even obeyed Ash during Battle.
Charizard then went on to defeat Tad`s Poliwrath in a re-match.
Orange League Final - Vs. Ash Ketchum (Sand Field)
Ash chose Charizard to battle against Electabuzz and ordered it to use Flamethrower against Electabuzz, who quickly jumped into the air and landed a Thunderpunch onto Charizard and follwowed up by shocking Charizard with an electric attack. Charizard managed to release himself from the electricity by firing a Fire Spin and then Charizard flew towards Electabuzz quickly making sure it could not use it Thunderbolt attack. Charizard got a good grip on Electabuzz and flew into the air and used Seismic Toss on it which eliminated it and left Drake with one Pokémon left.
Drake`s final Pokémon was his prized Dragonite who he sent out to battle Ash`s Charizard.
Charizard moved first by using a Flamethrower attack but Dragonite countered by using Water Gun which cuts through the Flamethrower and hits Charizard, who then takes to the skies whilst avoiding Dragonite`s Ice Beam.
Dragonite then takes to the sky itself showing great speed as it does so. Dragonite and Charizard exchange Ice Beam and Flamethrower attacks respectively but it is Dragonite who manages to clip Charizard wing using Ice Beam which send Charizard spinning to the ground. Charizard recovers and flies close to Dragonite in an attempt to use a Seismic Toss attack, however, Dragonite avoids and gets a good grip on Charizard which gives it the opportunity to use a Slam attack.
Charizard gets up quick although it is clearly tired but it has enough stength to launch a Dragon Rage attack. Dragonite uses the same move, the attacks collide and both Pokémon are sent flying backwards. When the dust settles both Pokémon are standing but exhausted from the previous battle, after a few deep breaths Charizard falls to the ground and is eliminated.
After Ash had won the battle against Drake he called out all of his Pokémon that participated in the battle on the stage as Drake presented him with the Winner`s Trophy. Then Ash, Pikachu, Tauros, Lapras, Squirtle, Bulbasaur and Charizard all had their handprints set in stone to be remembered in the Orange Island Hall of Fame.</description>
<picture>56582.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="10194" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2000-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40608" update="2005-08-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40609" update="2005-08-24">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="66519" update="2010-03-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Pokérap Gold &amp; Silver</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84299" update="2007-10-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84318" update="2007-10-13">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87905" update="2008-02-02">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="88481" update="2008-03-02">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92395" update="2008-08-08">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French trailer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Publicité Québecoise du 3e Film</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92396" update="2008-08-08">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">US trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92468" update="2008-08-12">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121350" update="2010-10-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2000-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121351" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2000-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
