<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9950" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-03-15</startdate>
<enddate>2014-03-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Sekaiichi Hatsukoi: Yokozawa Takafumi no Baai</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 世界一初恋 横澤隆史の場合</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8567" type="Prequel">Sekaiichi Hatsukoi 2</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10049" approval="2" total="3">Hybrid Child</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="371670">A very good adaptation of the first instalment of Yokozawa Takafumi no Baai series. Note that the original material is not manga but a novel. ;)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://sekai-ichi-movie.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="19268" type="Character Design">Yasuda Takahiro</name>
<name id="1752" type="Character Design">Kikuchi Youko</name>
<name id="10226" type="Original Work">Nakamura Shungiku</name>
<name id="1482" type="Direction">Kon Chiaki</name>
<name id="19268" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yasuda Takahiro</name>
<name id="9943" type="Music">Anze Hijiri</name>
<name id="44904" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamaguchi Jinshichi</name>
</creators>
<description>The movie follows up on the last episode of http://anidb.net/a8567 [Sekaiichi Hatsukoi 2], after http://anidb.net/ch29555 [Yokozawa Takafumi]`s heart gets broken by his longtime friend and first love http://anidb.net/ch29558 [Takano Masamune]. Now, trying to get over him, he goes out drinking and starts to bond with Japun`s editor-in-chief http://anidb.net/ch63060 [Kirishima Zen] and his daughter http://anidb.net/ch63061 [Hiyori].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="183">6.68</permanent>
<temporary count="186">7.12</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>147662.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14912</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>22404</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20815</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20371</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://sekai-ichi-movie.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>世界一初恋&amp;redirect=no#.E5.8A.87.E5.A0.B4.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347173</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17071</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17072</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29551" type="appears in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="24">3.75</rating>
<name>Yoshino Chiaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60774.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29552" type="appears in" update="2011-03-27">
<rating votes="39">6.57</rating>
<name>Onodera Ritsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29553" type="appears in" update="2011-07-13">
<rating votes="24">6.52</rating>
<name>Kisa Shouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29555" type="main character in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="16">5.99</rating>
<name>Yokozawa Takafumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29557" type="appears in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="27">5.72</rating>
<name>Hatori Yoshiyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29558" type="appears in" update="2014-11-16">
<rating votes="50">8.50</rating>
<name>Takano Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34075" type="appears in" update="2014-12-13">
<rating votes="16">5.12</rating>
<name>Yukina Kou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He works in a bookstore and is taking charge of the Shoujo section there. He`s really good with his (female) customers and practically makes them buy new manga with his really good looks.
"I thought you could buy this so next time you come in we can bond over how good this manga is."</description>
<picture>74512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63060" type="main character in" update="2015-01-27">
<rating votes="4">7.75</rating>
<name>Kirishima Zen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The editor-in-chief of Japun.</description>
<picture>168043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32833" picture="17354.jpg">Sougetsu Noboru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63061" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-27">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>Kirishima Hiyori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The surprise daughter of Kirishima Zen.</description>
<picture>168044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="156876" update="2015-01-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2014-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159525" update="2015-01-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2014-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界一初恋 バレンタイン編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sekaiichi Hatsukoi Valentine Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekaiichi Hatsukoi Valentine Hen</title>
<summary>This short depicts the stories of the couples from the Hatsukoi universe on Valentine`s day.
The first part shows Yokozawa Takafumi and Kirishima Hiyori, the second Yoshino Chiaki and Hatori Yoshiyuki, the third Kisa Shouta and Yukina Kou, concluded by Onodera Ritsu and Takano Masamune`.</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
