<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="996" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1984-07-07</startdate>
<enddate>1984-07-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Choujikuu Yousai Macross: Ai Oboete Imasuka</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Super Dimension Fortress Macross Do You Remember Love</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Clash of the Bionoids</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">macross movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">초시공요새 마크로스: 사랑, 기억하고 있나요</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Macross: Alguém se Lembra do Amor?</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Fortaleza Superdimensonal Macross: Você se Lembra do Amor?</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Macross DYRL</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">超時空要塞マクロス 愛・おぼえていますか</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Macross - Do You Remember Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Macross - The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Macross, te rappelles-tu de l`amour ?</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Macross: A Batalha Final</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Macross: Maailman isoin taistelukone</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Macross: Az Űrcsatahajó</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Macross: ¿Recuerdas el Amor?</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="501" type="Sequel">Choujikuu Yousai Macross II: Lovers Again</anime>
<anime id="77" type="Alternative Setting">Choujikuu Yousai Macross</anime>
<anime id="2324" type="Other">Choujikuu Yousai Macross: Flash Back 2012</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="678374">Yes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="616461">Hikaru redefines himself from the kinda wimpy guy in SDFM to one of the greatest badasses in mech anime history! Oh, and Minmay gets bitchslapped. Watch this if you already saw SDFM.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tatsunoko.co.jp/works/archive/movie_macross.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="830" type="Work">Tatsunoko Production</name>
<name id="997" type="Work">Mainichi Housou</name>
<name id="1082" type="Work">Shogakukan</name>
<name id="512" type="Character Design">Mikimoto Haruhiko</name>
<name id="152" type="Story Composition">Kawamori Shouji</name>
<name id="1126" type="Original Work">Studio Nue</name>
<name id="151" type="Direction">Ishiguro Noboru</name>
<name id="152" type="Direction">Kawamori Shouji</name>
<name id="3469" type="Music">Haneda Kentarou</name>
<name id="1059" type="Work">Big West</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru] is a Valkyrie pilot aboard the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross], which is in the middle of a cosmic war against a race of giant humanoid aliens, the Zentradi. During the battle, he comes across the pop star http://anidb.net/ch7418 [Lynn Minmay] whose singing might be the only hope against the Zentradi`s culture. But can she sing when Hikaru, her love is caught between the pop star and Lieutenant http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Hayase Misa].
Note: Filled with aerial combat choreography and emotional drama, the release of Macross: DYRL was a major event in Japan. Also known as Robotech in the US, or as Clash of the Bionoids — an English version of the movie that was cut down to 90 minutes.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1527">7.57</permanent>
<temporary count="1533">7.66</temporary>
<review count="4">7.08</review>
</ratings>
<picture>84415.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1089</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1542</identifier>
<identifier>dytqni</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tatsunoko.co.jp/works/macross-the-movie</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Macross:_Do_You_Remember_Love?</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>超時空要塞マクロス_愛・おぼえていますか</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>762</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>90090</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2633" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>prison</name>
<description>A building used to house convicted criminals and accused persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3138" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-08">
<name>fictional language</name>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3167" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-16">
<name>Tokyo destroyed</name>
<description>Tokyo is depicted as being or having been destroyed, either partially or completely, by some sort of disaster, such as a nuclear blast, a very large-scale fire, or rising sea levels. Should the situation be dire enough, Tokyo may be destroyed again after a recovery, or a new Tokyo may be built and subsequently destroyed, by a new disaster.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3277" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-28">
<name>bendy lasers</name>
<description>Lasers — of all things — bend at strange angles, are profusely in effect in this anime. Usually seen in a space setting, as part of a weapon system on spaceships.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3874" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>bridge bunnies</name>
<description>A term and English nickname describing the attractive girls who manage the various functions aboard a ship`s/starship`s bridge area. 
Although it originated in reference to characters from Macross, it does not exist among Japanese fans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4237" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-01-22">
<name>organic spaceship</name>
<description>The primary design of the spaceships in this anime seem to be organic in nature. This is quite rare in sci-fi, and hints at certain regenerative properties of these ships, i.e. damage can automatically be repaired. Or that the ships need not be "built", but can be "grown". It might even imply a consciousness on the part of the spaceship.
Typically spaceships are made of "dead" inorganic materials, though.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4342" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-06">
<name>large-scale war</name>
<description>When the whole world, or, at least, a big part of it, partakes in the hell that is war.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4404" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-28">
<name>real robot</name>
<description>A smaller form of mecha with no special abilities. They are mostly used by deploying them in battle just like modern tanks. They can be mass produced and their pilots (usually military officers or soldiers) are (mostly) interchangeable. Tanks are often a threat to them and they are more easily destroyed than their bigger counterparts.</description>
<picurl>42787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4446" parentid="2639" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-12">
<name>faster-than-light travel</name>
<description>Faster-than-light travel is taken for grated in this anime. This is achieved by travelling via hyperspace, nullspace, or wormholes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5767" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-16">
<name>Itano circus</name>
<description>The Itano circus is named after Itano Ichirou, a Japanese animator, and refers to a highly stylized and acrobatic method of depicting aerial combat and dogfights in many anime, particularly the Macross series, where it was utilised by Itano for the first time and was ground-breaking.
The Itano circus is characterized by detailed, fluid shading of the mecha, the close-range acrobatic moves the duelling fighters make in combat, as well as twisting contrails left by fighters and missiles. It is also commonly used in specific reference to an attack where a mecha or spaceship launches a large swarm of missiles with meticulously animated spiralling smoke trails and erratic trajectories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7418" type="main character in" update="2012-09-14">
<rating votes="116">4.58</rating>
<name>Lynn Minmay</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born in Yokohama Chinatown, Japan (though she is of partial Chinese descent) as Linn Minmei, Minmay moved in with her uncle http://anidb.net/ch21740 [Shaochin] and aunt http://anidb.net/ch21741 [Feichun] on South Ataria Island in hopes of finding the path to fulfill her dream of becoming a star. On the day of the Zentradi invasion, she meets http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] and a series of events leads to her being swept off on the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] along with the rest of the surviving population from that island. While on the space fortress, Minmay wins the Miss Macross beauty pageant and is propelled into celebrity.When the Macross returns to Earth, she is the only civilian allowed off the space fortress. After her trip home in Japan (where her parents remained), Minmay returned to the fortress with her cousin http://anidb.net/ch10513 [Lynn Kaifun] (and http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru]`s competition for her affection) in tow. Her beauty and singing talent also win over several Zentradi spies sent to explore human society, who spread their impressions among their fleetmates, thus unwittingly evoking peace-oriented attitudes among the alien aggressors. Ultimately, Minmay sings the songs that end the first war against the Zentradi.
During the second part of the series, the very fame and success she craved finally left her tired and virtually alone. She tries to run away from her celebrity status and start anew, with a more simple life alongside http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru], who is now more confused than ever in defining his feelings for Minmay and http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Hayase Misa]; all of this while new conflicts arise between the human and Zentradi survivors of the first war. At the end of the series both http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] and Minmay realize they are very different people, and Minmay accepts that http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] belongs with http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Misa], remaining a friend to the couple afterwards.
In 2012, she embarks on the SDF-2 Megaroad-01 colony ship, which disappears 4 years later during its voyage towards the center of the Milky Way galaxy, becoming a legend in the Macross universe since then.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>43010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3995" picture="25878.jpg">Iijima Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7652" type="main character in" update="2019-05-09">
<rating votes="102">8.43</rating>
<name>Hayase Misa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hayase Misa is of Japanese ethnicity. She was born into a Japanese family with a hundred-year military lineage and was the only daughter of Admiral http://anidb.net/ch10525 [Hayase Takashi]. Misa also had aspired to enter the military since childhood. This dream was bolstered by a desire to join her boyfriend and first love, http://anidb.net/ch10524 [Riber Fruhling], in the UN Spacy. Misa`s hope is tragically unrealized as http://anidb.net/ch10524 [Riber] dies during the destruction of the return fleet from the Salla Mars Base where he was stationed, shortly after leaving Misa on Earth.
After graduating first in her class at the UN Spacy Officers` Academy, she earned a bridge post aboard the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross]. She and fellow SDF-1 bridge officer http://anidb.net/ch10509 [Claudia LaSalle] became close friends. As Misa herself admits, her mind is constantly preoccupied with duty. This changes, however, after she meets the young pilot http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru]. Their officer/subordinate status would slowly evolve through the series, from originally a difficult professional relationship (with http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] even calling her "old lady" when he first hears her over his Valkyrie`s onboard radio, which results in his senpai, http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker], getting a good laugh, much to Misa`s chagrin) to a friendly personal one; and much later to a romantic one, clashing with the already strong infatuation http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] has with http://anidb.net/ch7418 [Lynn Minmay]. She also has some short-lived feelings for http://anidb.net/ch7418 [Minmay]`s cousin http://anidb.net/ch10513 [Kaifun], who bears a striking physical resemblance to the deceased http://anidb.net/ch10524 [Riber].
Initially ranked as First Lieutenant, she is later promoted to Captain, and later to Major, concluding with her being chosen as the commander of the new SDF-2 Megaroad-01 ship and crew.
Despite having early disputes with http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru], she slowly begins to harbor feelings for him as they share some adventures during the war, discovering both have very much in common. In the final episode, http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] realizes he is in love with Misa, and after the climactic final battle, they marry and become members of the SDF-2 Megaroad-01 crew to leave on a stellar exploration mission in 2012. Shortly thereafter, Misa and http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] have a daughter, Ichijou Miku, in 2013.
After their ship disappears in 2016 without a trace near the center of the galaxy, they were reported as missing. The whereabouts of Misa and http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] and the ship`s crew (includinghttp://anidb.net/ch7418 [ Lynn Minmay], who remained as their friend and also joined the exploration mission) are still unknown.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>67458.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="542" picture="60897.jpg">Doi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7654" type="main character in" update="2012-09-14">
<rating votes="68">5.81</rating>
<name>Ichijou Hikaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hikaru Ichijyo is Japanese. Hikaru grew up with his father as a talented aerobatic flier, having won seven amateur flying contests by the age of 16 in 2009. When his "senpai" http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker] invited him to the launch ceremony of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] he found himself pulled into a galactic war against an alien race called the Zentradi. He later joins the UN Spacy after a talk with http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Focker] and http://anidb.net/ch7418 [Lynn Minmay]. Shortly after joining, he gains a reputation as a skilled pilot and leader, and he is promoted to second lieutenant and later first lieutenant. He pilots the http://anidb.net/ch48790 [VF-1S Valkyrie] "Skull One" after the death of http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Focker], and is eventually promoted to captain at the end of the series.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>2938.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12107" picture="40970.jpg">Hase Arihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10505" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-14">
<rating votes="33">8.56</rating>
<name>Roy Focker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roy Focker is an American who was born and lived in the United States in the late 20th century. During his college school days he had interest in prehistorical civilizations and archeology studies, and was in a relationship with his senior http://anidb.net/ch14115 [Aries Turner]. However, after being left by her, Roy dropped his studies and became a stunt pilot in the air circus led by http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru]`s father. Some time later he decided to join the U.N. Spacy after most of his friends died in the U.N. Wars. His flight instructor during this time was D.D. Ivanov.
During the war Roy became a talented and strong-willed fighter pilot, known for his love of women and alcohol. Focker was selected later as one of the first test pilots for the development of the variable fighters by the U.N. Forces. In 2008 he is deployed as a squadron commader with the Skull Team aboard the stealth carrier CVN-99 Asuka II on a secret mission in the South Pacific and flies the VF-0 Phoenix in battle against the SV-51s of the Anti-U.N. Forces. The work done on the VF-0 helps the coinciding development of the VF-1 Valkyrie.
Despite his long absence during the U.N. Wars and the death of http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru]`s father, http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] still remained a close friend to Roy and considered him his sempai (upperclassman/big brother figure). After the end of the U.N. Wars, Focker involved himself in the VF-X development project flying both the VF-X and the VF-X-1 (non-transformable and transformable flight test prototypes of the VF-1 Valkyrie), and his flight experience earned him the command of the VF-1 Skull Squadron aboard the super-large-scale semi-submersible attack aircraft carrier http://anidb.net/ch48774 [CVS-101 Prometheus].
During Space War I Roy Focker is still a smoking, drinking womanizer who constantly defies death and, when not on another desperate mission, enjoys life and its pleasures to the fullest. He has a relationship with http://anidb.net/ch10509 [Claudia LaSalle], an officer stationed on the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] bridge.Roy dies in episode 18 ("Pineapple Salad"), from wounds sustained while defending http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] from http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia Fallyna]`s force of Queadluun-Rau battle suits. Instead of going to the hospital to treat his wounds, he chooses to play the guitar while waiting for http://anidb.net/ch10509 [Claudia LaSalle] to finish her pineapple salad; while she`s cooking for him, he collapses from a sudden internal bleeding and passes away few minutes later. To http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru]`s chagrin given his then shaken self-confidence in his flying skill in war, he is promoted as the new leader of Roy`s squadron, using his mecha as well.
In http://anidb.net/a996 [The Super Dimension Fortress Macross: Do You Remember Love?] 1984 film adaptation of the original TV series, the character Roy Focker dies aboard an alien Zentradi ship while fighting http://anidb.net/ch10516 [Quamzin Kravshera]. In the movie Roy sacrifices himself to let both http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru] and http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Hayase Misa] escape.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>31541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10506" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-19">
<rating votes="24">7.66</rating>
<name>Maximilian Jenius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Max Jenius was born in Europe. He is a young fighter pilot, having joined http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru]`s Vermillion Team, along with http://anidb.net/ch10508 [Kakizaki Hayao], at the age of only 16. Jenius shows in his first sortie that he is a preternaturally talented ace pilot who is near invincible in combat, despite his need to wear corrective lenses on duty. Max is quickly recognized as the top pilot of the force, as marked by being granted to distinctively repaint his mecha into his preferred blue color.
Jenius` skill at piloting mecha becomes even more celebrated with feats that no other pilot would have thought of, much less achieved. One outstanding incident involves his infiltrating a Zentradi battleship in his valkyrie and disguising it with a Zentradi uniform, allowing him to escape detection.
Jenius is not above an occasional egotistical musing when he is off duty, but he also respects his comrades and they return the favor. He is also an incurable romantic in his youth which shows when he meets his future wife. That occurred when the top Zentradi ace pilot, http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia Fallyna], hears about a formidable pilot aboard the humans` http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] space fortress and seeks to challenge him personally in battle. Max manages to defeat http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia] not once, but thrice. The first in their respective mechas, the second in simulated combat (a video game) and finally in a knife fight to the death. It is this final fight where the two rivals fall in love. Immediately after the knife-fight in the park Max proposes to http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia] who accepts. Afterward, http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia] is allowed to join the mainline fighting forces of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] and becomes Max`s wingmate on duty, piloting a distinctive red Valkyrie alongside Max`s blue one.
After the Zentradi Fleet that nearly destroys the Earth is vanquished, Max and http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia] settle down in the new city built around the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] and begin a new life together. In March 2011, they give birth to a daughter (the first of seven) named Komilia Maria Fallyna Jenius. The name Komilia (which means "Little Milia") is chosen because with her green hair and green eyes, she looks so much like her mother (although it has also been suggested that the "ko" simply refers to the Japanese kanji character "child" that is often used on the end of Japanese female personal names - a suggestion which is supported by the title of episode 30: Viva Maria, as opposed to Viva Komilia). Komilia proves how related the Humans and Zentradi are. The "first stellar interracial child" is very unabashed baby, and proves resilient to http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia]`s sometimes rough and inexperienced handling. Max, despite his relatively young age, proves to be a happy and successful father, although he clearly has a strong dislike of Komilia`s playfulness with his hair. http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Hayase Misa] and http://anidb.net/ch10509 [Claudia La Salle] find Komilia adorable and are amazed that she isn`t shy at all, and envy Max and http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia] for having such a beautiful child.
Max and his family play a crucial role in the U.N.` capture of a factory satellite in November 2011. After blasting their way into the enemy command ship, Max and http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia] proudly display their child, cradled in http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia]`s arms and wearing a tiny pink and white spacesuit, to the hostile Zentradi. Max smiles as http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia] explains that Komilia "was created by the two of us...". The hostile Zentradi, who have had no exposure to human culture and have never seen a baby before, become terrified of Komilia and flee in fear, causing chaos aboard the command ship and disorder throughout the enemy fleet. This allows the earth forces and the allied Zentradi to seize the factory.
In the original Macross series, Max and http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia] have seven natural daughters and adopt a Zentradi girl over a period of twenty years from 2011 to 2031. The oldest is Komilia Maria Fallyna Jenius, who is the only one seen in the original series. The youngest is http://anidb.net/ch14046 [Mylene Flare Jenius], who becomes a major character in http://anidb.net/a442 [Macross 7]. http://anidb.net/ch41428 [Emilia Jenius] is seen briefly in http://anidb.net/a443 [Macross 7 the Movie: The Galaxy`s Calling Me!].----------
In http://anidb.net/a996 [The Super Dimension Fortress Macross: Do You Remember Love?], an animated film adaptation of the original series, Max and http://anidb.net/ch49062 [Milia] met in a completely different way. After the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] returns to Earth, the Meltrandi, under the command of Lap Lamiz, launched their own campaign against the Macross. The Meltrandi fleet sends in their highly trained http://anidb.net/ch49048 [Queadluun-Rau] power armor fighters, led by their ace pilot, http://anidb.net/ch49062 [Milia Fallyna], to retrieve a Protoculture tablet containing an ancient song they believed could help them defeat their Zentradi enemies. In the ensuing battle with the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] and subsequent death of http://anidb.net/ch10508 [Kakizaki Hayao], Max and http://anidb.net/ch49062 [Milia] fight against each other. In the last phase of the battle, Max and http://anidb.net/ch49062 [Milia] enter the Lap Lamiz`s ship and there, Max manages to down his opponent. Upon breaching the armor, Max is enamored by http://anidb.net/ch49062 [Milia] as she is with him, and expresses his awe at the Meltran pilot.
In the final battle between http://anidb.net/ch49057 [Boddole Zer] and the Macross fleet, a macronized Max is seen with http://anidb.net/ch49062 [Milia] battling together in their respective specialized blue and red http://anidb.net/ch49048 [Queadluun-Raus]. This scene is one of the few scenes showing Max without his glasses.
Another difference in the movie is that after http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker]`s death, Max is promoted to leader of the Skull Squadron, thus having Hikaru Ichijyo and http://anidb.net/ch10508 [Kakizaki Hayao] briefly as his subordinates.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>31503.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10507" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-15">
<rating votes="13">7.90</rating>
<name>Bruno J. Global</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bruno J. Global is of Italian ethnicity. Before commanding the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross], Global`s commanding officer during the U.N. Wars was http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Hayase Misa]`s father. He was the captain of the U.N. Navy submarine Marco Polo and the UN Spacy Oberth class space destroyer Goddard, which engaged and destroyed her hijacked sister ship Tsiolkovsky in the first ever use of reaction weaponry in real ship-vs-ship space combat during the U.N. Wars. Bruno J. Global rose through the ranks of the United Nations Forces thanks to his exploits during the Unification Wars until he was assigned as Captain of the flagship of the infant Spacy, the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] fortress.
During the skirmishes of Space War I, Global came up with various strategies (with a little help from First Lieutenant http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Hayase Misa]) to evade the Zentradi, rather than attacking them head-on. The most tragic event under his command came with the collapse of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross]` ill-fated omnidirectional barrier, wiping out a large city in the Ontario region. The event caused a wider rift between him and the U.N., leading to the temporary exile of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] from Earth. Eventually, when http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia Fallyna] of the http://anidb.net/ch10537 [Lap Lamiz] fleet defected to the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] and wished to marry http://anidb.net/ch10506 [Maximilian Jenius], Global gave them permission, and by doing so made the first true step toward peace with the Zentradi.
After Space War I, he took an administrative position in the U.N. Government and designed the Human Emigration Project, a space colonization scheme followed by the U.N. for the following years to ensure the survival of mankind and its culture in case of further appearances of Zentradi and Supervision Army fleets. In the Macross continuity he became an admiral as well as commander of the U.N. Spacy after the battle against http://anidb.net/ch17601 [Boddole Zer]. He survives the Macross series to become U.N. Representative in 2014, and retires from the Spacy as a full Admiral.
He married Miho Global in March 2003. It`s unknown if they had any children, or if they survived the Battle with the http://anidb.net/ch17601 [Boddole Zer] Main Fleet.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>31510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3273" picture="239376.jpg">Hazama Michio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10508" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-15">
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<name>Kakizaki Hayao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hayao Kakizaki is an U.N. Spacy japanese variable fighter pilot who was assigned to the Vermilion Squadron, along with http://anidb.net/ch10506 [Maximilian Jenius], to be under the command of http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru]. He pilots a brown-white http://anidb.net/ch48787 [VF-1A Valkyrie] in the television series and in http://anidb.net/a996 [The Super Dimension Fortress Macross: Do You Remember Love?] movie he pilots a green-striped http://anidb.net/ch48787 [VF-1A Valkyrie]. Among the pilots of the Vermillion Squadron, Kakizaki is the least serious and skilled. His characterization adds to an already heavy laden humorous anime even more comic relief. He is portrayed also as being a laid back character, which often at times would endanger him while out battling the Zentradi. Compared to his teammates, Kakizaki is also the least experienced pilot, and from time-to-time, http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] and http://anidb.net/ch10506 [Max] had to save him from being killed.On November 2009, when Gunsight One`s radar system was damaged, Kakizaki, along with http://anidb.net/ch10506 [Max] and his superior, http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru] accompanied http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Hayase Misa] to scout the surrounding of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross]. During this mission, he and the others were captured by the Zentradi. This marks the first contact between the races.
In episode 19: Burst Point, Kakizaki was killed in action when the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross]`s barrier system overloads and Kakizaki`s Valkyrie was caught in the blast field. In the Macross chronology, he was KIA just after the episode of http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker]`s death. However, in http://anidb.net/a996 [The Super Dimension Fortress Macross: Do You Remember Love?] movie, he was killed in battle by missiles fired by a group of Queadluun-Raus led by http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia Fallyna] while joking with http://anidb.net/ch10506 [Max] and http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Hikaru] (Ironically underestimating their enemy`s strength due to them being female).Source: wiki</description>
<picture>31514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3196" picture="218728.jpg">Suzuki Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10509" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-14">
<rating votes="16">7.64</rating>
<name>Claudia La Salle</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Claudia La Salle is an American U.N. Spacy bridge officer in charge of weaponry and navigation of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] space fortress. She and fellow bridge officer http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Hayase Misa] are close friends, and she is often there to give her friend advice on matters of the heart (especially when it comes to http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Misa]`s confused feelings for http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru]), something http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Hayase] is awkward in. She used to be in a close relationship with http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker] until his death.
She is known as Claudia Grant in Robotech. Claudia LaSalle does not die at the end of Macross, although her Robotech counterpart does die.It is possible Claudia is a relative of http://anidb.net/ch14116 [Edgar LaSalle] from http://anidb.net/a427 [Macross Zero], who was http://anidb.net/ch14110 [Kudou Shin]`s RIO.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>31511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3414" picture="223019.jpg">Ohara Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10510" type="appears in" update="2009-07-19">
<name>Vanessa Laird</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3229.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6819" picture="173758.jpg">Sasaki Run</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10511" type="appears in" update="2009-07-19">
<rating votes="3">7.29</rating>
<name>Kim Kabirov</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3228.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10512" type="appears in" update="2009-07-19">
<rating votes="3">6.10</rating>
<name>Shammy Milliome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3227.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6820" picture="151692.jpg">Miyuki Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10513" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-19">
<rating votes="35">1.26</rating>
<name>Lynn Kaifun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10524" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<name>Riber von Fruhling</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55335.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21733" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<rating votes="9">8.07</rating>
<name>SDF-1 Macross</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>For thousands of millennia, an ancient war raged across the Milky Way Galaxy unbeknownst to the human race. In July 1999, that war came to humanity`s doorstep when a super-light-velocity spaceship crash-landed on Earth. The United Nations commences an investigation of the crash site located on South Ataria Island in the North Pacific Ocean. The spacecraft is given the code name Alien StarShip-1 (ASS-1) and investigations in the months following the crash uncover startling discoveries. Giant aliens, some five times the size of a human, crewed the craft which is revealed to be a warship; a Gun Destroyer from a faction called the Supervision Army. Most important of any discovery found in the alien spacecraft is the advanced technology contained within it. Given the name "OverTechnology," the United Nations Government (U.N.G) coordinates research quickly to understand it.
In 2001, several countries including Japan, United States, Russia, Germany, Britain, and France collaborate to establish an alien technology research institute called OTEC. Less than a year later, the OTEC commences a project to restore and reconstruct the ASS-1 to be commissioned as a capital ship for the newly formed United Nations Government. From February 2001 forward, the spacecraft is designated as the SDF-1; Super-Dimension-Fortress-1. Incredible advances are made from the research including the thermonuclear reaction system used to power the craft, the gravity control system, the space fold system for traveling faster-than-light and the super-dimension-energy cannons, the main weapon of the SDF-1. These technologies are adapted quickly and soon OverTechnology is being utilized in dozens of industries, notably super-small-scale thermonuclear reactors and the development of thermonuclear reaction bombs. Despite these unprecedented leaps of progress, many problems arise and threaten to undermine the launch of the SDF-1.
Originally set to launch in 2006, civil unrest abroad and the outbreak of the Anti-Unification Wars slows the SDF-1 restoration project. Eventually, the "UN Wars" cease on January 20th 2007 and the SDF-1 is rescheduled for launch in February 2009. It is the day of the launching ceremony that the opposing faction of the ancient war tracks the residual energies left by the ASS-1`s space fold and follow it to the Sol system. The newly christened SDF-1 Macross, armed with a heretofore undiscovered automated defense system, activates in response to the approaching enemy forces known as the Zentradi. The main cannon of the SDF-1 Macross fires from the surface of the Earth and destroys two Zentradi ships some 280,000 km out in space. The remaining Zentradi retaliate and intense fighting ensues. In an attempt to maneuver and regain the initiative, Captain http://anidb.net/ch10507 [Bruno J. Global] activates the space fold system to transport the SDF-1 Macross into Lunar orbit. Due to limited human understanding of the space fold system and improper instrumentation, the SDF-1 Macross folds far beyond the Moon, transporting the ship and much of the surrounding surface of South Ataria Island out past Pluto. This single engagement initiates the beginning of Space War I between the UN Spacy and the Zentradi.Over the length of more than a year during which Space War I is fought, the SDF-1 Macross travels from the outskirts of the Sol system back to Earth, fighting the forces of the Zentradi. The Zentradi are determined to capture the vessel, obsessed with the secrets of the ship`s obvious reconstruction and reaction weapons. This advantage allows the Macross to effectively use it`s formidable defenses, thwarting many attempts to be captured by the enemy. After Space War I ends on March 10th 2010, the Macross landing site is chosen as home for the reconstruction of Macross City. The Macross takes part in one more major engagement against rogue Zentradi Kamjin Kravshera`s forces during the Defensive Battle of Macross City in January 2012. Despite extensive damage following the battle, the Macross is repaired and undergoes a major refit. To this day, the Macross remains the home of the U.N. Military Command Center and is berthed in Macross City on Earth.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/macross.htm</description>
<picture>93969.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48774" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<name>CVS-101 Prometheus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The CVS-101 Prometheus was an open-type hangar deck aircraft carrier designed to serve as an amphibious launching craft for the VF-1 Valkyrie fighters. The Prometheus - along with the SLV-111 Daedalus - were present during the desparate space fold escape of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] in February 2009. Upon reaching Pluto, the Prometheus was docked with the port side of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] where the design of the Prometheus contributed greatly to the quick deployment of the Valkyrie fighters. During the remainder of Space War I the Prometheus and its complement of Valkyries played an important role in both the offensive and defensive operations of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross].
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/carrier-prometheus.htm</description>
<picture>93979.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48779" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<name>Quiltra-Queleual</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Quiltra-Queleual Class Landing Ship Tank (LST), like nearly all Zentradi ships of the line, has been in active service for hundreds of millennia. Another product of the war machines used during the ancient Schism War of the old Galactic Empire, the Quiltra-Queleual serves the role of a planetary assault ship. More than any of the other Zentradi capital ships, this vessel devotes the vast majority of internal volume to mecha bays and hangars for battle pods, fighters and re-entry craft. The ship features several launching hatches for efficient deployment including a large re-entry pod hatch. While not specifically designed for ship-to-ship combat, the Quiltra-Queleual still features a moderate number of anti-ship and anti-fighter weapons for attack and defense.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/quiltra-queleual.htm</description>
<picture>93986.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48783" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<name>Thuverl-Salan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The mainstay of the Zentradi fleets for at least 500 millennia, the Thuverl-Salan Class Battleships remain the primary combat vessel of the Zentradi war machine. Built in the latter era of the Protoculture and used extensively during the Schism War, the Thuverl-Salan`s impressive design and functionality guaranteed a long service life. The ship features numerous beam and missile weapon emplacements all along the craft and the practical wedge-shaped hull enables the Thuverl-Salan to bring to bear the maximum number of guns possible against a target vessel at nearly any angle. In addition to firepower, the Thuverl-Salan also carries numerous Glaug mecha, Gnerl Fighter Pods and Re-Entry ships for transporting land-based mecha to the surface of a planet.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/thurvel-salan.htm</description>
<picture>93990.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48785" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<name>Picket</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The picket is a patrol ship used by the Zentradi fleets for advance reconnaissance. Prior to any main fleet entering a potentially hostile or unexplored area of space, the picket ships are sent in to scout and report back to the command ship. When the Zentradi 67th Glruimual class branch http://anidb.net/ch10514 [Vrlitwhai] (Adoclass) Fleet entered the Sol system to find the crashed Supervision Army ship, two pickets were sent ahead to the planet upon which it crashed. The rebuilt http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross], having been set with an automated defense booby trap, fired upon the pickets and destroyed them both with a single shot. At 500 meters in length, the pickets were the smallest Zentradi capital ships seen in Space War I.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/picket.htm</description>
<picture>93992.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48787" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<name>VF-1A Valkyrie</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>After the crash-landing of the Alien StarShip-One in July 1999 it is discovered the alien crew was a race of giants some five times the size of a human. Fearful of being unprepared for a conflict with these aliens, the newly formed United Nations Government (UNG) begins researching anti-giant weapon systems technologies. Utilizing the now named OverTechnology found on the ASS-1, the non-variable humanoid mecha called the Destroid is designed; another weapon system is the transformable Battroid. The UNG contracts Stonewell and Bellcom to develop an all-environment variable fighter eventually known as the "Valkyrie." Rising to the challenge, Stonewell and Bellcom subcontract with OT reaction powerplant producer Shinnakasu Heavy Industry and Destroid developer Centinental to complete a basic design by 2005. The first transformable prototype is successfully tested in 2007 and the UNG decides to formally adopt the Valkyrie in November of that year. By late 2008, mass production is in full swing on the VF-1A variable fighter.
From February 2009 to March 2010, the VF-1A Valkyrie served as the standard variable fighter of the U.N. Spacy in Space War I. The VF-1 proved to be an extremely capable craft, successfully combating a variety of Zentradi mecha even in most sorties which saw UN Spacy forces significantly outnumbered. The versatility of the Valkyrie design enabled the variable fighter to act as both large-scale infantry and as air/space superiority fighter. The signature skills of U.N. Spacy ace pilot http://anidb.net/ch10506 [Maximilian Jenius] exemplified the effectiveness of the variable systems as he near-constantly transformed the Valkyrie in battle to seize advantages of each mode as combat conditions changed from moment to moment. The basic VF-1 was deployed in four minor variants (designated A, D, J, and S) and its success was increased by continued development of various enhancements including the GBP-1S "Armored" Valkyrie and FAST Pack "Super" Valkyrie weapon systems.
After the end of Space War I, the VF-1A continued to be manufactured both in the Sol system (notably on the Lunar facility Apollo Base) and throughout the UNG space colonies. Although the VF-1 would eventually be replaced as the primary VF of the UN Spacy by the VF-4 Lightning III in 2020, a long service record and continued production after the war proved the lasting worth of the design. The VF-1A was without doubt the most recognizable variable fighter of Space War I and was seen as a vibrant symbol of the U.N. Spacy even into the first year of the New Era 0001 in 2013. At the end of 2015 the final rollout of the VF-1 was celebrated at a special ceremony, commemorating this most famous of variable fighters.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/vf-1a-valkyrie.htm</description>
<picture>93999.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48789" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<name>VF-1J Valkyrie</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Shinnakasu Heavy Industry`s VF-1J (the "J" speculated as a prideful designation of the fighter`s region of origin) is an upgraded version of the standard VF-1, typically assigned to the senior officer of an air team or to a squadron leader. Unlike Stonewell/Bellcom`s VF-1D, the VF-1J remains a single seat fighter but shares the slightly increased firepower of that variant. The new head unit of the VF-1J (developed by Kyuusei Industry) features two Mauler RÖV-20 anti-aircraft laser cannons in a slightly improved configuration. Naturally, when the Shinnakasu-designed GBP-1S "Armored" system was given first operational deployment, it was installed on a VF-1J.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/vf-1j-valkyrie.htm</description>
<picture>94007.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48790" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<name>VF-1S Valkyrie</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The final of the four minor VF-1 variants, the VF-1S carries the heaviest weapon load of the standard variable fighter. Manufactured only in limited numbers, Northrom also enlisted Kyuusei Industry to design a new head unit for their own variant. The VF-1S mounts four of the Mauler series RÖV-20 anti-aircraft laser cannons and enjoys several upgrades in addition to firepower. The engines are improved Shinnakasu Heavy Industry/P&amp;W/Roice FF-2001D models resulting in measurably improved thrust and an enhanced avionics package is featured in each VF-1S. While usually reserved for CAGs (Commander of Air Group), the VF-1S also sometimes finds itself serving as the variable fighter for a squadron leader much like the VF-1J. Captain http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker] piloted a VF-1S during his command of the infamous Skull Squadron.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/vf-1s-valkyrie.htm</description>
<picture>94008.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48791" type="appears in" update="2012-09-13">
<name>ARMD</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The ARMD Class vessels were designed as space carriers for variable fighters and other U.N.S. spacecraft. The ARMD began construction in April 2003 at the Lagrange Point 5 manufacturing station. The first two carriers ARMD-01 and ARMD-02 were commissioned in July 2008 and October 2008 respectively and were opertaional prior to Space War I in February 2009. Built by OTEC Company, the ARMD carriers featured OverTechnology with gravity control systems, a reaction heat pile system and even the fold drive (though this super dimension navigation system was never implemented). At 430 meters in length, the ARMD carriers were much smaller than the large http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] and both ARMD-01 and ARMD-02 were originally meant to dock with the larger craft when the ship achieved orbit during its maiden voyage.
As a carrier vessel, the ARMDs held numerous ships and mecha. ARMD-01 held 78 SF-A3 Lancer II space fighters and 270 QF-3000E Ghost fighters (as well as an unknown number of VF-1A variable fighters) just prior to Space War I. In addition to several hundred fighters, the ARMD carrier was armed with many weapons including beam cannons, small anti-aircraft cannons and launchers as well as large anti-ship reaction warheads. The ARMD possessed many large vernier thruster nozzles positioned all over the craft. These powerful thrusters granted the ARMD excellent maneuverability in space and also proved very useful for combat engagement and evasion.Both ARMD-01 and ARMD-02 were destroyed in the first battle of Space War I on February 7, 2009. However, both vessels engaged in combat with the Zentradi fleet and proved quite successful in destroying several large Zentradi capital warships with their anti-ship reaction warheads. Eventually, six more vessels of the ARMD Class were commissioned and both the original ships were replaced. To this day, ARMD-01 and ARMD-02 remain docked with the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] on Earth.Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/armd.htm</description>
<picture>94009.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48811" type="appears in" update="2012-09-15">
<name>Regult</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Simple, efficient and reliable, the Esbeliben Regult is the standard mass production mecha of the Zentradi Army. Produced in staggering numbers to fill the need for an all-purpose mecha, this battle pod accommodates a single Zentradi soldier in a compact cockpit and is capable of operating in space or on a planet`s surface. In space, the Regult makes use of two booster engines and numerous vernier thrusters to propel itself at very high speeds, capable of engaging and maintaining pace with the UN Spacy`s VF-1 variable fighter. Within an atmosphere, the Regult is largely limited to ground combat but retains high speed and maneuverability. Armed with a variety of direct-fire energy weapons and anti-personnel/anti-aircraft guns, the Regult is capable of engaging both air and ground units. The Regult is also capable of high, thruster-assisted leaping that allows the pod to cover long distances and engage low flying aircraft. On land, the Regult is surprisingly fast, capable of closing with the VF-1 variable fighter in GERWALK flight (though likely unable to maintain pace at full GERWALK velocity).
The Regult saw much use during Space War I in repeated engagements against the forces of the UN Spacy, but its lack of versatility against superior mecha often resulted in average effectiveness. Several variants were seen in the war, typically with additional equipment to mount missile launchers or modified with electronic warfare equipment for ECM and reconnaissance roles. Possessing minimal defensive features, the Regult is a simple weapon that performs best in large numbers and when supported by other mecha such as Fighter Pods.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/reguld.htm</description>
<picture>94041.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48812" type="appears in" update="2012-09-15">
<name>Regult (Kogata Missile Soubi-gata)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Regult, being the Zentradi Army`s main combat mecha, was designed to be equipped with many optional weapons to increase effectiveness and adapt to different mission requirements. One of these variants of the standard Regult is the Light Missile Carrier. Sacrificing the aft-mounted anti-aircraft laser cannons, the Light Missile Carrier features two missile launchers on a single mount. Each of the two launchers features twelve guided missiles for use in close combat. The missiles utilized can vary significantly from single warheads to energy beam "flechette" missiles. Optimizing the weapons payload, the Light Missile Carrier has the option of firing single warheads, rapid succession payloads or burst groups of two-to-four missiles. Though primarily used for anti-aircraft/anti-mecha purposes, in large numbers the Light Missile Carrier is a danger even to large capital ships and is often found in mixed groups of Regult mecha along side Heavy Missile Carriers and standard Regults.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/reguld-light.htm</description>
<picture>94043.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48813" type="appears in" update="2012-09-15">
<name>Regult (Oogata Missile Tousai-gata)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Another variant to the standard Regult battle pod, the Heavy Missile Carrier utilizes two missile launchers in place of the standard aft-mounted anti-aircraft laser cannons. Using a single mount connected to the dorsal fuselage, the missile launchers of the Heavy Missile Carrier house only four heavy missiles. However, the missiles are outfitted with multiple warheads and are capable of destroying even the most heavily armored mecha. In most combat sorties, the Heavy Missile Carrier was used in conjunction with Light Missile Carriers and standard Regults, maximizing the combined arms of the Zentradi Regult mecha forces.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/reguld-heavy.htm</description>
<picture>94044.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48814" type="appears in" update="2012-09-15">
<name>Regult (Teisatsu-gata)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A deadly addition to the Zentradi Regult mecha forces, the Tactical Scout is the reconnaissance variant of the standard Regult battle pod. Removing all weaponry, the Tactical Scout is equipped with many additional sensor clusters and long-range detection equipment. Always found operating among other Regult mecha, the Scout is capable of early warning enemy detection as well as ECM/ECCM roles (Electronic Countermeasures/Electronic Counter-Countermeasures). In Space War One, the Tactical Scout was utilized to devastating effect, often providing radar jamming, communication relay and superior tactical positioning for the many Zentradi mecha forces.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/reguld-scout.htm</description>
<picture>94045.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48862" type="appears in" update="2012-09-14">
<name>HWR-00-Mk.II Monster</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>An immense mecha, the Heavy Weight Robot (HWR) Monster Mk II is a heavily armed "land battleship" with a name matching the great size of the destroid. Very shortly after the initial research into the destroids began in 2000 the HWR-00 series began development in December that year. After a lengthy design phase trial production began in October 2005 and the HWR-00 Monster first rollout was in September 2008. The Monster is the largest mobile ground weapon to ever be fielded in battle by mankind, over 41 meters long and weighing almost 300 tons. The Monster was envisioned as a trackless, self-propelled heavy weapon system to be utilized for attack and point defense. In actuality, the Monster`s massive size, poor maneuverability and dedicated long-range weaponry saw the mecha used as a semi-mobile artillery unit best utilized while avoiding uneven ground and any close-range engagement. When put to best use with supporting units in a combined arms role, the Monster is able to field incredible firepower equal to strategic bombing.
The Monster was originally designed to use 50cm linear cannons, but was scaled down with smaller guns when problems arose with system strength and insufficient power for continuous firing. Armed with four 40cm cannons, the Monster can fire a variety of munitions with the primary guns, including anti-armor shells, anti-aircraft munitions, howitzers and even nuclear reaction warheads (OverTechnology reaction warheads have an explosive yield rated at 0.1 kilotons to 50 kilotons). In addition to the main guns, the Mk II features a pair of 3-barreled missile launchers not originally included in the design but incorporated into the two arm units. To compensate for the Monster`s vulnerabilities such as the intense heat emissions of the unit (which prevented effective use of counter measures such as chaff or smoke), the armor was designed to be extremely thick and even capable of withstanding a near hit from a reaction weapon.
Though mass-produced like the other destroids, only two Monster Mk II units were onboard the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] during the outbreak of Space War I. During the conflict, the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] onboard factories made use of equipment for several more Monster mecha and produced a third unit to accompany the original two. Most of the other Monster units were destroyed by orbital bombardment from the Zentradi fleet. The few Monster Mk II units aboard the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] distinguished themselves as very capable war machines during Space War I. While most destroid units suffered heavy losses, the Monsters aboard the ship remained in active service for most of the war and the capability to launch reaction warheads was put to use during the battle with the http://anidb.net/ch17601 [Boddole Zer] Main Fleet in February 2010.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/destroid-monster.htm</description>
<picture>94097.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48881" type="appears in" update="2012-09-14">
<name>MBR-04-Mk.VI Tomahawk</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The first of the MBR-04 series Destroids, the Tomahawk Mk I entered service in February 2007. Conceived as a non-variable combat robot designed to counter giant-sized infantry, the Tomahawk was built using OverTechnology taken researched from the crash of the alien space craft known as the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] in 1999. Once successfully tested, the Tomahawk became the basis for three other Destroid types and the improved Tomahawk Mk VI quickly followed in late 2007.
The Tomahawk Mk VI is the most heavily armed Destroid of the MBR-04 series and the most widely deployed model. Of the nearly 600 hundred Destroids aboard the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] in February 2009, over 500 were Tomahawk Mk VI units. Armed with a wide array of weaponry suited to nearly any combat operation, the Tomahawk features particle cannons, missiles, machine guns, lasers and flamethrowers to unleash fire in any role from anti-personnel to anti-aircraft. The Mk VI version also features a retractable periscope and includes the option of mounting searchlight/missile packs in one or both mounts on either side of the top weapons bays.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/destroid-tomahawk.htm</description>
<picture>94107.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48891" type="appears in" update="2012-09-15">
<name>ADR-04-Mk.X Defender</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>After the successful design of the first destroids, the U.N. Government began exploring various concepts in destroid technology to build main battle robots (MBRs) suited to different operational roles. One such concept was to create an anti-aircraft destroid that could mount powerful, super-far-range weaponry for firing in space. A joint development program by Viggers-Chrauler was authorized by the U.N. Government and resulted in the eventual deployment of the Mk X Defender Destroid. Utilizing the standard destroid ambulatory system, the Defender featured a new upper chassis with two, double barrel Erlikon Contraves II weapons systems firing 78mm rounds. These impressive wide-bore guns fired 500 rounds per minute from each of the four barrels and had a muzzle velocity of 3,300 meters per second. Two large ammunition drums mounted on top of the chassis fed through the weapons bays for fast firing and designs were eventually made for enlarged magazines featuring a much greater ammunition capacity.
The Mk X Defender Destroid proved successful and was approved for mass production. Unfortunately the weapons systems were prohibitively expensive and notoriously difficult to manufacture, resulting in a lengthy lead-time to deployment. The first Defender units saw action shortly after the beginning of Space War I but only in limited numbers. Forty units were manufactured aboard the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] and served throughout the war along side other destroid units. Though the Defender was a capable mecha, as a defensive unit in constant front line engagements, these destroids suffered heavy losses during the war.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/destroid-defender.htm</description>
<picture>94136.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48996" type="appears in" update="2012-09-18">
<name>Quiltra-Quelamitz</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>A potent warship, the Quiltra-Quelamitz class vessel is an often forgotten but significant part of the Zentradi fleets. Though the craft is somewhat small by the standards of most Zentradi ships of the line, it possesses one of the most devastating weapons of the fleet. The forward half of the craft is dominated by the main gun, a heavy converging energy beam cannon. The bow splits in half vertically, collimating the energy of the blast just prior to release. The main gun can blast through the most heavily armored hypercarbon hulls of enemy spacecraft and can rain high-energy mass destruction down upon a planetary body. With it`s powerful primary weapon, the Quiltra-Quelamitz is the backbone of any large-scale fleet-to-fleet engagement and a necessary tool for operations requiring effective planetary bombardment. Though primarily an anti-ship/anti-fortifications vessel, the Quiltra-Quelamitz does feature many conventional cannon emplacements upon its hull and carries a modest complement of Nousjadeul-Ger powered armor suits for anti-mecha attack and defense.Aside from its role in the destruction of planet Earth on February 2010, the most notable operation involving a Quiltra-Quelamitz class ship was during the Defensive Battle of Macross City in January 2012. Zentradi warlord http://anidb.net/ch10516 [Quamzin Kravshera] commanded a Quiltra-Quelamitz in his failed attempt to destroy the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross]. During the battle, the main cannon of the Quiltra-Quelamitz inflicted fatal damage on the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] with a single shot, penetrating the hull and destroying the ship`s main reactors. Though the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] was able to briefly return fire via auxiliary power, the Quiltra-Quelamitz was able to remain aloft after a direct hit from the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] super-dimension-energy cannon. The Quiltra-Quelamitz then rammed the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [Macross] in a suicide run, but only succeeded in severing the starboard arm and docked http://anidb.net/ch48825 [SLV-111 Daedalus] carrier from the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1] before crashing to the ground just beyond the shore of Lake Macross.Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/sdfmacross/quiltra-quelamitz.htm</description>
<picture>94334.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49046" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Vrlitwhai 7018</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vrlitwhai appeared in the movie http://anidb.net/a996 [The Super Dimension Fortress Macross: Do You Remember Love?] as a Zentradi commander who also becomes a defector to the human side. However, he appeared bald with a modified uniform and face plate, and his name was changed to Vrlitwhai 7018 in the film credits.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>94418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5229" picture="156605.jpg">Kanie Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49047" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-19">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Exsedol 4970</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Exsedol appeared in the movie http://anidb.net/a996 [The Super Dimension Fortress Macross: Do You Remember Love?], also as a Zentradi advisor who becomes a defector to the human side. However, his appearance was radically redesigned, with a bald, swollen head, green skin, a cloak covering his body, and retractable tendrils for arms.
This design was carried over to his subsequent appearance in the TV series http://anidb.net/a442 [Macross 7], with some slight differences, namely that he has a blue collar, green tendrils, and a slightly darker skin tone. Exsedol in http://anidb.net/a442 [Macross 7] is also rarely seen without a hemispherical cap on his cranium, usually connected to the ceiling.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>94419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3383" picture="24325.jpg">Oobayashi Ryuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49048" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Queadluun-Rau</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Already largely organic in appearance, the film version of the Queadluun-Rau underwent only a subtle redsign from the television series. The most notable difference was the change in colors, utlizing the Meltrandi magenta fleet colors for the standard version while http://anidb.net/ch10517 [Milia]`s unit was colored red (perhaps a subtle historical allegory to Manfred von Richthofen, the Red Baron of World War I). Aside from the different colors and slight stylistic changes, the Queadluun-Rau was just as deadly in the movie.
Following the Great Interstellar War (Space War I), the Queadluun-Rau units were employed by the U.N. Forces. Unfortunately, breakdowns in production at the Factory Satellite caused a gradual decrease in operational units. Operational rates were reduced such that by the 2030s the Queadluun-Rau could not be supported by available spare parts. Fortunately, support for reproduction of the Queadluun-Rau remained strong. In 2035, variable fighter design and manufacturing company General Galaxy was entrusted by the U.N. Forces with a modernization and reproduction plan for the Queadluun-Rau.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/queadluun-rau-dyrl.htm</description>
<picture>94421.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49049" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Nousjadeul-Ger</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Similar in function and armament to the television series version, the Nousjadeul-Ger film version featured a more organic redesign for the movie. The Nousjadeul-Ger was also more visible in the film http://anidb.net/a996 [Macross: Do You Remember Love?] proven by it`s inclusion in three major combat sequences in the first two acts of the film. The film version of the Nousjadeul-Ger is also seen using rifles (in addition to a redesigned mecha pistol) and a barely seen variant featuring a 6-rack missile launcher mounted on the top left thruster is also briefly glimpsed during the initial combat scene.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/nousjadeul-ger-dyrl.htm</description>
<picture>94422.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49050" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Nupetiet-Vergnitzs</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Nearly identical to the television series version, the Nupetiet-Vergnitzs Class Fleet Command Battleship is featured with a slightly different color scheme in the film http://anidb.net/a996 [Do You Remember Love?]. The other significant difference seen in the film version of the Battleship is a ship-length heavy converging beam cannon similar to the http://anidb.net/ch48996 [Quiltra-Quelamitz] Class Gunboat. The Nupetiet-Vergnitzs main gun activates by lifting the dorsal hull and dropping the ventral hull (nearly opening the entire ship from stem to stern) and thus acts as a collimator for super dimension energy to collect and fire forward. In Space War I, Commander http://anidb.net/ch49046 [Vrlitwhai] used this powerful weapon to blast a large hole through the hull of the Bodol Zer Mobile Fortress, allowing the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] to fly into the ship and attack Gorg Bodolzaa directly.Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/nupetiet-vergnitzs-dyrl.htm</description>
<picture>94424.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49051" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>VE-1 ELINT Seeker</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A faster and much more extensively equipped electronic warfare variable fighter, the VE-1 "ELINT Seeker" saw service later in Space War One as a reconnaissance and ECM/ECCM unit. The unofficial designation "ELINT" stands for ELectronic Signals INTelligence, and refers to intelligence gathering by use of electronic sensors. Built by Shinnakasu Heavy Industry (with subcontractor Bifors), the VE-1 combines the capabilities of the FAST Pack space booster system with extensive electronic warfare hardware. Two CTB-04 conformal propellant/coolant tanks (mounted on the leg/engines), two NR-BP-E3 booster thrusters mounted on the dorsal section and two NR-FS-E3 units mounted on the leg/engines provide plenty of fuel for long-range operations and additional thrust for quick evasion. The customized FAST Packs also house the majority of the unit`s electronic warfare equipment including lateral, multi-directional and omni-directional radar systems. This two-seater variant quickly became a valuable support craft on the battlefield, assisting both fighter and capital ship scale long-range combat operations.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/ve-1-elintseeker-valkyrie.htm</description>
<picture>94426.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49052" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>VT-1 Ostrich</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>An unarmed variable fighter, the VT-1 "Ostrich" is the UN Spacy`s first dedicated training Valkyrie. Like the http://anidb.net/ch48788 [VF-1D], the Ostrich is a two-seater variant of the standard VF-1 variable fighter with a smaller, simplified head unit and the capability to mount a customized FAST Pack system for use in space. The Shinnakasu Heavy Industry NP-BP-T1 FAST Pack space booster system offers the VT-1 the increased range and improved thrust typical of the unit, but the packs include no micro-missiles. The Ostrich FAST Packs include oversized dorsal propellant tanks, an additional antenna on the starboard booster pod, a wide-nozzle booster mounted on the tail section and swaps two low-thrust verniers for two additional high-maneuverability vernier thrusters.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/vt-1-ostrich.htm</description>
<picture>94427.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49053" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Golg Gants Charts</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Golg Gants Charts heavy attack vehicle is the smallest craft that can be mounted with a warship gun and is designed to be a fast and maneuverable anti-ship unit. Built around the central converging energy beam cannon, the pilot controls both the craft and the main gun from inside the cockpit on the port side of the vessel while a gunner is situated inside the anti-aircraft turret on the starboard side. Possessing a double barrel laser cannon turret and two missile launchers for defense, the Golg Gants Charts must still rely on friendly supporting units to defend against light or medium enemy mecha. Often these ships are utilized in unison with other heavy attack craft and friendly mecha to engage enemy forces with some measure of success. During Space War I the Golg Gants Charts saw only limited use by the Zentradi forces as it was vulnerable to the strong destroid defenses of the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross]. However, the Golg Gants Charts was still feared for it`s great firepower and maneuverability superior to that of any large warship. In one notable battle during Space War I, the Golg Gants Charts attacked the forward destroid forces on the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] directly, allowing supporting heavy attack craft a chance to penetrate the hull of the U.N. Spacy ship and lead the http://anidb.net/ch49049 [Nousjadeul-Ger] battle suit forces inside.Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/golg-gants-charts.htm</description>
<picture>94428.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49054" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>A510</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Eye-catching in scarlet red paint, the two-seat A510 Sports Car is a fast and comfortable personal vehicle often seen in use by the civilian population aboard the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1] during Space War I. After an attack upon the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SFD-1 Macross] by Zentradi forces, http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru] and http://anidb.net/ch7418 [Lynn Minmay] were trapped inside a damaged section of the ship. After they were rescued, http://anidb.net/ch7418 [Minmay] drove off in an A510 Car, driven by her cousin http://anidb.net/ch10513 [Kaifun]. A popular and stylish vehicle, the lasting influence of the A510 can be seen in personal vehicles made in following decades. Most notably, the influence of the A510 can be seen during the late 2030`s and early 2040`s when several different cars and even motorcycles appeared, taking obvious design lineage from this stylish vehicle.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/a510car.htm</description>
<picture>94429.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49055" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>RC-4E Rabbit</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The RC-4E Rabbit is a small spacecraft typically used for reconnaissance and light personnel transport. The Rabbit features two large communication antennae and a large sensor mounted on top of the craft as well as four large thrusters of flight and two landing struts likely responsible for the ships name given the resemblance to a rabbit`s feet. The ship is large enough to carry 4-6 passengers (including flight crew) and some small storage for minor equipment. During an unauthorized pleasure flight around Saturn by http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru] in Space War I, 1st Lieutenant http://anidb.net/ch7652 [Hayase Misa] pursued http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou] in an RC-4E Rabbit to order him back to the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross]. The Zentradi then conducted an operation to capture the two craft and although the Rabbit was initially able to evade, the craft could not outrun the pursuing http://anidb.net/ch49049 [Nousjadeul-Ger] power battle suits over time.Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/rabbit.htm</description>
<picture>94432.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49056" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Quamzin 03350</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Quamzin is a brilliant but mentally unstable Zentradi commander during Space War I. He appears in the 1984 film http://anidb.net/a996 [The Super Dimension Fortress Macross: Do You Remember Love?] as a Zentradi commander who attacks and critically damages http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Roy Focker]`s Valkyrie aboard http://anidb.net/ch49046 [Vrlitwhai]`s ship. During the melee, http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Focker] shoots him in the back, and both die when http://anidb.net/ch10505 [Focker]`s Valkyrie explodes. (Quamzin is unnamed in the dialogue, but listed in the ending credits and script as "Quamzin 03350").Source: wiki</description>
<picture>94433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3254" picture="2047.gif">Meguro Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49057" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Gol Boddole Zer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Boddole Zer appeared in the movie http://anidb.net/a996 [The Super Dimension Fortress Macross: Do You Remember Love?] as a cyborg Zentradi leader who was fused with a massive combat mobile fortress that had a 120,000 cycle history of space battles. In the movie, Boddole Zer was also in command of a male Zentradi fleet which had been at war with the female Meltlandi for hundreds of thousands of years. He orders the destruction of Earth after his fleet discovers a rebuilt Meltlandi ship on the planet before the beginning of the film. After both the Zentradi and the Meltlandi become "cultured" by an ancient Protoculture song and join the surviving humans, Boddole Zer and his fortress are attacked by the combined forces of both fleets and the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross]. Boddole Zer himself is destroyed by http://anidb.net/ch7654 [Ichijou Hikaru] flying a VF-1 Valkyrie variable fighter at the end of the film.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>94435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3227" picture="24207.jpg">Ichikawa Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49058" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Gol Boddole Zer</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The largest "ship class" vessel of the Zentradi forces, the Gol Boddole Zer-Class Mobile Fortress served as the mothership for the Zentradi for 120,000 cycles and in Space War I. Decorated in the familiar green hull of the Zentradi forces, the sprawling Gol Boddole Zer mobile fortress appears almost organic in design, resembling vegetation. At some 600 kilometers in width, the vessel was bristling with weapons and functioned as a mobile port for the Zentradi ships of the line. Most impressive of all, the Gol Boddole Zer mobile fortress featured a powerful main beam gun located in large globe at the bow of the ship. When fired, the beam gun produced a broad beam of energy that could destroy thousands of smaller warships or even a vessel as large as itself with but a single shot. Though the gun could only be fired once (due to damage over the many years of interstellar warfare), Zentradi leader Gol Boddole Zer utilized it to destroy the Meltrandi mobile fortress in the final battle of Space War I. However, http://anidb.net/ch49057 [Boddole Zer]`s victory was achieved only at the cost of destroying thousands of his ships in the line of fire, a decision that ultimately brought about his own demise. Some 1,000 ships of this same class continue to operate in the Milky Way Galaxy at the end of Space War I.Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/gorgbodolzaa-mobilefortress.htm</description>
<picture>94436.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49059" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Conda 88333</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34076" picture="94525.jpg">Kent Gilbert</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49060" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Warera 25258</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94439.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49061" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Loli 28356</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6846" picture="31557.jpg">Fujii Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49062" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-19">
<rating votes="5">7.10</rating>
<name>Milia 639</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Just as in the original http://anidb.net/a77 [Super Dimension Fortress Macross], Milia is depicted as an ace pilot. Milia is first seen when the Meltrandi breached http://anidb.net/ch49046 [Vrlitwhai]`s http://anidb.net/ch49050 [Nupetiet-Vergnitzs]. As she entered the ship, Milia starts killing every Zentran she sees, and after executing her task, flees with gusto.Milia`s subsequent appearance in the movie is during the battle between the Macross fleet and the Meltrandi. In this battle, Milia entered into Lap Lamiz`s ship with a tailing http://anidb.net/ch10506 [Maximilian Jenius] behind her. She was shot down within the ship. Upon breaching the http://anidb.net/ch49048 [Queadluun-Rau] armor, http://anidb.net/ch10506 [Max] is enamored by Milia (as she is with him) and expresses his awe of the Meltran pilot. Milia and http://anidb.net/ch10506 [Max] are finally seen battling together against http://anidb.net/ch49057 [Boddole Zer] and his fleet, http://anidb.net/ch10506 [Max] having been enlarged to Zentradi size.Source: wiki</description>
<picture>94443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5930" picture="30527.jpg">Takeda Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49099" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-21">
<name>Moruk Lap Lamiz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5960" picture="188720.jpg">Ootori Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49100" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>Moruk Lap Lamiz</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Meltlandi Laplamiz-Class Mobile Fortress was seen only briefly near the end of Space War I. This immense spacecraft, comparable in size to the Zentradi http://anidb.net/ch49058 [Gol Boddole Zer Class Mobile Fortress], served as the mothership for the Laplamiz Meltlandi fleet. As tall as the ship is wide, the Laplamiz mobile fortress appears in the familiar magenta colors of the Meltlandi fleets but the hull appears almost rock-like in design, resembling a multi-tiered mountain range. The Laplamiz class is many times the size of the large Meltlan Flagships and within it`s hull the mothership can berth numerous other craft for fueling and supply. During the final decisive conflict of Space War I, the Laplamiz class led the Meltlandi fleet in battle against the Zentradi Gol Boddole Zer fleet. Though both fleets were evenly matched, http://anidb.net/ch49057 [Gol Boddole Zer] desired victory so greatly, he was willing to destroy many of his own Zentradi ships to defeat the Meltlandi. The http://anidb.net/ch49058 [Zentradi Mobile Fortress] fired it`s massive main beam gun upon the Laplamiz Mobile Fortress, destroying the Meltlandi mothership, a portion of the Meltlandi fleet and thousands of the Zentradi`s own ships. Ultimately, the strategy would prove the downfall of http://anidb.net/ch49057 [Gol Boddole Zer].Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/laplamiz-mobilefortress.htm</description>
<picture>94535.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49101" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>Meltlan Gunboat</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The medium-sized, gunboat-class is a famous Meltlandi vessel that was commanded by the ever more famous http://anidb.net/ch49062 [Milia 639] during Space War I. The two large-sized engines provide the gunboat with such high maneuverability and acceleration the ship can achieve the same capabilities as a space fighter. An excellent battleship, the gunboat boasts a potent high-output, short-range guided converging beam gun built as the bow of the ship. When preparing to fire, the bow of the gunboat separates laterally, gathers energy between the two forward booms and releases a very destructive blast at an enemy target. The gunboat class is suitable for a myriad of operation roles including search, reconnaissance, raids upon enemy bases or special missions. Like it`s counterpart vessel the http://anidb.net/ch48996 [Quiltra-Quelamitz] in the male Zentradi fleets, the gunboat is also well equipped for atmospheric maneuvering. Since it is operated by female Meltlandi, the ship carries a complement of http://anidb.net/ch49048 [Queadluun-Rau] mecha. The Meltlandi sent a gunboat to Earth to intercept and destroy the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1 Macross] upon its return. With a devastating blast from the powerful main gun, the Meltlan gunboat destroyed the top hull booms on the http://anidb.net/ch21733 [SDF-1]`s own main gun, causing the massive vessel to crash.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/Meltran-gunboat.htm</description>
<picture>94538.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49102" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>Meltlan Flagship</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>A large vessel some four thousand meters long, the Meltlan Flagship is a heavily armed fleet command warship for the female Meltlan forces. As large as the Zentradi http://anidb.net/ch49050 [Nupetiet-Vergnitzs] battleship but less massive, the Meltlan Flagship is a medium scale vessel that commands smaller fleet branches within any Meltlan main fleet. Like its Zentradi counterpart, the Meltlan Flagship is armed with many weapons, numerous mecha, and is the largest conventional warship in the Meltlan forces, eclipsed only by the Lap Lamiz Mobile Fortress.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/Meltran-flagship.htm</description>
<picture>94540.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49103" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>Meltlan LST</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>A long ship at some 3,000 meters, the Meltlan LST (Landing Ship Tank) is the capital ship carrier vessel for the Meltlandi war machine. The Meltlan LST, like it`s Zentradi counterpart the http://anidb.net/ch48779 [Quiltra-Queleual] Class, is a planetary assault ship that carries troops, vehicles and mecha for planet-side operations.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/meltran-lst.htm</description>
<picture>94541.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49104" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>Meltlan Destroyer</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Meltlan Destroyer is another sleek medium-scale warship with a prominently narrow and vertically structured hull. The counterpart to the Zentradi http://anidb.net/ch48783 [Thuverl-Salan] vessel, the Meltlan Destroyer is some 2,500 meters long and a primary combat vessel of the Meltlandi fleets.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/meltran-destroyer.htm</description>
<picture>94542.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49105" type="appears in" update="2012-10-08">
<name>Meltlan Battleship</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Meltran Battleship, like the http://anidb.net/ch49104 [Meltran Destroyer], is a mainstay combat warship of the Meltlandi fleet. Some 2,700 meters in length, the ship is larger and more heavily armed than the destroyer and is most likely used as a command vessel for smaller formations and groups within a larger fleet.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/meltran-battleship.htm</description>
<picture>94544.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49106" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>Meltlan Cruiser</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>At roughly 2,000 meters in length and over 700 meters high, the Meltlan Cruiser is notable move away from the sleek and lengthy designs typical of the Meltlandi capital ships. Nonetheless, the Meltlan Cruiser is another powerful addition to the female Meltrandi forces and is always part of any Meltlandi fleet.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/meltran-cruiser.htm</description>
<picture>94545.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49107" type="appears in" update="2012-09-22">
<name>Meltlan Picket</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>At roughly 300 meters in length, the Meltlan Picket is the smallest Meltlandi ship of the line and possibly the smallest capital ship among either the Meltlandi or Zentradi fleets. The Meltlan Picket acts as a forward line of any Meltlandi fleet to which it is attached, helping to warn accompanying vessels of enemy movements.
Source: http://www.macross2.net/m3/macrossdyrl/meltran-picket.htm</description>
<picture>94546.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49111" type="appears in" update="2012-09-21">
<name>Tewanton 3565</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch49062 [Milia]`s adjutant.</description>
<picture>94562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3147" picture="49928.jpg">Ogai Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="10233" update="2004-09-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>1984-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25134" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>1984-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="25135" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>1984-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72128" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1984-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72129" update="2008-01-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1984-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72130" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1984-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91388" update="2008-06-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91389" update="2008-06-15">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91390" update="2008-06-15">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91391" update="2008-06-15">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176389" update="2016-03-27">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 [30s]</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176390" update="2016-03-27">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 [15s]</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
