<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9967" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>22</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-10-11</startdate>
<enddate>2014-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Samurai Flamenco</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Samumenco</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">サムライフラメンコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Samurai Flamenco</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Samurai Flamenco</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Samurai Flamenco</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Самурай Фламенко</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">武士弗拉明戈</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8101" approval="17" total="30">Tiger &amp; Bunny</anime>
<anime id="11123" approval="6" total="12">One Punch Man</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="532954">A must see for superhero fans!! It just makes you want to put on a costume and start fighting the crime!Drama,action,humor it has the whole pack!It`s the core of the world Justice!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="230807">It`s a very nice anime in which the characters aren`t shallow and yet they are. It`s awesome. It`s weird how shallow and non shallow it can be at the same time, but it totally works!!

A must see!! but it is hard to descriphe why.. however if you watch it you`ll get hooked. 

Real life stuff with violence and humor!! The only thought that will go through your mind:

JAPAN IS DOOMED!! 

and that folks is what makes this series so awesome ~~ &amp;lt;3</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="558382">Good and enjoyable with a mixture of comedy and slice of life genre and both mature and childish sides until it becomes serious. Like the enemies that suicide at the end, this series did the same by changing its genre to an absurd fictional heroic type.

The ending is truly great.

Still recommended, but I won`t follow up with the rest of the series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="280191">Phenomenal. Even if you`re not a fan of tokusatsu, you`ll still have a great time. 

You never know what to expect. Just SIT DOWN and enjoy the ride.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.samumenco.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4359" type="Direction">Oomori Takahiro</name>
<name id="986" type="Work">Manglobe</name>
<name id="2457" type="Character Design">Yamashita Yoshimitsu</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="5059" type="Music">Tamai Kenji</name>
<name id="38344" type="Music">Agehasprings</name>
</creators>
<description>Famous model http://anidb.net/ch58678 [Hazama Masayoshi] has decided to become a superhero, despite having no superpowers or the technology to create a high-powered suit. He assumes the identity of http://anidb.net/ch60697 [Samurai Flamenco] and begins to fight crime in the name of justice. Police officer http://anidb.net/ch58679 [Gotou Hidenori] finds out about Samurai Flamenco and his real identity by a twist of fate, which leads to him getting involved into lots of trouble. Nonetheless, these two young men will come face to face with hardships of being crime-fighters while discovering what it truly means to be a hero of justice.
Source: ANN
Note: The first episode was pre-aired at a special event on 28.09.2013, regular TV broadcast started on 11.10.2013.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1130">4.56</permanent>
<temporary count="1138">6.32</temporary>
<review count="1">4.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>144072.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15498</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19365</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.samumenco.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Samurai_Flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>サムライフラメンコ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3192</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347044</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16498</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2131" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-19">
<name>psychotic</name>
<description>People suffering from psychosis can be described as having lost their contact with reality and deteriorated their social functioning to the point of becoming deranged. Sometimes, these people will try to achieve some absurd goal through trampling on other people, and that`s the point they become villains. Usually, psychotic villains will not show themselves to suffer from mental disorders at first, and will seem like completely normal people; however, as their story unfolds and the show progresses towards its climax, it is usual to have psychotic villains become more and more deranged, to the point of being best described by "batshit insane".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3135" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-16">
<name>hero complex</name>
<description>A hero complex is a state of mind in which an individual believes they need to save or assist others, uphold morals, serve justice, or perform other such supposedly hero-like acts, often at any cost. That is a common trait among vigilantes. Those with a hero complex may feel personally accountable for any failure at those self-assigned duties. Their main concern is performing their supposedly heroic deeds; any questions others might raise about such actions are all secondary concerns at best. Such questions can include, but are not limited to: who is to be saved; what are they to be saved from; why are they being saved; whether or not the other person needs or wants to be saved at all; whether or not others share in the sense of morals and justice being upheld; how people feel about the so-called heroic actions; whether people feel like those actions are being forced down their throats; what negative effects can arise from such actions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3824" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-05">
<name>sentai</name>
<description>In Japanese, sentai is a military unit, and may be translated as "squadron", "task force", "group" or "wing". In the anime fandom, however, it usually refers to the Super Sentai Series, a long-running superhero team franchise of http://anidb.net/t5000 [tokusatsu] shows featuring live action characters and colorful special effects, and other similar shows. A prominent characteristic of such shows is that the colour- and elemental-coded heroes, usually numbering around five or more, fight to save the world from the evil that terrorizes the area, which may even span the entire universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="58678" type="main character in" update="2013-11-22">
<rating votes="8">6.22</rating>
<name>Hazama Masayoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Masayoshi is a guy who used to admire superheros from childhood, thanks to his grandfather who loved action hero tv shows and comics.
He always has had a dream of becoming the hero of justice, so he asks a designer to design some superhero uniforms for him under the title of samurai flamenco. however, he has no abilities and logic over his actions and usually screws up and asks Gotou to rush over and help him. He is also a famous model</description>
<picture>145829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23805" picture="66166.jpg">Masuda Toshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58679" type="main character in" update="2013-11-13">
<rating votes="13">8.35</rating>
<name>Gotou Hidenori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A normal police officer guy who learns about Masayoshi`s secret by chance, and from that moment his life becomes more chaotic since he always has to rush over to clean up his mess and save him</description>
<picture>145828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58680" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-13">
<rating votes="14">3.94</rating>
<name>Maya Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58681" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-13">
<rating votes="5">6.02</rating>
<name>Misawa Mizuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58682" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-13">
<rating votes="4">4.78</rating>
<name>Morita Moe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37227" picture="195131.jpg">Yamazaki Erii</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59500" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-13">
<rating votes="3">4.06</rating>
<name>Kaname Jouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59501" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-13">
<rating votes="2">6.84</rating>
<name>Harazuka Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59502" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-13">
<rating votes="5">7.33</rating>
<name>Ishihara Sumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="234" picture="244740.jpg">Nakamura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59503" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-13">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Konno Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17631" picture="172640.jpg">Mikami Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60693" type="appears in" update="2013-10-21">
<name>Sawada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144634.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33017" picture="223810.jpg">Suzuki Haruhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60694" type="appears in" update="2013-10-21">
<name>Oba-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2460" picture="22350.jpg">Nagasawa Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60695" type="appears in" update="2013-10-21">
<name>Totsuka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60696" type="appears in" update="2013-10-21">
<name>Mineral Miracle Muse</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="60697" type="main character in" update="2013-10-21">
<rating votes="1">1.67</rating>
<name>Samurai Flamenco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23805" picture="66166.jpg">Masuda Toshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61759" type="appears in" update="2017-07-03">
<name>King Torture</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61760" type="appears in" update="2013-11-23">
<rating votes="1">9.56</rating>
<name>Guillotine Gorilla</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62170" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-09">
<rating votes="2">5.64</rating>
<name>Aoshima Souichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62171" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-09">
<rating votes="1">4.45</rating>
<name>Momoi Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62172" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-09">
<rating votes="2">5.94</rating>
<name>Midorikawa Hekiru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="303" picture="166016.jpg">Toyonaga Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62173" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-09">
<rating votes="2">6.25</rating>
<name>Kuroki Anji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="367" picture="17213.jpg">Kenn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63353" type="appears in" update="2014-01-23">
<name>Beyond Flamenco</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="151668" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-07-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Samurai Flamenco</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644879</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154910" update="2017-10-31">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サムライフラメンコ, デビュー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Debut of Samurai Flamenco!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Samurai Flamencos Debüt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les débuts de Samurai Flamenco</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samurai Flamenco, Debut!</title>
<summary>The setting is Shibiru City, Yukimachi Town. While most citizens are enjoying the peace and quiet, one young man makes a stand. His name is Hazama Masayoshi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644963</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154915" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傘がない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Umbrella`s Missing</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Schirm ist weg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je n`ai pas de parapluie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kasa ga Nai</title>
<summary>Shibiru City is now home to a superhero named Samurai Flamenco. By pure chance, policeman Goto Hidenori learns the identity of Samurai Flamenco, resulting in numerous headaches as he copes with the new hero`s atypical sense of justice. Goto arranges for a meeting to put a stop to all of the trouble, but Masayoshi shows up drenched.
Masayoshi explains that he doesn`t use umbrellas because of an incident in his past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644965</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154916" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">正義とは</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Meaning of Justice</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gerechtigkeit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Qu`est-ce que la Justice ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seigi to wa</title>
<summary>Samurai Flamenco is becoming jaded as Flamenco Girl runs him ragged. The police have been receiving an increasing number of complaints as the heroes wreak havoc.  Masayoshi struggles with his work as it seems that nothing is going right.
Masayoshi begins to wonder what it means to be a hero.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644971</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154917" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイドル蹂躙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Idol Devastation</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Idol</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Idol Devastation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idol Juurin</title>
<summary>After dealing with the imposter, Samurai Flamenco gets to catch his breath, but then he`s captured by some lawbreakers he approached.
When all hope appears to be lost, a mysterious new hero appears and saves him. However, the new hero knows Samurai Flamenco`s true identity and sees him as a rival. Samurai Flamenco now has a rival superhero. What next?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644969</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154918" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フラメンコVSニセフラメンコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flamenco vs. Fake Flamenco</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Flamenco gegen Flamenco</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Flamenco vs Faux Flamenco</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flamenco VS Nise Flamenco</title>
<summary>Samurai Flamenco is receiving more and more views on video sharing sites. Masayoshi is very pleased until a news site begins offering a reward to the person who unmasks Flamenco. That is when another person comes out as Samurai Flamenco. Who is this fake and what is his objective? The battle of Samurai Flamencos is about to begin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644967</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155875" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">猛攻! 悪の軍団</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack of the Army of Evil!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Angriff!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Attaque violente ! L`armée du Mal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moukou! Aku no Gundan</title>
<summary>A mysterious figure named King Torture has dispatched monsters across Japan.  They demand the unconditional surrender of the Japanese government and the enslavement of the populace.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644977</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155876" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チェンジ・ザ・ワールド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Change the World</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Change the world</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Change the World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Change the World</title>
<summary>Masayoshi`s efforts have paid off, as Shibiru City has seen a drop in crime.  His acting career is also picking up.  Life is looking good, but Masayoshi isn`t celebrating.  Instead, he begins to question what he should be doing as a hero.  Troubled, he returns to reading his grandfather`s notebook, but it turns out that the story of Samurai Flamenco hides a shocking secret.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644975</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155877" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サムメンコを捕まえろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Capture Samumenco!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schnappt Samu-menco!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Attrapez Flamenco !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samumenco o Tsukamaero!</title>
<summary>Flamenco Girl has powered up by recruiting additional Flamenco Girls!  She`s enjoying life as she fights evil and performs as an idol.  Meanwhile, Samurai Flamenco is on the run as the citizens have turned against him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644973</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156249" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキュメント! これがフラメンジャーだ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Document! We Are the Flamengers!!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das sind die Flamengers!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Document ! Voilà les Flamengers !!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Document! Kore ga Flamenger da!!</title>
<summary>Kaname turned out to be the commander of Samurai Base, a counter-secret-organization unit.  Masayoshi is joined by new allies, Soichi, Hekiru, Anji, and Sakura to form the Flamengers who fight to defeat From Beyond.  However, the Flamengers are very different people who struggle to work together.  As their leader, Masayoshi grows worried as monsters continue to attack.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644985</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156250" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">1.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フロム・ビヨンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Beyond</title>
<title xml:lang="de">From Beyond</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">From Beyond</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">From Beyond</title>
<summary>After King Torture`s death, Samurai Flamenco reveals his identify before the press. But in the next moment, Masayoshi is taken away in a aircraft that appears out of nowhere. At the same time, a giant fortress appears in Tokyo Bay. Out of the frying pan and into the fire. What will happen to Samurai Flamenco next?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644983</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156251" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! 敵の基地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Battle at the Enemy Base!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Entscheidungsschlacht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Défi final ! La base de l`ennemi !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Teki no Kichi</title>
<summary>Samurai Flamenco heads to the enemy base to save Flamenco Diamond. Flamenco Diamond and Flamenco Sapphire are undergoing torture after being captured.  Diamond tries to protect Sapphire, but King Torture reveals an inconvenient truth. Finally, Samurai Flamenco faces off against King Torture. The true objective of the Evil Army will come to light!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644981</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156252" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">抗えぬノルマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Predetermined Quota</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Quoten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une mission à laquelle je ne peux échapper</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aragaenu Norma</title>
<summary>The monsters have become part of everyday life. Their attacks are nothing more than a nuisance to the public, leaving Mari wanting more excitement. While the initial excitement has died down, the attention that is still being paid goes to the monsters and Samurai Flamenco.  Unhappy, Mari makes an unexpected move.  Meanwhile, Harazuka has a theory about the monsters` peculiar behavior.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644979</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156355" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156356" update="2013-11-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157220" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さすらいのヒーロー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wandering Hero</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Heimatloser Held</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Héros vagabond</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasurai no Hero</title>
<summary>The government has framed the Flamengers as terrorists who were responsible for the From Beyond attacks. They have also proposed a bill which bans vigilante activities.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644993</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157221" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イミテーション・ジャスティス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Imitation Justice</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Imitation Justice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Imitation/Justice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imitation Justice</title>
<summary>The monster that looks exactly like Masayoshi addresses him as Big Brother and calls himself Beyond Flamenco.  Masayoshi is visibly upset as Beyond Flamenco begins to speak about From Beyond`s purpose and objective. At the same time, it appears that the government also has another trick up its sleeve. How will the battle with From Beyond end?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644991</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157222" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニッポン壊滅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Destruction of Japan</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Japans Untergang</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`anéantissement du Japon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nippon Kaimetsu</title>
<summary>After the press conference, phones begin to ring across Japan. It turns out that the missing monsters of From Beyond are calling to announce their upcoming all-out attack. Little time remains. The Cabinet declares a national emergency and orders the JDF and police into action. After Kaname goes missing, the Flamengers are forced to take lead themselves. From Beyond`s attack is about to begin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644989</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157223" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦前夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Night Before the Decisive Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vor der Entscheidungsschlacht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La nuit avant le combat décisif</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen Zen`ya</title>
<summary>The Flamengers become the first citizens of Japan to receive the National Hero award as the country places its hope in them.  They are doing well in the battle against From Beyond, but one day, the monsters suddenly vanish.  It seems unlikely that they`ve given up on taking over Japan.  The Flamengers believe that an all-out attack may be coming and begin to prepare, but they encounter an unexpected obstacle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644987</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157790" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつか見た少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boy from the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Junge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un jeune homme que j`ai déjà vu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuka Mita Shounen</title>
<summary>The boy named Sawada Haiji has put an end to the temporary peace. He was one of the middle school students that Masayoshi had lectured as Samurai Flamenco.  Haiji declares that he is Masayoshi`s last enemy.  He then proceeds to attack the Flamengers, Kaname, and other people who are associated with Masayoshi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645001</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157791" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">静かな生活</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Quiet Life</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein ruhiges Leben</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une vie calme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shizuka na Seikatsu</title>
<summary>After battling Alien Flamenco and talking to the will of the universe, Masayoshi returns to Earth and finds peace and quiet in a world without evil.  There are no bad guys left, so Masayoshi no longer has anything to do as a superhero.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644999</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157792" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙でフラメンコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flamenco in Space</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Flamenco im All</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Flamenco dans l`espace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu de Flamenco</title>
<summary>With help from the resurrected Flamenco Girls, Masayoshi is able to defeat the Prime Minister. However, the government`s true objective wasn`t to defeat the superheroes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644997</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157793" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強総理</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ultimate Prime Minister</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der mächtigste Präsident</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le premier ministre le plus puissant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou Souri</title>
<summary>Masayoshi`s last hope is Goto. Goto gives him a warm welcome, despite the fact that he is a wanted fugitive. However, they immediately find themselves surrounded.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644995</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158462" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サムライフラメンコ・ネイキッド!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Samurai Flamenco Naked!!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Samurai Flamenco Naked</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Samurai Flamenco naked!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samurai Flamenco Naked!!</title>
<summary>A gunshot rings through the night. Masayoshi races to find Goto who has been captured by Haiji.  Masayoshi wanted to be a hero. Goto wanted to hold onto his girlfriend.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645005</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158463" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛をおしえて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaching Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Liebe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Apprends-moi l`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai o Oshiete</title>
<summary>Masayoshi thinks about taking his own life to stop Haiji. After multiple incidents and an argument with Goto, Masayoshi runs into another wall as he attempts to track down Haiji. Goto is also in a difficult position. That is when Haiji makes his next move.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>645003</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-flamenco</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158696" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158697" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158698" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158699" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158700" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158701" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158702" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158703" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158704" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158705" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
