<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="997" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-01-21</startdate>
<enddate>1997-04-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ayane-chan High Kick!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">綾音ちゃんハイキック!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ayane`s High Kick</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="633721">it`s one of the very first anime i chose instead of just watching it because it was on tv</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="4558" type="Character Design">Takigawa Kazuo</name>
<name id="1086" type="Work">Rikuentai</name>
<name id="5401" type="Original Work">Okao Takahiro</name>
<name id="5401" type="Direction">Okao Takahiro</name>
<name id="6018" type="Music">Inoue Nittoku</name>
</creators>
<description>Ayane Mitsui is a High School student who wants to become a pro wrestler. She sets this as her most important goal, neglecting school and other responsibilities. This is Ayane`s ultimate dream. At the beginning of the tape we find Ayane at the All-Japan Women`s Pro Wrestling Try-Outs. She fails to get accepted yet afterwards meets a strange old man who saw her audition. He tells her that she has great legs and wishes for her to join his Dojo so that he could train her. She accepts and training begins that night. They start by building the ring, and then continue the next day after school with practicing kicks. Ayane practices everyday while having to hide these events from her mother and her school`s assistant principal who detests violent sports. After weeks of hard training we find Ayane going in to take a test which she thinks is for Pro Wrstling, but in actuality it`s for kickboxing. Totally off the road of her goal, she blindly follows the trainer in her quest to become a wrestler. Her trainer is constantly hiding his real intentions from her (to be a kickboxer) throughout the entire tape until Ayane`s debut fight. All is pulled out into the open as she finally discovers what she has gotten into as the bell is rung...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="316">3.61</permanent>
<temporary count="319">5.80</temporary>
<review count="1">6.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>5277.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>515</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2183</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>55</identifier>
<identifier>bfxlyx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ayane's_High_Kick</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>綾音ちゃんハイキック!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1439</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88184</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="10237" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私はプロレスラーになるのだ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Going to Be a Pro Wrestler!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi wa Pro Wrestler ni Naru no Da!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10238" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ポニーテールのイヤな奴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nasty Ponytail</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ponytail no Iya na Yatsu</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
