<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9985" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2013-10-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ansatsu Kyoushitsu</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Assassination Classroom (2013)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Assassination Classroom Jump Festa 2013 Special</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Assassination Classroom Jump Super Anime Tour 2013 Special</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">暗殺教室</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">암살교실</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10702" type="Other">Ansatsu Kyoushitsu (2015)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.jumpfesta.com/anime/ansatukyoucitu.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1704" type="Character Design">Shibata Katsunori</name>
<name id="982" type="Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="8467" type="Original Work">Matsui Yuusei</name>
<name id="1725" type="Direction">Gotou Keiji</name>
<name id="3399" type="Music">Kikuya Tomoki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr8467 [Matsui Yuusei]`s comedy manga.
A strange tentacled creature suddenly vaporised 70% of the moon in an explosion. It can slink around at 20 times the speed of sound; it also has a 10 billion yen price on its head. Yet, for some reason, it ended up becoming a teacher for a middle school class at the beginning of the school year. The students now have until graduation to assassinate their teacher, or it will destroy the Earth as well.
Source: ANN
Note: Part of the Jump Super Anime Tour 2013 (ジャンプスーパーアニメツアー2013) event, which traveled to five cities throughout Japan from October 6 to November 24, 2013.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="671">4.81</permanent>
<temporary count="678">6.44</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>148276.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15534</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19759</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jumpfesta.com/anime/ansatukyoucitu.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ansatsu_Kyōshitsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>暗殺教室</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348083</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3841" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-18">
<name>Jump Super Anime Tour</name>
<description>Animes released in the Jump Super Anime Tour.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="60049" type="main character in" update="2014-11-10">
<rating votes="119">8.55</rating>
<name>Koro-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60050" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-29">
<rating votes="111">6.94</rating>
<name>Shiota Nagisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60051" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-01">
<rating votes="39">6.22</rating>
<name>Kayano Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60052" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="98">7.88</rating>
<name>Akabane Karma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60053" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-20">
<rating votes="16">4.91</rating>
<name>Sugino Tomohito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3189" picture="81680.jpg">Honjou Yuutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60054" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-01">
<rating votes="29">5.07</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Yukiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60055" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-29">
<rating votes="49">7.78</rating>
<name>Karasuma Tadaomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60056" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-29">
<rating votes="70">6.56</rating>
<name>Irina Jelavic</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60057" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-27">
<rating votes="7">3.31</rating>
<name>Red Eye</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181837.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68164" type="appears in" update="2014-06-24">
<rating votes="4">1.00</rating>
<name>Ryuuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68165" type="appears in" update="2014-10-20">
<rating votes="8">2.72</rating>
<name>Mimura Kouki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39679" picture="152239.jpg">Yamaguchi Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68166" type="appears in" update="2015-08-01">
<rating votes="27">5.97</rating>
<name>Nakamura Rio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40321" picture="157158.jpg">Tabata Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68167" type="appears in" update="2017-03-27">
<rating votes="29">5.55</rating>
<name>Kurahashi Hinano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurahashi`s personality is best described as "yurufuwa" (a person who is warm, gentle, and relaxing). She is an energetic and positive girl and is always seen with a smile on face regardless of whether she`s trying to assassinate Korosensei, or whatever else. She`s an animal and nature lover as shown in Chapter 56. She was also noted to be a "reliable assistant" for the group of boys who are on the path to becoming "sleazebags." This stems from the fact that she has older siblings who are all boys and as a result can handle even the sleaziest talk. She is a very soothing and calming person and is described as being innocent and genuine. She is also good at making money, particularly being able to assess the price of the stag beetles she was hoping to capture and sell and at the end of the manga managing to get parents to pay her handsomely to take their kids on nature hikes.</description>
<picture>163018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39786" picture="223840.jpg">Fukuyama Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68168" type="appears in" update="2014-10-20">
<rating votes="10">5.45</rating>
<name>Maehara Hiroto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="367" picture="17213.jpg">Kenn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68169" type="appears in" update="2015-08-01">
<rating votes="20">5.46</rating>
<name>Hara Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40243" picture="239174.jpg">Yamane Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68170" type="appears in" update="2015-08-01">
<rating votes="27">5.89</rating>
<name>Okuda Manami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27221" picture="131964.jpg">Arakawa Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68171" type="appears in" update="2014-11-16">
<rating votes="6">4.77</rating>
<name>Okajima Taiga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39787" picture="191405.jpg">Nakatsukasa Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68172" type="appears in" update="2015-08-01">
<rating votes="11">5.16</rating>
<name>Okano Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38429" picture="141830.jpg">Hino Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68173" type="appears in" update="2014-10-20">
<rating votes="8">3.63</rating>
<name>Kimura Masayoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163019.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68174" type="appears in" update="2014-11-16">
<rating votes="8">2.08</rating>
<name>Muramatsu Takuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40318" picture="223674.jpg">Miyamoto Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68175" type="appears in" update="2015-08-01">
<rating votes="21">5.11</rating>
<name>Kataoka Megu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29955" picture="157037.jpg">Gotou Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68176" type="appears in" update="2015-08-01">
<rating votes="28">5.87</rating>
<name>Hazama Kirara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164259.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40320" picture="157159.jpg">Sakamoto Asumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68177" type="appears in" update="2015-08-01">
<rating votes="22">6.61</rating>
<name>Yada Touka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33959" picture="203633.jpg">Toda Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68178" type="appears in" update="2014-10-20">
<rating votes="12">5.47</rating>
<name>Isogai Yuuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37466" picture="225911.jpg">Uemura Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68179" type="appears in" update="2015-08-01">
<rating votes="18">4.84</rating>
<name>Hayami Rinka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31971" picture="85817.jpg">Morisaki Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74829" type="appears in" update="2016-01-27">
<rating votes="4">1.21</rating>
<name>Tanaka Nobuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181836.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="74830" type="appears in" update="2016-01-27">
<rating votes="4">1.21</rating>
<name>Takada Chousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181835.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="152145" update="2015-01-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2013-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
